Question 1
You hear this news item on the radio
Who has been arrested
Hey
Harold Wilson
Be
Ronald malench
See
Okay I'm Khan
Manjile supporting prime minister Harold Wilson signature
20 years ago is back behind bars
Ronald Milling isn't Hong Kong Christmas l.a. waiting trial later this month on fraud and Firearm charges
56 year old was jailed for three years in 1974 for trying to prove that mr. Wilson was involved
In Allendale niggun
17 months I did 1918 move to the Philippines
The new woman in his life all kind of con18 who shares his minute of home settings current Venture was in
Importing radio cassette players into China
Dimensional for forging prime minister Harold Wilson signature
20 years ago is back behind bars
Ronald Village isn't Hong Kong prison cell awaiting trial later this month on fraud and Firearm charges
The 56 year-old was jailed for three years in 1974 for trying to prove that mr. Wilson was involved
In Allendale niggun
17 months I did 1918 move to the Philippines
The new woman in his life all kind of con18
Coushatta is Manila home settings current Venture with importing radio cassette players into China
Question 2
You overhear this telephone conversation in a car spare parts shop
The person speaking is
Hey
The manager
Be a customer
See a secretary
Then it's my thoughts can I help you the order the party place
I'm sorry about that
No I'm afraid I can't send you a replacement package I didn't have the authority to do that you'll need to speak to Miss Brown
Seth Lisa I'll put you through now
Then it's my thoughts can I help you
I'm sorry about that
No I'm afraid I can't send you a replacement package I didn't have the authority to do that you'll need to speak
Chris Brown
Fashionista I'll put you through now
Question three
You hear friend reading something aloud
She is reading from
Hey
A diet book
Be a cookery book
See the hotel brochure
You can eat you like me
Whatever suits you best
You can say fruetel yokuts from Emil to have it this night during the day it is important
Quite often I gain weight is just due to eating too much
Rather than eating the wrong Foods
Dunno that sold in cooking or at the table
Low-calorie dressing may be used in salads
You can eat your light meal
Whichever suits you best
You can say fruits Hill Yogurt from a meal to have a snack during the day
It is important to weigh your food
Quite often I gain weight is just due to eating too much
Rather than eating the wrong Foods
Do you know that sells in cooking or at the table
Low-calorie dressing may be used in salads
Question for
You overhear this conversation in a shop
The shop is
A butcher shop
A Baker's shop
Be aggressive shop
Good morning
Message where are you ready for the holidays
Morning George
Yes
With your family coming I got to buy a lot more than usual
Planning to do some bacon
And I suppose
Good
Are you ready for the holidays Minecart
Yes
With your family coming I got to buy a lot more than usual
Spanish
And I suppose
Question 5
You hear friend reading something aloud from
A holiday Persia
Be
A history book
See
A storybook
Welcome to the land of Cinderella consoled
Once upon a time in a Faraway land to live the king cold Ludwig dearest wish was to make all of his subjects
So he built them fairytale consoles soon the land had the most beautiful castles in the world
How far away is Germany
Atlanta full of beautiful surprises
So come to the land of Cinderella consoles the land of Ludwig the land of Happily Ever After
Welcome to the land of Cinderella castles
Once upon a time in a Faraway land the Luther King childhood week-old of his subjects
So he built them fairytale consoles soon the land had the most beautiful consoles in the world
A Faraway land was Germany
Atlanta full of beautiful surprises so come to the land of Cinderella consoles the land of Ludwig
Orlando happily ever after
Question 6
Listen to this summary of a man's career
The man is about to be
Hey
Interviewed on TV
Be interviewed for a job
See
Interviewed about his book
The next candidate left University 21 and what is a farm in Botswana for 3 years
Then he joined why agricultural College as an extra
He's been promoted twice he's Publix one Broken Heart.
Impressive
Okay
The next candidate left University 21 and what is a phone in Botswana for 3 years
Then he joined why agricultural coloreds as an extra
He's been promoted twice he's published one book on herb garden
He looks very impressive
Okay
Question 7
A young couple of thinking of moving house
I'm talking about the move
They think that moving house will
Hey
Cause huge problems
Be
Byc effort
See
Be too expensive to be possible
Commando unit
So many more space and it's a nice neighborhood
Yes but it would mean the children moving schools just when they settled into the ones that right now
We could manage
Recommended
So many more space and it's a nice neighborhood
Yes but it would mean the children moving schools
Yeah that is a nuisance and what about the car so it's pretty high
Sure we can manage
Questions 8
You want to order cassette of jazz music from White World Book & Music shop
You hear this message
What you have to do next is to
A
Wait
Be
Leave a message
Speed
Call another number
Thank you for calling whitewalls Book & Music shop
I'm sorry older lines busy at the moment but your call has been queued
If you were calling about fixing that non-fiction books please hold the line and we will answer you soon or he may live in
Message after the tone
If you recording about feet or recorded music please call my music department Direct on 96-81
2 / 2863 thank you
Thank you for calling whitewalls Book & Music shop at the moment
Husband cute
If you're calling about fiction and nonfiction book please hold the line and we will answer you soon or humanely.
Message after the tone
If you recording about people recorded music please call my music department Direct on 96-81
Tuple 28/63 thank you