Questions 14 through 18
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Ray what are you doing here in the library after school don't you have soccer practice to it
Actually mrs. boss I decided not to play on the team this year
I'm going to focus on my grades instead
Focus on your grades but you're already getting all A's
In fact I'm pretty sure that you've never gotten anything below and A- since elementary
Country School
Yes ma'am that's correct
But I want to make sure my grades don't drop this year after all
I'm applying to a lot of top colleges
Ray do you mind if I give you a little bit of advice
Not at all man I'm always willing to accept advice
Especially if it's free colleges especially the best ones in the country
Don't just want students who have good grades
They don't
Well grades are important of course
But most colleges are looking for well-rounded individuals in other words they wants to
Students who not only have good grades but who also participated in various extracurricular activity
I think I see what you're getting at
I hope so
What I'm trying to say is that if you don't play sports or don't belong to any clubs no matter
How good your grades are you're going to have a harder time getting into an elite College
So talk to Coach Patterson and see if he'll let you on the team
Yes ma'am I think I'll do that
Now answer the questions
Number 14 what did the voice stop doing this year