Questions 19 through 22 listen to a conversation between two students
David how is driver's ed today you got to drive on the road for the first time today
I didn't you
Yeah Beth I did
It didn't go too well
You didn't crash the car or anything did you owe no please tell me you didn't
I didn't crash the car but
Okay spell it I think I scared Miss Hooper while I was driving
Miss Hooper art teacher
Yeah here's what happened
When I pulled out of the school parking lot I guess I pressed down on the accelerator too hard so the tire
Tires squeal pretty loudly
I'm surprised you didn't hear it from your classroom
Oh so that's what that noise was
Okay nevermind
Anyway as I left the school I happen to pull out in front of a car that was going really fast
So it almost hit us
Fortunately the driver managed to stop at the last moment
I was pretty shaken up by that
So I didn't notice that the first stoplight we came to was red
I drove right through it without even stopping
I can't believe I broke the law like that
You didn't I did
I guess Miss Hooper had had enough by then since you told me to pull over and mediately
She made me sit in the passenger seat
Was he drove back to school
She berated me about my driving skills the entire trip back
I guess that you're not going to be driving in class again for a long time
That's what Miss Hooper said
Now answer the questions
Number 19 what is the girl mean when she says this
Spill it