Questions 23 through 25 listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Mrs. Campbell do you think I could have a word with you
I need to talk to you about something
Sure Larry are you hear about your grade on the book report
Yes ma'am
I'm not really sure why I got a C+ on it
I mean I thought I followed your directions
This is the lowest grade I've ever gotten at school will Larry there were a lot of
Obama's with your paper I could have easily given you a lower grade but it seemed obvious to me
That you had tried hard while writing it
A lower grade
Did you bring the paper with you I can show you a few things if you have it here
Yes ma'am I got it right here just a minute
I hear it is
Alright let's look
No do you see this fart
That's a run-on sentence that's bad grammar so you lost points for that
Okay
And you didn't use quotes here
Right here you use the wrong verb tense you know Larry you really need to work on your grass
You had so many of those mistakes on your paper I guess I've never cared that much of a grandma
I never seen that important
You're going to have to get a new attitude toward it now if your grammar isn't any good in my class there's
No way that you'll get an A or a B I C I'll start reviewing Grandma as soon as school is done
And today
That's a good attitude good luck Larry
Now answer the questions
Number 23
What are the speakers talking about