Now you will hear longer talks or conversations
Each talk or conversation will be followed by three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between a student and a principal
Good morning Molly
Please have a seat in this chair
As the principal of this school I'd like to be the first person to welcome you here
Thank you sir I'm very glad to be a new student at Briarwood
I'm happy to hear that
Milk before you attend your first class do you have any questions for me
Not right now sir I'm sure I'll have some questions later but
I guess I don't really know what to ask at the moment
Alright
In that case let me tell you a little bit about what we expect from you at this school
Sure
First of all here at Briarwood we take the honor code very seriously so there is to be no cheating
That means no cheating on homework test presentations or other assignments
In addition we frown upon lying here
I understand
Good student who cheat or lie are severely punished
Do it twice and we will kick you out
But you seem like a nice young lady so I'm sure we won't have any problems like that with you
I hope not sir is there anything else
Yes there's one more thing before you go to class
Please understand that you can talk to me anytime you have questions or problems
I know it's not easy being a transfer student in the middle of the semester
It might take you a while to adjust here
But I want to see you succeed
So please come to my office if there is anything bothering you
Okay if I have any problems I'll be sure to talk to you about them
Now answer the questions
Number 10
What is the principal explaining