Test 2 part 4 Page 65
Directions
You are going to hear some talks given by one speaker
You are going to be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter A B C
4D on your answer sheet on page 202
The talks are not printed in your test book and will be spoken only once
Question 71 273 refer to the following message
Hi this is Janet Suzuka from the office I'm sorry to bother you on the weekend
But I need to let everyone know that our email system has been hacked
At around 2 a.m. on Friday a person or persons hacked the system and
And retrieved all the email addresses of our employees
These addresses were then used all day on Saturday to send advertisement
To every address saved in each account
This means that every client you have ever emailed and every friend or associate
You have messaged got some very annoying messages in their inboxes
I was alerted to the problem Sunday morning and I'm working to resolve the problem right now
I'm very sorry for the inconvenience and I promise to strengthen our security systems
Right away call me at the office if you have any questions
What is the purpose of this message
When was the system hacked
What is the speaker doing right now
Question 74 276 refer to the following announcement
The ferry to Catalina Island will leave in 20 minutes
Please have all vehicles ready to board in 5 minutes
If your vehicle is not in line with the appropriate sticker on the window at that time you cannot drive onto the
Siri
Windows ticket passes can be purchased at the booth in the northwest corner of the parking lot
Do passengers on foot please have tickets ready and one form of identification
The trip will take approximately one hour
Return tickets can be purchased at our destination
Thank you and have a good day
Who is listening to this announcement
What must cars have in order to board
How long is the trip
Question 77 to 79 refer to the following advertisement
Are you a small-business owner who is wondering how to make social media work for you
Would you like to expand your customer base significantly without spending much money
If the answer is yes please text social contact to 1-800
98-79 999
And a customer services representative from social contact will return your call within the hour
Please have your credit card ready
Off the payment is processed a personal advisor will help you with a business plan to bring
New marketing strategy into the 21st century
We can start helping you today
Remember it's as easy as texting social contact to 1-800
98.7 9999
What is the purpose of this advertisement
Who should send a text to this number
What do you need to have when the representative calls you
Questions 8282 refer to the following announcement
Thank you for coming in on such short notice
As you all know we have been in negotiations for months with garabelli the famed cha
Chocolatiers from Italy
Acquiring garabelli as another part of this company would be a huge game for us as
The international brand recognition for this name is very high
So Not only would we see an immediate Rising sales nationally we would also be
Entering into the European candy Market
Well I am extremely pleased to announce today that an agreement has been reached and Gyro
Belly becomes part of the Bradbury family today
Who is listening to this announcement
Why is this deal so important
When will these two companies merge
Questions 83 285 refer to the following message
Hello this is Gina from Horizon mobile returning a call from Mr Glenmont
Martinez
Mr. Martinez had a question about the refund for the mobile phone he recently bought from us
In order to receive the refund $100 he must mail in the refunds card
Plus a copy of his receipt to all head offices
Please address the envelope to Horizon mobile refund Center 16
16 Gateway Drive Philadelphia PA
Just to reiterate this is a mail-in refund only and cannot be submit
Email or fax mr. Martinez has 30 days to mail the documents
If the envelope is postmarked more than 30 days after the date of purchase the refund offer
Is invalid
If you have any questions please call us back at 7 for 6
5656 thank you
Where would this message be heard
When did mr. Martinez buy his phone
How should the refund card be sent
Questions 86 288 refer to the following talk
Hello all and welcome to the meeting please take a seat
Please direct your attention to the screen at the front of the room for the agenda as you can see
See the first item of business to discuss is the parking lot situation
By law we are required to designate at least 10 of our parking spaces for Des
Disabled people
Currently we only have two so we must decide who will give up his or her
Spot for this purpose
Second on the agenda is a brainstorming session for the regional sales meeting that we are
Are hosting this year
We have a lot of details to iron out for this huge event
Lastly I will be presenting an award to the salesperson of the month
Okay ask for the parking
Who is the speaker
How many more disabled parking spaces are needed
What is not on the agenda for today's meeting
Questions 89 291 refer to the following presentation
Thank you so much for coming to this meeting
I've invited all the small business owners in the area to attend tonight to discuss the huge chain super
Install glamour's which just open nearby
All over the country these enormous stores have opened and soon all the surrounding independent
Lyon stores. Shutdown
Glamour has stores all over the globe
And their purchasing power is enormous
Therefore they can buy and sell any product at much lower prices than our smaller businesses I able to
The Aloha prices coupled with offering everything a person needs in one place guarantees
Is it a sales will drop as glamorous flourishes
So what are our options here
How can we compete in the future with glamour's
What is the purpose of this meeting
According to the speaker what is the effect of a glamour opening
How does glamour attract shoppers
Questions 92 294 refer to the following presentation
Today we are opening the doors of a cutting-edge project
A project that is near and dear to me
As I've been working on this idea for nearly a decade
At long last the Community Technology Centre is ready to help people
This is a place where anyone of any age race or background can learn and
Floor ideas that are relevant in the modern world
We don't offer basketball cards and a swimming pool as traditional Community Center stew
Rather we consider ourselves more of an educational Institution
Are you having trouble searching for jobs
Come see our job counselor and learn how to use internet resources efficiently and
Effectively
Do you feel your general computer skills are not meeting today's employment requirements
Drop in and check out our class schedule or sign up for a free private tutor
In addition to these Services we would offer
Why is this woman introducing the project
What is a facility that can be used at the center
What group of people will likely get help at the center
Questions 95 297 refer to the following speech
Hi there my name is mister young and I'm going to be taking you around the showroom floor today
I understand that you are opening a new branch office here in town and you need a great deal of nuance
Office furniture
Since you will be buying so many pieces from us you will be receiving a significant discount on oil
Purchases
First let's take a look at desks you can see we have reception desks Elsa
Shapes desks u-shaped desks and executive desks
Every model is available in Black
Brown off-white
Alternatively if you need to set up a room with cubicles we do off of workstations as well
Moving onto storage
These file cabinets are lost Year's model so they are on sale now but we're guessing in new ones tomorrow
Media storage centers are on the left in front of the bookcases
Now let's take a look at something very important to employee health
Chaz
Where is the speaker
Why is a large discount being given to these customers
What will the speaker do now
Questions 98 to 100 refer to the following announcement
Attention passengers
We are experiencing some technical problems and are being forced to make an unscheduled stop
In Paris
Due to storm activity in the area The Landing may be a bit bumpy but please.
Advise that any turbulence is normal and by no means dangerous
Once we land we may be grounded for quite a while because of the storms
Although we are being allowed to land Charles de Gaulle Airport is not letting any planes take
Off tonight
Therefore all passengers on this flight will receive a fifty-year-old food voucher
Redeemable anywhere in the airport plus another voucher good for one night at Annie
Nearby Hotel
Please go to the MBA airdesk upon disembarking for these vouchers
According to reports we should be able to take off in the morning
Why are they Landing in Paris
When will they most likely be able to continue their Journey
Where will the passengers sleep