Hello all and welcome to the meeting
Please take a seat
Please direct your attention to the screen at the front of the room for the agenda
As you can see the first item of business to discuss is the parking lot situation
By law we are required to designate at least 10 of our parking spaces for Dish
Disabled people
Currently we only have two so we must decide who will give up his or her
Spot for this purpose
Second on the agenda is a brainstorming session for the regional sales meeting that we are
You're hosting this year
We have a lot of details to iron out for this huge event
Lastly I will be presenting an award to the salesperson of the month
Okay ask for the parking
Who is the speaker
How many more disabled parking spaces are needed
What is not on the agenda for today's meeting
Thank you so much for coming to this meeting
I've invited all the small business owners in the area to attend tonight to discuss the huge chain super
Install glamour's which just open nearby
All over the country these enormous stores have opened and soon all the surrounding independent
Lyon stores. Shutdown
Glamour has stores all over the globe
And their purchasing power is enormous
Therefore they can buy and sell any product at much lower prices than our smaller businesses I able to
The Aloha prices coupled with offering everything a person needs in one place
Guarantees that I sales will drop as glamorous flourishes
So what are our options here
How can we compete in the future with glamour's
What is the purpose of this meeting
According to the speaker
What is the effect of a glamorous opening
How does Klamath attract shoppers
Today we are opening the doors of a cutting-edge project a project that does Nia and theater
As I've been working on this idea for nearly a decade
At long last the Community Technology Centre is ready to help people
This is a place where anyone of any age race or background can learn and ask
Floor ideas that are relevant in the modern world
We don't offer basketball cards and a swimming pool as traditional Community Center stew
Rather we consider ourselves more of an educational Institution
Are you having trouble searching for jobs
Come see our job counselor and learn how to use internet resources efficiently and
Effectively
Do you feel your general computer skills are not meeting today's employment requirements
Drop in and check out our class schedule or sign up for a free private tutor
In addition to these Services we would offer
Why is this woman introducing the project
9 is a facility that can be used at the center
What group of people will likely get help at the center
Hi there my name is mister young and I'm going to be taking you around the showroom floor today
I understand that you are opening a new branch office here in town and you need a great deal of new
Office furniture
Since you will be buying so many pieces from us you will be receiving a significant discount on oil
First let's take a look at desks
You can see we have reception desks
L-shaped desks
U-shaped desks and executive desks
Every model is available in black brown or off-white
Alternatively if you need to set up a room with cubicles we do off of workstations as well
Moving onto storage
These file cabinets are lost is modal so they are on sale now but we're guessing in new ones tomorrow
Media storage centers are on the left in front of the bookcases
Now let's take a look at something very important to employee health
Chaz
Where is the speaker
Why is a large discount being given to these customers
What will the speaker do now
Attention passengers
We are experiencing some technical problems and are being forced to make an unscheduled stop
In Paris
Due to storm activity in the area The Landing may be a bit bumpy but please be
He advised that any turbulence is normal and by no means dangerous
Once we land we may be grounded for quite a while because of the storms
Although we are being allowed to land Charles de Gaulle Airport is not letting any planes take
Kickoff tonight
Therefore all passengers on this flight will receive a fifty-year-old food voucher
Redeemable anywhere in the airport plus another voucher good for one night at a
Nearby Hotel
Please go to the MBA airdesk upon disembarking for these vouchers
According to reports we should be able to take off in the morning
Why are they Landing in Paris
When will they most likely be able to continue their Journey
Where will the passengers sleep