Questions 3333
Listen to a teacher talking in a history class
Two of the oldest civilizations in human history our Egypt
And Mesopotamia
We talked about both of them during the past two days right
As I hope you all remember
They were fairly different societies
But I want to talk today about how they had some similarities
For one rather large structures
No
When I mention Egypt what do you usually think about
Yeah that's right pyramids
The Egyptians build pyramids all over the place
Many of them are still standing
Okay
But when I mention Mesopotamia
What kinds of buildings do you think about
No one
Yeah that's what I thought
Well the Mesopotamians build cigarettes
That's ziggurats
There's a picture of them on page 218 in your books
Take a look
Here's a picture of a pyramid as you can see
The main differences between the two are there shapes and sizes
Notice that the Egyptian pyramid is more triangular in shape
Also the pyramid is smooth-sided and its sides are rather steep
But look at the ziggurat here
You can see that it has a step appearance
By step
I mean that the ziggurat look like it has different levels doesn't it
It looks sort of like a lot of different size boxes stacked on top of one another
The biggest box is on the bottom and the boxes get smaller as you go higher
Oh and noticed that the ziggurat has a set of stairs leading to the tub
The pyramid Laxus
Why did cigarettes have stairs
Each had a temple at the top
So the Mesopotamians climb the stairs to reach the temple
This brings me to another key difference
Ziggurats were places of worship
They were used by priests to pray to the various Mesopotamian gods
But the pyramids were tunes for the Pharaohs
They were the kings of ancient Egypt
Many pharaohs built pyramids to be their tombs when they died
The largest one took nearly 20 years to build
How did the Egyptians and Mesopotamians build these huge structures
That's a good question
No one is sure
But people have some theories
Let me tell you about a few of them right now
Now answer the questions
Number 30
What is the main idea of the talk