Questions 27 through 29
Listen to a teacher talking in a biology class
All the species of squirrels that exist probably the most interesting one is the flying squirrel
It doesn't really fly though after all this girl doesn't have wings and it can't take off from
The ground either
Instead of flying it Glides
How is it able to do that
It's body has a special membrane that stretches between its legs and feed
This membrane is found on both sides of its body it's made of skin and fur and is very
Flexible
Normally the membrane is tucked along the sides of its body
Take a look at the picture on page 156 in your books
See it
That Ridge like fold of fur along its side is the membrane
What does the squirrel do with that membrane
Let me tell you
First
In order to take to the air the Flying Squirrel needs to be high above the ground
It typically jumps from tall trees
When it leaps into the air it stretches its legs
This causes the membrane to unfold and to become taught
I guess it's sort of like
Like a parachute at that point
This membrane catches the air and allows the squirrel to Glide
In some cases
It can even act like a wing and enable the squirrel to gain a small amount of altitude
Yes Gina
How far can one of these squirrels Glide
In general they make relatively short Glides of around 5 2:30 however
The longest Glide ever observed by a person was nearly 90 m
Why don't we take a look at a video
And then you can see the flying squirrel in action
Now answer the questions
Number 27 what is the teacher mainly talking about