Questions 34 through 38
Listen to a teacher talking in a biology class
One of the most beautiful creatures in the forest is the deer
It lives pretty much everywhere in the world except for Australia and Antarctica
There are many species of deer
However the one I want to talk about is the white-tailed deer
It mostly lives in North America
I'm sure that many of you have seen this deer before
I actually saw a couple of them near the road as I drove to school this morning
Anyway the first thing I should mention is that we have different names for male and female deer
The mail is usually called a buck
Some people call it a stag or a heart though
That's Hart not heart
The female deer on the other hand is called a do
And a baby deer is a fawn
There are several differences between Stags and doze
A stag is bigger than a do
A stag weighs 100 kg on average
However some of them can grow to be much larger than that
As for females they averaged around 70 kg in weight
Another big difference between the two is antlers
Antlers are the long sharp pointed bony protrusions on a deer's head
They begin as Too Short stubby knobs
As they grow they can form several branches that have many points
But only Stags have antlers
Those don't have them
Oh here's something you might not know
Antlers fall off every year
Stags lose their antlers during the winter and then new ones grow during the Spring and Summer
Deer are mammals so that means the mothers give birth to live animals
I do has between one and three fawns when it gives birth
The Fawns have white spots when they're born
For the first six weeks of their lives they drink their mother's milk
Remember that's another characteristic of mammals
Bonds don't exclusively drink milk
They can walk pretty much as soon as they're born
So they can forage for grass and other food right away
Now answer the questions
Number 34
What is the teacher mainly talking about