Directions
You will hear some short talks given by single speaker
What the speaker says select the best response
BC
Copy printed in your textbook
The 25th Annual International textile trade show will be held from
October 21st and will include International
Textile manufacturers such as
Sponsors of the fashion houses
And Prada is expected
Approximately 45% of the participants are expected to be foreign companies and by the
Coming from all over the world
The expected number of attendance is expected to easily exceed 5,000
Number 71
What is
Number 72
How many businesses are expected to participate
Number 73
Among this year's participants how many companies are predicted to be from overseas
Question 7476
The Consular section
If you are interested in receiving
You can pick them up
Number 74
Why is Big getting this message
Number 75
When does the embassy close on Fridays
Number 76
How can a person wanting to get a Visa
Question 77 through 79
It is with great pleasure that I
Angelina Sanchez she's currently the head professor of psychology at
Has written
Psychology
Presently
Number 77
What is Dante Sanchez is made of division
Number 78
What is today
Number 79
What is Miss Sanchez's most publicized work
Questions
Thank you for allowing me to attend the meeting today my name is John Lucas and I am with the safety inspection
Sun protection board As You Are
Petoskey completed
And during this process you will also have the responsibility of making sure that your team
Safety and protection adequately supervise
For this reason we are going to go through the safety inspection and protection board policy and procedures manual
So that you can understand exactly what is expected of you during your supervisory roles
Who is the
According to the speaker what is the responsibility
Number 82
Next
Go on to the next page
Questions 83 through 85
Mesmerizing
Covers for the past 20 years
Help me
For Delia Delight
Number 83
How long has the singer been performing
Number 84
Which one
Number 85
According to the speaker what did most music
Questions 86-88
Welcome to our 5th annual educators conference this morning we will open the 1st
Lecture entitled challenges and changes in teaching for the 21st century
Which starts at 9 a.m. and lasts until 11 a.m.
Then we will have some time set aside to mix and mingle before we break for lunch at 11:30
We recommend making lunch appointment with our other guests
You will have the choice of attending any of the 27
The 27 oz will run until 3
The first seminoff is entitled
A second seminaries eLearning
Number 86
How often is the event held
Who is the
Number 88
Next
Question
Thank you for calling the technical support
Unfortunately customer representative
Taking inquiries regarding
Please do not hang up as your business is important to us
Assist you
Right now the estimated waiting time is 2 minutes
If you'd like to check the states
Please
Will tentatively can relax and listen to the music
Sprite
Who would most likely hear this message
Number 90
Number 91
How can I get information about the account status
Question business
Emerge
Remaining
Through this purchase
Number 92
What is the report about
Number 93
According to the report what happened
Number 94
Who is Bill Graham
Questions
Hello this message is for Mister Jorge Mateo my name is
Resources department
Accounting department
Days convenience
Send me an email
Stating whether this day will be acceptable for you or not
If this day is not good for you please leave an alternative time
I will send a confirmation reply
Thank you
Why is the message
Number 96
What department does mismo
Number 97
According to Jane
Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following
On your camera
On Today Show on the island of Cancun Mexico with some of the craziest
Angeles
Tables
And the technician MK regular putting on this
Special effects
Open the program we sing some of the wildest and craziest Antics by some of the hottest
Stick around
Number 98
How often does the show air
Number 99
What is Freddy's occupation
Number 100
Where is the show being aired today