Questions 71 through 73 refer to the following advertisement
Have you been looking for an affordable way to stock your office supply closet with quality product
And don't miss this unique opportunity
You've always relied on office supplies Incorporated to provide you with the best products at the best prices
Now we are announcing our biggest sale of the year
With fantastic savings on all items big and small
From pens to photocopy machines
Our doors open at 8 a.m. tomorrow and everything in the entire store will be reduced by fifty percent
Percent for 3 big days
Thursday through Saturday
Sale ends Saturday at 6 p.m. so hurry on down don't miss out on this great chance to say
Save save save
Number 71
What is being sold
Number 72
How long does the sale last
Number 73
When does the sale end