Questions 74 through 76 refer to the following weather report
Good morning and welcome to another cold grade A
That's right folks it looks like yesterday's weather will be with us again today
Will have more freezing rain all day with a chance of snow later on this evening
This dreary weather will likely be with us for a few more days though the weekend forecast is looking up
The low-pressure system should be moving out of our area by late Friday
Then we can expect sunny skies all weekend with a high temperature of around 11 degrees Celsius
So don't despair
Better weather is just around the corner TuneIn again at noon for an updated report on today's weather
Number 74
What was the weather yesterday
Number 75
When might it snow
Number 76
What will the weekend temperature be