Questions 77 through 79 refer to the following news item
This urgent item just in
The electricity company warned citizens living in the tri-state region sejuta unusually high
Temperatures the demands for electricity mix seeds the supply
Air conditioners and fans are in constant use during this hot summer weather
Putting an enormous strain on electricity Supply
This increase in demand for electricity may result in power failures in scattered areas throughout the
Region
In order to help avoid blackouts citizens to keep the air conditioner set at temperature
Hello of an 80 degrees Fahrenheit
I'm surround them only intermittently during the hottest part of the day
In addition any non-essential use of electrical appliances should be avoided during the Middle
The day
If a power failure occurring in your neighborhood should cause a potentially life-threatening emergency
Call the electricity companies emergency hotline at 5559 74
Emergency workers are standing by in your area ready to respond when needed
Number 77
What kind of news item is this
Number 78
When might this announcement be heard
Number 79 what causes power failure