Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following recorded announcement
Thank you for calling Jetstream Airlines
Please excuse the short delay
Due to a special Logan phase olar agency busy assisting other colas
Okoles will be answered in turn
Please stay on the line and an airline representative will be with you shortly
Here's a tip for busy Travelers
When planning your trip don't forget to allow plenty of time to arrive at the airport
Improved airport security means long lines when passing through security control
Domestic Travelers should plan to arrive two hours before the scheduled departure time
While International Travelers should arrive 3 hours ahead of time
Number 80
Who is probably listening to this announcement
Number 81
Why is there a delay
Number 82
When should travelers to other countries get to the airport
Go on to the next page