Questions 83 through 85 refer to the following announcement
Good afternoon I want to welcome you all to our management Improvement luncheon
We have a delicious meal to look forward to
The catering staff here at the club always makes our noon events special
We also have a fantastic speaker with us today
Mr. Andrew margulis worked as a management trainer for 20 years before he retired
He is giving seminars all over the country and in several places abroad
Now he works only in his garden but I am pleased that he has honored Us by agreeing to be here today
He will share his experiences as a manager and lead us through some exercises designed to help us evaluate our
Effectiveness with our staff
And now without further Ado I give you Andrew margulis
Number 83
What kind of people are attending the seminar
Number 84
Which of the following describes mr. Mark Ellis
Number 85
Where is the announcement being heard