Perfect oval Junior practice test book 3
Practice test 1
The listening section has 42 questions for the long as you listen to the directions to the listening section
Directions in this section of the test you will hear talks and conversations each
Talk or conversation is followed by one question choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter
Letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet you will he reached awkward conversation only one time
Here is an example
Listen to a conversation between two friends in the classroom
You looked pleased about something did you get a good grade on your math test I don't know of
About that yet but I just found out that I made the baseball team
Why is the boy happy
No read the answer choices
The correct answer is a he was selected for the baseball team
Here is another example
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Jenny I think you need to try harder the paper you wrote wasn't very good
I'll try to improve my writing the next time
What are the speakers mainly talking about
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is B the quality of the girls work
Go on to the next page and the test will begin with question number one
Number one listened to a conversation between two friends
Are you going to attend the tutorial that Mr Sanders is giving during study hall
We only want to make sure I understand the material for the test he's going to give me further
His tests are really tough
That's exactly what I've heard is well I'm going to be sure to pay close attention during the Tudor
Mario
What are the speakers mainly discussing