Now you will hear longer talk or conversations
East awkward conversation will be followed by three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question then Mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between two students
Hey Greg
I see you just finished up soccer practice
Volleyball practice ended for me only a few minutes ago
That's great
How is the team looking this year
Do you think you'll have a winning record
Oh we definitely expect to do well
All of the starters from last year's Squad are returning and that team only lost three games all year
If you ask me I'd say we have a great shot at winning the state championship
That's awesome news
I hope the team meets expectations
So what about the soccer team
How do you guys expect to do
We are hoping to have a winning record
But
I don't know if I am going to be a part of the team this year
Huh
Tryouts are already over and you made the team coach Murphy isn't going to cut you now is he
After all you are a starter
No it's not that
It's just that I'm having trouble keeping my grades up right now
I'm taking to advanced placement classes
In math and history
And you know how much work they are
Since the team either practices or plays everyday
I'm losing a lot of valuable study time
You shouldn't quit though it's your senior year this is your last chance to be on the team
Teen
But what about my grades
We're in the same AP classes right
Why don't we get together after practice every day in study
I could invite a couple other members of the team to join our study group
Make it good grades so we could help each other
That just might work
What do you say to having our first meeting tomorrow
It sounds perfect
I'll talk to Jenny and Karen later tonight
Now answer the questions
Number 10 what are the students mainly talking about