Perfect topple jr. practice test book 1
Practice test 1
The listening section has 42 questions follow along as you listen to the directions to the
Listening section
Directions
In this section of the test you will hear talks and conversations each talk or conversation
Is followed by one question choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the car
Correct answer on your answer sheet you will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Here is an example
Listen to a conversation between two friends in the classroom
Aren't you going to band practice now it's our first meeting of the year
Banda pass this year
What does the girl mean
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is B she is not going to be a member of the band
Here is another example
Listen to a conversation between two friends at school
I can't wait for spring break to come I could really use some time off
Agree with you I'm looking forward to not having class for a week as well
What are the speakers talking about
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is C spring break
Go on to the next page and the test will begin with question number one
Number one listened to a conversation between two friends
Bill are you going to the soccer game this evening I wish I could but my parents
Want me to go home immediately after school are you in some kind of trouble
No it's not that today is my sister's birthday so we're going out to eat at our favorite rest
I'll have to take a pass on the game
What does the boy mean when he says I'll have to take a pass on the game