Now you will hear longer talks or conversations
Each talk or conversation will be followed by three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Miss Martin
Do you have a couple of minutes to speak with me
It's kind of important
Stuart David what's going on
I need to talk about the report that we're supposed to hand in tomorrow
Is it possible for me to get an extension on it
Why do you need an extension
Every other student in the class is going to turn his or her report in on time
Well I haven't had enough time to do the report
Coach grabs his kept a soccer team practicing late after school
Everyday this week
So by the time I get home I'm totally worn out
I just haven't had enough energy to write the paper
David I think you need to get your priorities straight
What do you mean
I mean that you're supposed to be focusing on learning at school athletics
Soccer team is of lesser importance but look I know how important soccer is to you
But your classes are more important so I'm going to have to reject your request you
You need to get that report to me by tomorrow
Yes ma'am
But I don't know how good it's going to be
Do your best
Why don't you go to the library now and start doing some research you've got an hour before you have to
To go to your next class
Use this time wisely you can start Gathering all of the information you need right now
Alright thanks
Now answer the questions
Number 10
What are the speakers mainly discussing