Parts for
Directions
You will hear some talks given by a single speaker
You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
On your answer sheet
The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time
Question 71 through 73 refer to the following excerpt from a meeting
Good morning everyone I have asked all the managers to come along today because I would like to go over the new budget for this
New Financial year I would like to congratulate everyone for not going over their budgets well done
We had a fantastic year last year with profits increasing by 20% compared to the previous year
This is enabling me to add one new staff member to the sales department and two new members to the development
I'm confident that by this time next year we will have some exciting Innovative products that will make
Are competitors envious
Number 71 what is the purpose of this talk
Number 72 what changes will the speaker be making at the company
Number 73 what does the speaker believe will happen over the coming year