Question 68 through 70 refer to the following conversation and facts
Were there any calls while I was at lunch yes your travel agent called he said there have been
Some changes to your reservation he said to ignore the fact that he sent this morning your flight is now at 8:30
Okay that's actually good because it gives me more time I won't need to leave the office as
Is early there is one more thing your seat number has changed that's worrying
I hope I still have an aisle seat I don't think you need to worry about that you've been upgraded to business
Glad
Number 68 where is this conversation taking place
Number 69
How does the men feel about his change seat number at first
Number 70
Look at the graphic how much later is the new flight time
Go on to the next page