Parts for
Directions
You will hear some talks given by a single speaker
You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
On your answer sheet
The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time
Question 71 through 73 refer to the following talk
Welcome to this evening so bend in some parts of the world people have to leave their countries due to
Dangers such as War they seek peace and protection in other countries these people
Are refugees the United Nations established an agency in 1950 to help refugees
It's Staffworks in difficult and sometimes dangerous conditions natural
Masters can also force people to flee their homes this is becoming more common as climate changes May
Making storms and floods worse refugees faced many challenges but we will continue to
To help them now and in the future I hope you will give generously to our fund
Number 71
What is the purpose of this talk
Number 72
What is the man talking about
Number 73
According to the man which is a reason why people become refugees