Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following announcement
Ladies and gentlemen the captain has turned on the fasten seatbelt sign please ensure all carry on love
Luggage is stowed underneath the seat in front of you over head compartment
Passengers seated next to an emergency exit should read the special instructions card by their seats if
If you feel unable to perform these functions in the case of an emergency please ask the flight attendant to reseat you
If you have any questions about our flight today please don't hesitate to ask one of our flight attendants
We will be serving drinks in about 30 minutes
Number 80 where is this announcement being made
Number 81
Which passengers should read special instructions
Number 82
What will happen after this announcement