Question 74 through 76 refer to the following announcement
Thank you for choosing kids can't I have a few words to say before you leave your child here for the neck
3 weeks
Your child will have an amazing summer doing a variety of creative and fun activities
Kids Camp is a caring and safe environment with carefully trained staff selected on the basis of their paw
How to experience skill enthusiasm
Spend a lot of time outside so I hope you had test sunscreen and bug spray for your kids
If not we can provide these items for a small fee okay let's get this show on the road
Number 74
Where is this announcement taking place
Number 75
What kind of people work at kids camp
Number 76
What does the woman mean when she says let's get this show on the road