Question 77 through 79 refer to the following excerpt from a lecture
I'll return your exams at the end of class so please be patient but first we're going to look at
Mojo's
Open two companies join to strengthen their position in the market orgy diversifying a changing economy
There are three main types of Mojo's horizontal vertical and concentric I'm going to talk about horror
Concentric messages today and save vertical merges for inex lecture horizontal merges
Is a cub between two companies that offer the same kinds of products or Services a concentric measure is win
Two businesses that all the different products or Services joined together
Number 77
Where most likely is the speaker
Number 78
Which is not a type of merger mentioned by the speaker
Number 79
What can be inferred about the speaker