Questions 83 through 85 refer to the following telephone message
Hi there my name is Eric swatski and I'm calling on behalf of driver seat Auto Insurance
Have you heard about our Premium Insurance Service called Smart Auto it offers auto insurance to
Careful drivers like you a special feature of the plan is claim forgiveness even if you have
An accident and file a claim with Smart Auto your insurance rates won't go up afterward receive a tree
Traffic ticket for a minor driving offense unlike at other insurance companies your rates won't go up
Even better if your insurance premiums get a price lock guarantee no rate increases
Ever give me a call or text to find out more at 9 30333 2226
Fix or email me at Eric at driversig.com
Number 83
What is the purpose of this message
Number 84
What is true about Smart Auto
Number 85
Which is not a means of contacting Eric
Go on to the next page