Question
You turn on the TV and hear this introduction
You are watching
Hey
A political interview
Be
A quiz show
See a travel program
And the next contestant is
Judea Milroy from 7th and sorry she's 32 years old and a secretary in a local company she's married
Jonathan has two lovely children and tonight Julia gets the chance to answer questions do not stop rice
And this week I'll surprise is a holiday for two in Hawaii
The next contestant is
Julia Milroy from 7th and sorry she's 32 years old and a secretary and a local company she's mad
Sorry to John and has two lovely children and tonight Julia gets the chance to answer questions do not stop rice
And this week I'll surprise the holiday 42 in Hawaii
Question 2
You overhear this telephone conversation
Someone is trying to buy
Hey
A railway ticket
Be
An airline ticket
See a bus ticket
How can I help you
Let me just know I'm sorry
BFF connecting bus service which ones every year just off the boat with a ticket to and I'll tell you what to do
I s class ticket to Bristol Parkway then that'll be 18 lb how would you like to pay
How can I help you
What is the railway station to let me just know I'm sorry the name is Stacy
BF4 the connection bus service which ones every I just fell Sepulchre the tickets and I'll tell you where to go
A second class ticket to Bristol Parkway then that'll be 18 lb how would you like to pay
Question three
My friend reads the report of a football match from the newspaper
The match Was Won by
Hey bonsly
Bea Oxford
See
A food
Size of relief could be heard among the shrieks of Triumph with a Ford made heavy weather of them Mexicans band
Bob Spitz Concours in the first round
Fonzie may be facing a battle against relegation from the Diadora League Premier Division but what they lack in the Billet
They more than made up for in competitive spirit and share hard work
They created a number of scans before I'm a first-class finally showed
After an even first half it was less than two minutes into the second half when Defender Richard Sherry needs as Nique
Conceited the corner
Kevin Keith headed in from the kick to take a foot into the next round
Size of relief could be heard among the shrieks of Triumph with Amplified made heavy weather of them match against Bond
Tom Cruise in the first round
Bonsly may be facing a battle against relegation from the Diadora League Premier Division in the village
They more than made up for in competitive spirit and share hard work
They created a number of scans before I'm a first-class finally showed
After an even faster if it was less than two minutes into the second half when Defender Richard Sherry needlessly
We conceded the corner
Kevin Keys headed in from the kick to take a foot into the next round
Question for
You are listening to a description of a procession on the radio
It is going to
Hey
The coronation
Be a funeral
See a wedding
The procession moves in front of us
Slowly
I'm so lonely
The only gone to my chest in front
With representatives of the three services
Canady first senior service
The army
Lost the most recent of the services
The Air Force
Images of behind them
A cortege
The crowd stand silent
With a heads bowed
Now the Queen's Carriage follows behind
The head of the line of mourners
How many different nations
That we can see the president of France
Splendid in his uniform
Next to him
The king of Norway
Samba in Black
With his pants in his hand
The procession moves in front of us
Slowly
I'm solemnly
The only gone to my chest in front
With representatives of the three services
Levi first who's the senior service
The army
Lost the most recent to the services
The Air Force
Immediately behind them comfortable days
The crowd stand silent
With their heads bowed
Now the Queen's Carriage follows behind
The head of the line of mourners
How many different nations
Advocacy the president of France
Splendid in his uniform
I'm next to him
The king of Norway
Samba in Black
With his top hat in his hand
Question 5
You hear the following on a News Bulletin
A couple
Author and Frederick amor
A Consulting lawyers about a
The wedding
Be
A wedding anniversary party
See
Ending their marriage
Arthur Moore and his wife Frederick admitted last night that I can sew
Go to two letters about that marriage the couple of be married for 25 years and up just celebrated their silver wedding anniversary
Me with a huge celebrity party leading Separate Lives
The statement added that the matrimonial Affairs were under discussion and requested the media to allow the couple to get on with their lives in
River City
The statement came to the 58 year-old dismissed media speculation on the reconciliation until the German paper is Deepak
Attachment for 39 year-old
Baltimore and his wife Frederick admitted last night that I cancel
Go to tell us about that marriage the couple of being married for 25 years and have just celebrated their silver wedding anniversary
With a huge celebrity party leading Separate Lives
The statement added that the matrimonial Affairs were under discussion and requested the media to allow the couple to get on with their lives in Brea
Privacy
The statement came to the 58 year-old actor dismissed media speculation on the reconciliation until the German paper is Deepak
Attachment for 39 year-old
Question 6
You hear an interview with Mary staffer who has just been given a film pot
She is
Impatient
Be happy
See
Nevus
Mary
You just been dying to play the leading female role of scarlet in the film sequel to Gone with the Wind
How do you feel about this
You must feel very excited but perhaps a little nervous too
It's your first major film role after all
Most of all I'm thrilled it's like Christmas and birthday and New Year's Eve all rolled into one
It's a huge challenge for me and you're right it's a big step but I'm not intimidated and I'm not
It's something I'm really looking forward to really can't wait to get started
Mary
You've just been dying to play the leading female role of scarlet in the film sequel to Gone with the Wind
How do you feel about it
You must feel very excited but perhaps a little nervous too
It's your first major film role after all
Most of all I'm thrilled it's like Christmas and birthday and New Year's Eve all rolled into one
If a huge challenge for me and if you're right it's a big step but I'm not intimidated and I'm not
It's something I'm really looking forward to really can't wait to get started
Question 7
You hear two men talkin about the car
The second man is
Hiring the car
Be
Buying the car
See borrowing the car
Ford Escort
Doing fine
No I need to see your lunch thanks
Okay that seems to be all in order
That'll be twenty-four pounds of divert this car for up to a week. Special course of course of course
What about insurance Maybe cover by Ron policy but we recommend that you take out the temperature without asking
It's only 10 lb extra fine
Just sign on the dotted line then please
Ford Escort
Doing fine no I need to see your license
Thanks
Okay that seems to be all in order
That'll be twenty-four pounds of divert this car for up to a week special course of course of course
What about insurance Maybe cover by Ron policy but we recommend that you take out the temperature in Gdansk
It's sunny sometimes extra fine
Just sign on the dotted line then please
What's June 8th
What is the relationship between the man and the woman
She is his secretary
Be
He is her business partner
See he is her boss
Joan great to see you again
Hello mr. Nice to see you too so don't call me Jim
Let me get you a drink please
Proposal to put you that I think you're going to like proposal gym
Yes you know what opening a new office in Frankford well Joan I'm asking you the head the whole operation will you do it
Ideal preparation so I have a free hummus but I mean Jim yet naturally Joan apprehend
Name your own salary
Joan great to see you again
Hello mister nice to see you too so don't call me Jim
Let me get you a drink
I think you're going to like proposal gym
Yes
You know opening a new office in Frankford well Joan I'm asking you to head the whole operation will you do it
So I have a free hummus but I mean Jim yet naturally Joan apprehend and you name your own salary