Questions 14 through 17
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Jeff you said that you wanted to talk to me about something
Do you have a moment to chat right now
Yes ma'am I think I've got a few moments before my next class
Great so what's going on is everything okay in class
Class is going great I think I understand most of the material we are learning
But that I have a question about our upcoming lab assignment
You're talking about the one where we dissect some animals right
Yes that's the one
You see I'm a little squeamish and I'm not quite sure how I'm going to react to Cuttin Up Anna
Do I have to do this assignment
First of all I wouldn't worry too much after all it's not like we're going to be dissecting
Dogs cats or any other cute animals
For our first lab assignment we're simply going to cut up a few worms
Wareham's that's it
That's it you don't have a problem with worms do you
No not at all in fact I use worms as bait everytime I go fishing
I don't think I'll have any problems with the lab in that case
That's great to hear but do me a favor
If you have a problem dissecting something else in the future just tell me I can excuse you if
If you really think you can't do it
About two or three students each year so it's not a big deal
That's good to know thanks for telling me that
Now answer the questions
Number 14
What is the main topic of the conversation