Questions 18 through 22
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Mr. Pressler Tommy just told me that you wanted to speak with me about something
He wasn't pulling my leg was he
No he wasn't I know Tommy is something of a joker but he was telling you the truth
I did ask him to find you for me
Well here I am
Indeed
Anyway it's about your science project you were supposed to submit the status report on it to me yesterday but
You never did that
What's going on
Oh its status report I totally forgot to email it to you I've been so busy
Busy with classes and other things that it slipped my mind
That's alright I understand
Well since you're here why don't you just give me the status report now if I remember
Correctly you were doing some sort of chemistry experiment in your father's laboratory at work right
That's right
How's it going
The lab work is pretty much all finished I got some interesting results
They weren't quite the results that I had predicted but they're still unique
Okay and how about the report you're going to write how's the progress on it going
Actually I haven't even started on it yet
I know there are only two more weeks until it's due so I'm going to get to work on it tomorrow
Is that alright
I suppose that's fine for now
But be sure to send me a status report next Monday I need to know how you're doing with that report
Sure I can handle that
Now answer the questions
Number 18
What is the main topic of the conversation