Questions 23 through 26
Listen to a conversation between two students
Etsy you don't look happy right now is something the matter
Yeah I got a big problem
I am completely overwhelmed by all of my work
I'm probably going to fail the history test we have this Thursday 2
I simply can't seem to remember any of the information for it
I'm sure that if you keep studying you'll do well on it
That's easy for you to say
You always get good grades in school
It's a lot harder for me though
You just need to try hard that's all I do
You must have a few tips that you can give me
Go ahead and fill me in
What should I do to improve my grades
Well why don't you tell me where you usually study
I pretty much study in my bedroom
I lie down on my bed and do most of my studying and homework there
Okay that's your first mistake
You should never lie down while you're studying
All that does is make you sleepy
It's hard of you to remember things if you're trying to keep from falling asleep
Instead sit at a desk
And you might want to play some soft music like
Classical music while you study
Classical music
Serious I always play rock music when I'm studying
That's another mistake
Why don't you turn the music off
And don't watch TV either
You need to focus solely on the material you're studying
Oh and one more thing
Don't log onto the internet while you're studying
You'll just get distracted
And you'll waste tons of time checking your email and your blog
Yeah that seems to happen to me a lot
Anyway thanks I'll try out your suggestions when I study later tonight
I hope they work
No answer the questions
Number 23 what is the girl mention her history test