Exam practice
You'll hear people talking and eight different situations
The questions 128
Choose the best answer
Boc
You hear a boy talking about a sporting event
What was the weather like
Hey
It rained heavily all afternoon
The sun came out between showers
See
It stays cloudy but dry
When we can't open the afternoon to play the match we have no idea where they would get to the end without getting wet we were crying for
Bad to take a break during the match if it rained but in fact we managed to get through the whole night without stopping
It looks as though it is going to rain after which finished but it didn't I certainly didn't need my sunglasses though we do is gray
Grace guys anyway I'm glad that much didn't get this phone because of the weather because we won
When we change open the afternoon to play the match we have no idea where they would get to the end without getting wet we work right repair
Had to take a break during the match if it rained in fact we managed to get through the whole night without stopping
It looked as though it was going to rain after which finished but it didn't I certainly didn't need my sunglasses though we do is Grace
These guys anyway I'm glad too much didn't get this phone because of the weather because we won
You had two friends talking about a science lesson they just hired
What do they do
Hey
It was a lot harder than they thought
It was less interesting than they'd hoped
See
It was much longer than they'd expected
Whew I'm glad I science lessons over for the day on U2 get to the break I'm real
Really hungry well that's because it was today that always goes on for over 2 hours doesn't it
Anesthesia Pulling Teeth though I'd really read Lots about volcanoes before I came so I was sure don't.
Go back to that I did I might ask my brother to help me
I really like seeing the multiple the teacher set up the DVD in the library
Whew I'm glad I science lessons over for the day on U2 get to the break I'm real
Well that's because it was a double lesson today that always goes on for over 2 hours doesn't it
Anesthesia Pulling Teeth though I'd really read Lots about volcanoes before I came so I was sure
No I do understand it will back up that I did I might ask my brother to help me
I really like seeing the multiple the teacher set up the DVD in the library
Much better though don't know about that
Tri
You have a girl leaving a voicemail message for her father
Marshy founding
Hey
2 Ranger lift home
To let him know her plans
To ask him to buy her something
My dad is Fiona have you finished work yet I'm going out with my friends in Town Lake
Thanks for the money for the concert by the way so I was wondering if you could do something for
Cookery at school tomorrow could you possibly stop on the way home and get some ingredients
Let me know what time you leaving okay
Sky dad
My dad and Fiona have you finished work yet I'm going out with my friends in town late
Thanks for the money for the concert by the way so I was wondering if you could do something for
Curious school tomorrow so you could you possibly stop on the way home and get some ingredients
I'll text you what time you leaving okay
Bye.
You hear two friends discussing an online Music Quiz they just completed
What did the girl think about it
Hey
Beyonce's it gave one to always correct
Be
The musicians is asked about what very well-known
See
Photos it showed what clear enough
Hi Karen
Did you get that Music Quiz I sent you about bands till I tried on string lights
Christian really
I thought they were pretty straightforward even the ones about photos of Ben's well maybe I just don't know what
Some bands look like and some of the other questions looks easy so I couldn't believe it when I go in and says wrong
Maybe lots of the band say was talking about her any familiar to Rio music fans not you I mean you go to
I didn't really do that may be alright
Oh well that's a lot next time
Hi Karen
Did you get that Music Quiz I sent you and I saw sign you loads about bonds till I tried on string lights
Is Christian really
I thought they were pretty straightforward even the ones about photos of Ben's well maybe I just don't know what
Some bands look like and some of the other questions looks easy so I couldn't believe it when I go in and says wrong
Maybe lots of the band say with talking about around you familiar to Rio music sounds like you I mean you go to
I didn't really do that may be alright
Oh well that's a lot next time
You had two friends talking about and you clothes shop in that town
What problem did the girl have that
It was too crowded for her to try anything on
Be
The clothes world too expensive
That was too little choice of colors and styles
What did you think of that new clothes shop in the city centre Amy
Well I was really Keen to go and have a look so I went last Saturday there's a huge variety
Styles that are in that stuff to sue everyone was having a favorite color
Yeah but the price tags looked a bit High to me
That's what you'll find in a city centre shops and it's worth paying a bit more for cool stuff
I might have to go again on a different day anyway everyone does that shopping on Saturdays so they just want
Changing rooms free let me know when I'll come too
What did you think of that new clothes shop in the city centre Amy
Well I was really Keen to go and have a look so I went last Saturday
There's a huge variety of styles that reason that stuff to sue everyone whatever that favorite color
The price tags looked a bit High to me
That's what you'll find in a city centre shops and it's worth paying a bit more for cool stuff
I might have to go again on a different day anyway everyone does their shopping on Saturdays so they just one
On any changing rooms free
Well let me know when I'll come too
You hear a boy talking to a friend about his recent somebody holiday
What made it so enjoyable
Hey
They stayed in a place that had lots to do
Be
He had a big room to himself
What if his friends went with them
How is your holiday turn okay we stayed in a cottage on the coast it was
Remotes notown from Miles because you love being in Thai
But we went for walks and things that was okay till the weather changed and we was
Stuck inside
Even more boring Swope my mom invited John to come I know him from my sports club
Sorry that meant we could play computer games all day
It was great having someone to do that with
There wasn't much space where I was sleeping but it didn't matter there was enough for my laptop
How is your holiday turn okay we stayed in a cottage on the coast it was
Remotes Motown from Miles because you love being
But we went for walks and things that was okay till the weather changed and we was
Stuck inside
Even more boring Swope my mom invited John to come I know him from my sports club
Sorry that meant we could play computer games all day
It was great having someone to do that with
There wasn't much space where I was sleeping but it didn't matter there was enough for my laptop
Yujiro voice owning his friend
What is the boy doing
Hey
Checking on homework requirements
Asking for information about a future lesson
See
Giving details of what his friends has missed
Hycarus it's Alex I'm just reading about school so you can't be that today hope you're feeling better
Anyway I just need to find out about what we were supposed to be doing for mr. Armstrong next week
I've written down that will be finishing a project in the lesson but I remember he also said we had to do some research at home before
Let me know what kind of exactly I don't want
Call me later okay
Hycarus it's Alex I'm just reading about school so you can't be that today hope you're feeling
Anyway I just need to find out about what we were supposed to be doing for mr. Armstrong next week
I've written down that will be finishing up project in the lesson but I remember he also said we had to do some research at home before
We went to let me know what kind of exactly I don't want to spend hours on the internet and find out it's wrong
Call me later okay
You hear go talkin about the first time she tried swimming underwater
How did she feel
Hey
Confident she could swim some distance
Be
Surprised at how strange it felt
See
Worried about losing her sense of direction
I can remember the time at my swimming club when the teacher wanted us to try swimming underwater
Atlantis win but I was Keen to give it to God
Emoji people in the group went fast they'd oversleeping doing it for ages I make it right across the Pooh
I really didn't think I'd manage that but if I went
How I'd imagined suddenly you just can't hear anyone anymore
But I just kept focused on the wall of the pool on the other side so I knew which way to go and I made
I can remember the time at my swimming club when the teacher wanted us to try swimming underwater
Attorney just learned to swim but I was Keen to give it to go
Emoji people in the group went fast they'd oversleeping doing it for ages I make a right across
Approved
I really didn't think I'd manage that but if I went
How I'd imagined suddenly you just can't hear anyone anymore
But I just kept focused on the wall of the pool on the other side so I knew which way to go and I made it