You are going to hear some talks given by one speaker
You are going to be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says and each time
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter A B C
Giordi
The talks are not printed in your test book
Flight 268 to Morocco will be taking off shortly
Since this is a short flight drinks will be served immediately after we reach cruising altitude
Also if you can show us a reservation number for any hotel in Morocco you'll drink soft
But those of you not staying that you have to pay for your beverages
Flight attendant Joella will be walking around the cabin with crayons and coloring books for any of you
You traveling with little ones
Lunch will be served 1 hour off to take off
Full first class passengers the menus are in the seat pocket in front of you
Other passengers your choice will be between vegetarian lasagna or fish
The movie today will be Jack and Laura's wedding
Thank you for choosing easy blue and enjoy your flight
Why would drinks be served right away
Why is a flight attendant offering coloring books
How do first-class passengers order lunch
Good morning everyone and what a beautiful morning it is
To die on the Santa Margarita boredom is definitely not on the itinerary
I know most of you are probably enjoying a delicious breakfast at the Barnacle Buffet but I
Just wanted to let you know what excitement await you after you finished
Starting at 10 a.m. the lovely Britney will be leading a water class
The south pool and a scavenger hunt for the whole family starts at 11
This afternoon we will dock at Saint mops for 3 hours so all of you can go shopping for
We'll just lie on the beach and taking the gorgeous views
Don't forget tonight is the 1950s Rock and Roll dance so bring your dancing shoes
Who is listening to this announcement
What is not an event happening today
For how long will the ship dock at st. marks
James I've asked you into my office for a very specific reason
Now it's nothing to be alarmed about so stop looking so worried
You have actually been chosen to participate in a conference being held in London next week
We've noticed how hard you work and we're amazed at how quickly you have picked up the skills needed for this
So as we at extra flowers like to reward those who deserve it we would like to pay
Pay for your entire trip to London
When you return with the certification in Arrangement you will receive at the conference you will be eligible
Cable for a promotion to head of the weddings Department
Unfortunately there is a promotion freeze until the new fiscal year so we cannot promote do you friend
Another five months
However you will definitely get the new position at that time
Who is speaking
How is James being rewarded for his hard work
When will James probably be promoted
This program is brought to you by the makers of sound around the new speaker system
Systems
This new system features the latest technology to bring you sound so true to life
Life that you won't realize you're listening to a recording
If you combine this speaker system with the new 3D TV every movie
TV watching experience will seem just like real life
If you want to experience walking on the moon simply pop in the new DVD release
Lease of moon trippers
If you purchase either the TV or the sound system before the end of the month
You will also receive a free copy of this fantastic new movie
Buy today
Where would this advertisement be seen
What products are not mentioned
What will the customer receive if purchasing before the end of the month
Hello
This is a message from cam last cable
We recently installed a new phone line and high-speed internet connection in your home at 786 North Monroe
We would like to thank you for choosing our company
And we want to let you know that your bill is due in two weeks
If for some reason you're not able to pay this bill in full
Please call our billing department
If you're experiencing any difficulties with these services
Do have any questions please call our customer service department
We hope that you enjoy the new phone line and internet connection
And please remember that if you add another service
Such as a cable TV package
All prices are reduced by an additional 5%
What services were recently bought
What should the customer do if there are internet problems
How are people encouraged to buy the cable package