Questions 23 through 26
Listen to a conversation between two students
I'm so relieved that we've only got one more class to go until the weekend
You're telling me it's been a long week
That's true
So do you have any plans for the weekend
Actually I do
I've got to go to my part-time job on both Saturday and Sunday
I didn't know you work part-time
When did you start doing that
I just landed the job 2 weeks ago
I work as a cashier at the supermarket down the street
You know danielson's
It's a decent job
I make about $8 an hour
And I only have to work on weekends
But I do a 5-hour shift every Saturday and an 8-hour shift every Sunday
Wow those are long shifts
Still it must be nice to make money
It is
My parents want me to start saving for college because they have no desire to pay for the entire cost of tuition
That's too bad for you but I understand them as well
As a matter of fact I think I'm going to have to find a part-time job myself
Find a job
But don't you already have one
You work at
One of those clothing stores in the mall don't you
I did but I quit before school began I wanted to focus on my studies this semester
How is that been going for you
Quite well I'm getting all A's at the moment
That's why I'm thinking of getting another job
There are only a few weeks left in the semester
So I don't think that working now will harm my grades too badly
You know
You might want to wait until the semester is over you feel awful if you bombed a final exam because
Cuz you couldn't study the night before it since you were working
I see what you mean
You may be right
That would be depressing what an ed
I guess I can wait a little while longer to start working again
Now answer the questions
Number 23
What does the boy mean when he says this
You're telling me