Questions 18 through 22
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Thanks for explaining that problem to me mrs. Peters
I think I understand the material a lot better now
It's my pleasure James I'm glad I could help you out
Anyway I guess I should leave I have PE class now
Oh James
Hold on a minute there's something I've been meaning to ask you
What's that
In the past three weeks or so you've started speaking up in class you were so quiet last year
And in the first month of the semester but now you are contributing a lot during class
Right
Well I'm curious what sparked this change
I guess I have more confidence now I mean
My grades have been improving in all of my classes this semester since I started studying everyday
So I guess I know more answers than I used to
Right
In the past I kept quiet because I
To be honest
I never knew the answers to any of the teachers questions
And I didn't really understand the material either
Now that I'm trying harder I find that I can answer the questions
So
I suppose I just want to show that I know the answers
Good for you James I must say that I and several of your other instructors and Varian
Impressed with how you've changed recently
Be sure to keep up the good work and talk as much as you want in my class I love it when students
Your answers
Thanks for the vote of confidence I was actually a little worried that you thought I was speaking
Too much
Not at all I wish I could get most of the other students to speak half as much as you in class
It would make for lively discussions
Now answer the questions
Number 18
What are the speakers mainly talking about