Questions 14 through 17
Listen to a conversation between two students
I'm really not looking forward to going on tomorrow field trip
It's going to be so boring
Why do you say that I think it will be fun to go to City Hall tomorrow
You've got to be kidding me
Not at all I mean
First of all we are going to get to meet
The mayor
And he's even going to talk to us for half an hour or so
So what
He's the mayor
He's the most important person in our city
Oh right I just remembered that you're interested in politics
I on the other hand couldn't care less about anything connected with politics
But I guess that explains why you're so eager to go on the field trip
Yeah exactly I know all about me a Robinson so I can't wait to hear him speak
In fact I heard that he's going to take questions from us
There are a couple of things I'm eager to ask him
Well I'm glad you're excited about this trip
As for me I much rather go on a field trip somewhere else
Like where
We went to the hospital last year I thought that was pretty cool we got to see a bunch of dog
Doctors in action
Getting to watch some of that I operation was so awesome
I didn't like that field trip at all
In fact I hate hospitals
I start to get sweaty and dizzy anytime I get near them
I think I'm allergic to doctors or something
Oh well I guess everyone has different tastes
Now answer the questions
Number 14
What are the students mainly discussing