Test free
This is the Cambridge English first four schools listening test
I'm going to give you the instructions for this test
I'll introduce each part of the test
I'll give you time to look at the questions
Are the stars of each piece you will hear this sound
You'll hear each piece twice
Remember why you listening write your answers on the question paper
You'll have five minutes at the end of the test to copia Lance's onto the separate answer sheet
It will now be opposed
Please ask any questions no because you must not speak during the test
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
Part 1
You'll hear people talking in eight different situations
The questions 128 choose the best answer a b or c
You hear a boy making a phone call
Why is he phoning
To ask for money
To explain why he's late
To tell someone where he is
Hi it's me I couldn't call you earlier sorry because I was in the cinema anyway
I'm fine and the film was great I just wanted to say I'm in the park next to the cinema with Jerry and the other
Is that okay
I'll come get the bus home because I haven't got any money
So you could pick me up in about an hour if you like you passed right by here on your way home from lunch on you
Thanks Dad see you then
Hi it's me I couldn't call you earlier sorry because I was in the cinema anyway on
I'm fine on the film was great I just wanted to say I'm in the park next to the cinema with Jerry and the others
Is that okay
I'll call and get the bus home because I haven't got any money
You could pick me up in about an hour if you like you passed right by here on your way home from work Tony
Thanks. See you then
You had two friends talking at school
How does the girl feel no
Tired
Be
Happy
See
Novice
Hi Joe how was your dance class thanks teacher is very strict so I felt a bit
Scared of having the first few lessons now everyone's used to her and you can tell she's going to teach his loads
I bet you're feeling exhausted now I want you to be worn out after my class
Now they with this new teacher I always come out feeling great and I can't stop smiling
Feeling tired and a bit miserable
Hi Joe how was your dance class thanks teacher is very strict so I thought the B
Scared of her for the first few lessons now everyone's used to her and you can tell she's going to teach us loads
I bet you're feeling exhausted that I want you to be in my class
Now they with this new teacher always come out feeling great and I can't stop smiling evening
Feeling tired and a bit miserable
Tri
You hear positive a music program on the radio
Where is the speaker
Hey
In a club
On a boat
See
At the beach
My folks about you but I'm having a fantastic time I love my job on days like this
And I haven't just been lazing around in the sun all day here on the deck of the southern belle at 2
Really cool bands you may already know them they've been playing in clubs all over the country this year and now
Signing along with clear blue water all around us and not a cloud in the sky they're going to play some summer
You'll soon be dancing on the beaches we'll start with a w
My folks about you but I'm having a fantastic time I love my job on days like
Best and I haven't just been lazing around in the sun all day here on the deck of the southern belle at 2
Really cool bombs you may already know them they've been playing in clubs all over the country this year
Sailing along with clear blue water all around us and not a cloud in the sky they're going to play some some
How much evens you'll soon be dancing on the beaches
You hear two friends talking about some shoes they see in a shop window
What do they agree about
The shoes are too expensive
The heels are too high
See
The color is to dog
I like these ones do you have
Yeah they're okay
Guppies episodes of color you like I thought you'd prefer something Liza
It's the shape I care about they look comfortable too I don't like very high
High heels hurt my feet
What the hell is all quite high so you think to bad I'm just not sure why.
Never want to pay this much for shoes well I didn't think they were that
I like these ones.
Yeah they're okay
Puppies episodes of color you like I thought you'd prefer something Liza I don't mind reading
Is the shape I care about comfortable to I don't like very high
I hate my feet
What the hell is all quite high so you think know they're not too bad I'm just not sure that
Never want to pay this much for shoes well I didn't think they were that
You hear it go talking to her little brother
Why is she annoyed with her brother
He forgot to buy milk
Be
He lost his keys
See
He didn't send her a message
Well I do think you could have remember the simple things like that I don't think it's that complicated really oh yeah
How to do is let me know you'd picked up the milk and orange juice on the way home and you did get the milk and orange juice tanks
Just a quick text would have been enough I know you had to go back to the shop and get your keys I'm glad they found them and kept them
For you that was nice but I still think you should have remembered
But I do think you could have remember this simple thing like that I don't think it's that complicated really
You have to do is let me know you'd picked up the milk and orange juice on the way home and you did get the milk and orange juice tanks
Just a quick text would have been enough I know you had to go back to the shop and get your keys I'm glad they found them and kept
For you that was nice but I still think you should have remembered
Shakes
You hear two friends talking about a day out
Where are they going
Hey
To take part in a sports event
To watch sports event
Do a sports museum
I've been looking forward to this for ages
I hope the weather's good great anyway when my brother win last year
Wanted these picture next to one of the players and he looked telling me my brother I mean
Sports museum we went to
And things he's always trying to copy them but I can't play at 2 but I not the matches on TV
I can't believe we're actually going to want me to
I've been looking forward to this for ages I hope the weather is good
Anyway when my brother went last year someone took his picture next to one of the players and he looked telling me
Does your brother play basketball
Museum we went to he shows you all the different moves and things he's always trying to copy them
But I know she's on TV leave or actually going to work
You hear a teacher talking to her class
What does she want them to do
Hey
Take some notes
Be
Write an essay
See
Prepare a presentation
Now listen carefully everyone because I'm going to explain what we're doing for the next couple of weeks
I've invited three different speakers to come and give presentations on topics connected with it
Environment there's no need to write anything down during the tools because the speakers will give you hand out
At the end
I'd like another topic also to do with an environmental issue
You'll be able to use information from essays evil ready written the internet
I hope you'll find this interesting and enjoy the challenge
Now listen carefully everyone because I'm going to explain what we're doing for the next couple of weeks
I've invited three different speakers to come and give presentations on topics connected with
Environment speakers will give you hand out
Another topic to do with an environmental issue
Issue you'll be able to use information from essays you've already written the internet.
I hope you'll find this interesting and enjoy the challenge
You hear a brother and sister talking in the kitchen at home
What are they doing
Hey
Eating of a pizza
Making some popcorn
See
Baking a cake
Just smell that way cool isn't it I think it will be great
Popcorn we made the pan to remember Mom made us promise never to make it home again
She didn't need to it was seriously bad
You just have to remember to get this Pizza Route 15 minutes in the oven then it's ready
It was a good idea
What you think we should have for dessert
I fancy some cake let's make one
Just smell that way cool isn't it I think it will be great
Better than that popcorn we made for me by the pan to remember Mom made us promise never to make it home again
She didn't need to it was seriously bad
Just have to remember to get this pizza route
Yeah 15 minutes in the oven then it's ready it was a good idea
What do you think we should have for dessert
I fancy some cake yeah let's make one
That's the end of part 1
No time to talk to