Question
You are watching this quiz show on TV
The contestant is answering questions on
Hey
History
Be
Current affairs
See
Geography
So here are the questions on the
Subject you chosen to win tonight's top prize
Take your time now
You have 10 seconds to think before you have to answer each question
Okay
Good
And here's your first question
Who was shot in Sarajevo in 1914 by Carrillo princip
Take your time now before you answer
So here are the questions on the
The subject you chosen to win tonight's top prize
Take your time now
You have 10 seconds to think before you have to answer each question
Okay
Good
And here's your first question
Who was shot in Sarajevo in 1914 by Carrillo princip
Take your time now before you answer
Question 2
You are thinking of going to watch a football match
But you are not sure what to wear
You found the weather line
Yeah this message
And decide to wear
A t-shirt and shorts
Be a raincoat
See a warm coat with gloves and scarf
Thank you for calling the Saturn telephone
Give me the weather forecast for today Tuesday the 21st of March
Today will be cutting avocado pit with only a 10% chance of rain when's will be like tomorrow at but it will
Freezing cold day with icy patches on the roads so take care of your driving
Spell Behati Brook tonight with temperatures as low as -5 degrees C
The long-range forecast is the snow to vote the end of the week
Thank you for calling the Saturn telephone
Give me the weather forecast for today Tuesday the 21st of March today will be cloudy and overcast but without any attempt
Winds will be light to moderate but it will be near freezing all day with icy patches on the road
So take care of you driving tonight with temperatures as low as -5 degrees
The long-range forecast is for snow to vote the end of the week
Question three
You hear this item on the radio news
The painting by Titian has Bean
Hey lost
Be stolen
See
Island
Rest on the flight to Egypt is probably the only small-scale Titian
Private homes
Painted in 15 10 and 15 1127 the founder of hibernate Sons painting in Venice with anesthetic twenties
Painting small signs my Would Have Made It attractive to thieves as a greasy be carried
Kitchen expert dr. Pol showman at Cambridge University said it is a lovely little thing a little gem and it is very sad that it
Has disappeared
Tell me a couple of other small pictures by teaching the known one in Bergamo Italy and one in the Metropolitan Museum in New
Rest on the flight to Egypt is probably the only small-scale
Fishing in private hands
Painted + 50 + 10 + 50 + 11 when fishing the founder of hibernate Sons painting in Venice was in his early twenties
Painting small inside my Would Have Made It attractive to thieves other could easily be carried
She's an expert Dr po7 at Cambridge University said it is a lovely little thing a little gem and it is very sad but it's
Has disappeared
Only a couple of other small pictures by tichenor known one in Bergamo Italy and one in the Metropolitan Museum in New
Question for
You're booked on flight ta20 412 New York
And y'all waiting in the departure Lounge at Heathrow Airport
When you hear this announcement
You go to
Hey
The exit
B Gates 20
Be
Hospitality suite B
Transatlantic Airlines
Regret to announce the cancellation of flight pa-204 12 San Francisco by Shannon New York and Chicago
I can just run into go immediately to the main exit a bus will take you to Gatwick wearing alternative light
Being arranged
Passengers to San Francisco have been transferred and her doing flight vt365 from date 21 days is called
Arrangements at fielding Mesa passengers for New York and Chicago if these passengers would like to go to hospitality
Sweet pea a complimentary Buffet has been arranged
Transatlantic Airlines
Regret to announce the cancellation of flight PA to a 4-12 San Francisco by Shannon New York and Chicago
Passengers brought in to go immediately to the main exit a bus will take you to get to acquire an alternative flight
Has been arranged
Passengers with San Francisco being confident you're doing flight vt365 from gate 21 days
Arrangements at fielding Mesa passengers the New York and Chicago if these passengers would like to go to hospitality suite
A complimentary Buffet has been arranged
Question 5
You hear these two people talking
Play on
Hey
Brother and sister
Be
Husband and wife
See friends
Let's go somewhere Rex Titan this year
You say that every year and every year we end up staying with your sister in Blackpool I know
But this year I want to do something different to Blackpool without your sister be sensible
I want to go do something exciting and get some soon
25 years ago
Now I see well it says our anniversary and the kids have said they'll pay for
Tickets As a treat
Let's go somewhere exciting this year
You say that every year
And every year we end up staying with your sister in Blackpool I know
But this year I want to do something different to Blackpool without your sister be sensible
I want to go abroad
To see something exciting and get some Stone
25 years ago
Now I see well
It is our anniversary and the kids have said they'll pay for all tickets As a treat
Question 6
This telephone call is overheard
It takes place in
Hey
A Santa booking office
Be
An airline booking office
See
A travel agency
I transfer
Yes
I'm sure we can transfer your ticket
What's the date of the performance
I'll just pull that up on the screen
Okay
Now what number is your seat
X3
Okay
Where would you like to move to IC
Somewhere near the front
How about T1
That's available
Don't worry about that
All seats have a good view
Now I've made the change shall I send you the new ticket
Would you like to pick it up
I transfer
Yes
I'm sure we can transfer your ticket
What's the date of the performance
The 24th
I'll just go back up on the screen
Okay
Now what numbers go seat 3
Where would you like to move to I see somewhere near the front
How about T1 that's available
Don't worry about that
All states have a good view
Now I've made the change shall I send you the new ticket or would you like to pick it up
Question 7
In this conversation Maria is asking George
Hey
To write her essay
Be
To read her essay
See
To help her with an essay
Yes
Avenue
So what do you want me to write it for you do you
Cuz you know I mean what's the point is to use
Yes
Avenue
So what do you want
Expect me to write it for you do you
What's the point is
We could start by telling me which books to use
What's your fate
You overhear this conversation when you are traveling on
Hey a plane
Be
Abbas
See a train
Excuse me sir I'm sorry
This compartment is non-smoking
Could you please put out your cigarette
I know and I'm sorry
But this is non-smoking as a signs on the Windows show quite clearly
The other passengers are complaining
Johnson just open the window I'm sorry sir if you want to smoke you must move to a smoking compartment
There's one in the next car is just after the buffet car
Excuse me sir I'm sorry
This compartment is non-smoking
Could you please put out your cigarette
I know and I'm sorry but this is Norm smoking as a science on the Wind
Show quite clearly
The other passengers are complaining
Gosh I just open the window I'm sorry sir if you want to smoke you must move to a smoking compartment
There's one in the next car is just after the buffet car