Questions 31 through 33 listen to a teacher talking in a history class
In the early 1800s Texas was a part of Mexico
However as many Americans began to move Westward
Lots of them migrated to Texas
After a few years they had established their own communities
These settlers had no desire to belong to Mexico
Instead
This ought to be independent
Understandably
The Mexicans objected to this
After all
Which country wants to lose land that it controls
Anyway in 1835 some fighting broke out between the American settlers
And Mexican soldiers
For the most part
The Americans won those battles
Then in early 1836
The Mexican sent a large army into Texas
At that time the Texans occupied and old Spanish church mission in San Antonio that was called the
The Alamo
The Mexican Army surrounded the Alamo and laid Siege to it on February 23rd 1836
The Mexicans had around 3,000 men and were led by Santa Anna
The Texans meanwhile only had about 250 men
They were led by Colonel William Travis the famous Frontiersman James Bowie and Davy Crockett
The Alamo as well
I'm sure you've heard of both men
The Siege lasted until March 6th on March 5th Santa Ana ordered his soldiers to move into position for an
All-out assault on the Alamo the next day
In the morning on the 6th the attack began
The Texans were good shots and killed a large number of Mexicans
Who were out in the open
But there were too many Mexican soldiers
The Mexicans breach the walls broke into the Alamo and killed all of them in there
It was a stunning defeat for the Texans
However they use this loss to inspire them to Victory Remember the Alamo became the battle
Cry of the Texans
They soon defeated Santa Anna's Army and even captured him
After that
Texas split apart from Mexico and became an independent nation
Now answer the questions
Number 31
What is the main topic of the teachers talk