Questions 34 through 37
Listen to a teacher talking in a biology class
Australia has lots of unusual mammals
Such as the kangaroo and the koala
We're going to get to them in a bit
But for a couple of minutes I'd like to tell you about another unique animal that lives there
It's called the dingo
The dingo is a predator that's similar to a dog
I guess you could say it's more like a wild dog
It's believed that the dingo migrated to Australia
From Southeast Asia thousands of years ago
Since there are wild dogs similar to the dingo in some parts of Southeast Asia
Anyway
The dingo lives mainly in the interior of Australia which is called the Outback
It has short fur that's reddish brown in color
Its Underside is more whitish in color
The dingo has short pointed ears and a long-tailed as for its size
It averages around 30 kg in weight
You can live for up to 20 years
As I already mentioned
The dingo is a predator in fact
It's Australia's largest Predator that lives solely on land
The dingo typically eat small mammals like a
Like rabbits and rats
It also eats birds and reptiles particularly lizards
The dingo has been known to attack livestock
Mainly sheep and Cattle
There's an ongoing battle in Australia between farmers
Who want to kill the dingoes that attacked their livestock
And people who want to keep them alive
Dingos occasionally attack humans
And have in a few rare cases
Killed small children
The dingo is a social animal
That typically travels in packs of up to 10
In that way I suppose it's like the wolf
Another animal related to the dog
Female dingoes breed once a year
And give birth to up to five pups at a time
The pups usually stay with their mother for up to eight months
Now let me tell you a little about how dingoes communicate with each other I think this is pretty
Now answer the questions
Number 34
What is the purpose of the lecture