Questions 27 through 30
Listen to part of a discussion in a science class
Can anyone tell me what a current is
Alice do you know
I think it's like when the water in the ocean moves like a river
I mean the current seems to move differently than the water around it
That's not a bad definition of a current Alice thank you
Oceans and seas have currents
Like Alice said they're like rivers that move in larger bodies of water
There are both warm water and cold water currents
There are currents all around the world
Some even have names
Do any of you happen to know the name of one
Read your hand is up
The Gulf Stream is a current
I know that because it blows right by our city
In fact
My dad and I take our boat out to fish in the Gulf Stream
When we have the time
Well done Fred that was the answer I was looking for
I'm sure most of you have heard of the Gulf Stream
But you might not know what exactly it is
So let me give you a few facts about it
The Gulf Stream is one of the world's largest and longest ocean currents
Look at the map here
It extends from the Gulf of Mexico and passes Florida and the eastern coast of North America
America as it heads northward
It crosses the Atlantic Ocean and goes to Europe
There it divides into two main streams
1 Head South toward Africa
The other moves North past England and Western Europe
And then goes north to Norway
As for the Gulfstream itself it's about 100 kilometers wide
It moves at a rate of 2 1/2 m per second
It made me move Eastward and northward because of the wind conditions where it originates
The win you see helps move the water
The Gulf Stream starts with very warm water
But as the wind pushes it the water starts cooling off
By the time the water reaches Europe it's much warmer
Not sorry I mean cooler
It's much cooler than it was when it left the Gulf of Mexico
Alice
I heard that the Gulf Stream affect the climates of different places
Is that true
It sure is
And that's what I want to tell you about now
Now answer the questions
Number 27
What is the subject of the discussion