Exam practice
You hear people talking and ain't different situations
The questions 128
Choose the best answer
Boc
You hear someone introducing a school show that is about to start
Who is getting the introduction
Students
A teacher
Apparent
Welcome everyone to annual performance
And we hope you'll find it as enjoyable as always
Elusive hard work's been going on behind the scenes by both staff and students
Parents have put in a thank you to everyone who helped
About ready to start so prepared to see Olaf favorite teachers
In some very unusual Road in fact some of us didn't actually recognize them
And I should also mention that we have completed our homework for this evening for any worried
Parents in the audience
So let's get on with the show
Welcome everyone to annual performance and we hope you'll find it doesn't
Enjoyable as always
Elusive hard work's been going on behind the scenes by both staff and students
Parents have put in a lot of hours to thank you to everyone who helped
About ready to start so prepared to see Olaf favorite teachers in
Some very unusual Road
In fact some of us didn't actually recognize them
And I should also mention that we have completed our homework for this evening for any worry
Parents in the audience so let's get on with the show
You hear two students talkin about a trip they are going on tomorrow
Where are they going
To City
To a forest
See
To the coast
He's ready for the Youth Club trip tomorrow Holly
Don't forget to wear something warm
If it's anything like lost it it'll be freezing yeah I remember all that walking
Kill the snake lovely covering over trees
This time the wind can be really cold when it comes off the sea
Maybe a trip to the city museum would have been a better idea especially at this time of year
But then I wouldn't get such great photos as I'm hoping to take tomorrow
Easy for the Youth Club trip tomorrow Holly
Don't forget to wear something warm
If it's anything like lost it it'll be freezing yeah I remember all that walking
Lovely covering over trees
This time the wind can be really cold when it comes off the CO2 shelter
Maybe a trip to the city museum would have been a better idea especially at this time of year
But then I wouldn't get such great photos I'm hoping to take tomorrow
You here ago phoning Hutto the cousin
Munchie phoning
Hey
To tell him some good news
Be
To ask him a favor
See
To complain about something
Hi jacket Fiona
I know you had the results of the writing competition that I wanted as you know I wasn't really expecting to win
Said the results wasn't a great surprise but I guess I was still a tiny bit disappointed anyway I know you
Already good at writing
So I sent you my piece to have a look at it would be great if you could send me some hints on how I could improve Irani
He wants to be a journalist like you when I'm older I'll probably never be as good but you never know
Hi jacket Fiona
I know you've had the results of the writing competition that I wanted as you know I wasn't really expecting to win
The result wasn't a great surprise but I guess I was still a tiny bit disappointed anyway I know you
You're really good at writing so I sent you my peace to having a cat
It would be great if you could send me some hints on how I could improve I really want to be a journalist like you when I'm older
I will probably never be as good but you never know
You hear Ramon presenting a radio program about support Bond
Where is he now
In recording studio
Be
In a hotel
See
Awesome music festival
Evening everyone tonight I'll be talkin to pop sensation Merrick about that latest album they've just
Finished recording in that studio so look out for that when it's released it's going to be a massive hit
I'd arranged to interview them here straight after they've come offstage before they leave for that hotel in the Centre of town
They've definitely been the highlight of the evening the crowds have been even bigger this yet with counter
First numbers of tents out on the field surrounding the main stage so they should be pleased
Evening everyone tonight I'll be talkin to pop sensation Merrick about that latest album they've just
Finished recording studio released it's going to be a massive hit
I've arranged to interview them here straight after they've come offstage before they leave for that hotel in the central
They've definitely been the highlight of the evening
The crowds of an even bigger this year with countless numbers of tents out on the field surrounding the mainstay
So they should be pleased if I come now
You hear ago talking to a friend about her painting that is being in an exhibition
How does she feel about her painting
Hey
Annoyed about mistakes she made
Be
Believe the people were positive about it
Disappointed at the reaction it.
Hi Maggie I saw your painting in the end-of-year school I'll text admission all the parents went to it was fantastic
Well my art teacher wanted to make sure it was displayed as she seemed really pleased with it but I'm not sure
What the parents tools don't worry I only had them saying good things about it
Did I miss out B and haven't use the right colors but don't think anyone noticed
It was too late to do anything about it unfortunately
I will next time I'll do something Becca hopefully
Hi Maggie I saw your painting in the end-of-year school out exhibition all the parents went to it was fantastic
Well my art teacher wanted to make sure it was displayed as she seemed really pleased with it but I'm not
The parent stores don't worry I only heard them saying good things about it
That I missed out bits and haven't use the right colors but don't think anyone noticed
I did but it was too late to do anything about it unfortunately I will next time I'll do something
You had two friends talking about stuffing as a resort
What do they agree about
The waves that aren't very big
There are too many people
See
There aren't enough competitions
So have you had a good day surfing great thanks I never imagined the weather would be so warm here
Well that's what makes the place so crowded during the season but that's one aspect of it icon stands to be
Be honest at least that means related to Staffing competition so it really pushes you to improve your own stuff
Very thing is I guess the Seas a bit flat compared with some of the big stuff and capitals around the world
Have you had a good day surfing great thanks I never imagined the weather would be so warm
Well that's what makes the place so crowded
To be honest I need that means a larger Staffing competition so it really pushes you to improve your eyesight
Laughing moose
Anything is against the season B flat compared with some of the big stuff and capitals around the world
Unlikely to go to any of those though so we'll have to make do with this place
You hear a boy talking about the football match that his favorite team played in
What is his opinion of the way they played
I was lucky to win the match
Be
They missed a lot of chances to school
See
They were better than the other team
Well it was still a pretty exciting match as the result could have gone either way
And it was hard to predict what would happen
I mean the team I support been playing brilliantly up to now so I don't know what went wrong tonight
It's hard to say who was Stronger them or their opponents but in the end the better team one I think
My team could have got more girls but they just didn't take the opportunities
So they deserve to lose Raley
Nevermind we'll see how they do in the next game
Well it was still a pretty exciting match as the result could have gone either way and it was hard to predict what would
I mean the team I support been playing brilliantly up to now so I don't know what went wrong tonight
It's hard to say who was Stronger them or their opponents
But in the end patatine one I think
My team could have got more goals but I just didn't take the opportunities
But he deserved to lose Raley
Nevermind we'll see how they do in the next game
You hear it go talking to her friend about a TV program they both soul
What was she surprised about
It featured someone they both knew
It included a topic they've both been studying
T
It was filmed close to where they both live
Yeah
Did you see that science program on TV last night I did it yeah interesting wasn't it
Exactly the same thing we've been talking about on the phone I couldn't see it fast where is have been made though
It must be somewhere in another country but then I recognized the beach in the background is there anybody
10 km from Avalanche
Hey you right
I didn't recognize any of the people in it
Me too
Your eyes
Yeah
Did you see that song on TV last night
I did yeah interesting wasn't it it was about exactly the same thing we've been talking about
I can't see it fast where is have been made though I thought it must be somewhere in another country but then I
Nice the beach in the background it's only about 10 km h
I didn't recognize any of the people in it
TV Crews that have definitely gone to the beach that day