You are going to hear some talks given by one speaker
You are going to be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says and each time
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter A B C
Giordi
Good afternoon ladies and gentlemen and welcome to the Opening Ceremonies for the brand
New technology Library
We are pleased to have you all here today to witness this historic event
In just a moment you can walk through the twelve rooms that are open to the public today
Featuring writings from the very beginning of what we might Now call technology
You cannot only read about the various inventions and theories but you can also
Lucy actual reproductions of such objects as the first printing press
And the very first robot
Of course we would have loved to show you what the first computers looks like but they were
Wouldn't fit in any of our rooms these reproductions are only
Exhibited for our opening week and they'll then be returned to the museum
Self Oaks take your time to wander around reading and playing with exhibit
And do let us know if you have any questions
What is the purpose of this talk
What is not shown at this Library
What will the audience do after the talk is finished
We are so sorry for the inconvenience everybody but due to technical difficulty
Train number 6550 to Miami will be delayed for 1 hour
I know this may cause some problems for some of you but there is really nothing we can do
As we must wait for a replacement part to be delivered
To apologize for any difficulty the delay has caused we would like to offer all of
Of the passengers on this train free lunch
Meal vouchers for The Station Restaurant will be brought to everyone shortly so please
Stay in your seats until you get the vouchers
Thank you for your time and again we sincerely apologize
When will the train leave
What will passengers receive now
Who is listening to this announcement
Question 77 to 79 refer to the following message
Thank you for calling Ricky's Salon and Spa services
Due to the public holidays Ricky's will be closed from Friday to Monday
So during this time Alice stuff is taking a much-needed vacation
Bethel we were gretz that we are not able to take any appointments on the 4th Thru the 7th
However to make it up to our wonderful clients we have a deal for you
By any service before March 17th and you can receive a second service for half
Price
If you would like to make an appointment please leave your name number
The time and date you want to come in and which service you would like
Happy holidays
Why is Ricky's Salon closed
When will they open again
What should people not leave in their message
Attention everyone pair of pink and black gloves has been found on a table
In the food court
In front of the sandwich shop
There was also a wallet with the pink gloves
These items have been taken to the information booth at the north entrance which is
Is located between Macy's department store and the sunglasses Shack
If you believe these items belong to you please come in person to the information
Please bring proof of identity that matches the name and address in the wallet
The wallet will not be given to anyone who cannot prove that it belongs to them
Thank you and have a good day
Where is this announcement taking place
Where were the items found
How can the owner get the items back
I suppose many of you
A wondering why I called you all in here today
Well
I have some bad news.
I guess some of you might see it as good news
As of today
I am no longer your manager
I have been offered a new position in our Beijing office
Which I have accepted and I am actually moving there tomorrow
I know it seems sudden
But I'm just terrible at goodbyes and I wanted to avoid any long farewell
I have loved working with all of you these past three years
And I hope the feeling is mutual
I would also like to introduce you to my replacement a woman who has been with the company
Almost as long as I have
And we really deserve this promotion
Patty Park
Please come up here
And say hello to your new stuff
When is she moving
Why did she wait to make this announcement
What is the purpose of this announcement