Question 1
Listen to this news item
If the workers don't get what they want
That will be a
More warnings
Be
More inflation
Strike
Sadie's on pool yesterday when I like
Striking the gym and Engineering industry food truck to a standstill some 24,000
Dispute over pay idea metal which is the country's largest Union wound employees
Strike with one and only and would be followed by others at a better pay offer was not made the union is claiming arrived
Kubota 6% which is nearly triple the rate of inflation in Germany
Data's on pools
Striking the gym and Engineering industry food truck to a standstill, 24,000 workers down
Dispute over pay idea metal which is the country's largest Union
Strike was wanting only and would be followed by others at a better pay offer was not made to Union is claiming arrival
Play the 6% which is mainly trouble the rate of inflation in Germany
Question 2
Listen to this telephone conversation
The man is talking to
A a farmer
Be his employer
See the police
Joe
Joe is that you
No. I haven't got time to talk
I'm only in the farmers for S listen I just been up to the top fields in about 57 Lambda meeting
Roblox mm2
Well I was going to ask you to spend any of money on your land but it must be Rustler
No I didn't hear anything last night either
Uncle the placement of the rhyme to see you
Joe
Joe is that you
No. I haven't got time to talk
I'm only in the five miles per second I've just been up for the top fields in about 57 Lambda meeting
Listen to
Well I was going to ask you to spend any of mine and your land but it must be Rustler
No I didn't hear anything last night either
Uncle the place middle beer I'm just a game
Question three
Listen to this conversation
Mary wants to go to
A listing tomorrow
Be the theater
Neither Fanta
Mary let's go out tonight
We could go to the cinema
Sleepless in Seattle at the Odeon
The Lion King
The ground has a consonant
It's a long time to that fast
Mary let's go out tonight
We could go to the cinema
Sleepless in Seattle at the Odeon
The Lion King
The ground has a pencil in them
Question for
Listen to this announcement in a department store
You want to buy a pair of shoes
You could go to a the third floor
Be the ground floor
See the second law
Give me the date
Doesn't this week special offers at Dental Department still
On the second floor on during shipment search for me today advantages by 10% employees for the summer series
In the foot wedge apartments on the third floor Gucci loafers and Monsoon drives around offer
15% reduction
Probably on the ground floor or third hole is penalizing products from France this way and the respect
Bonkers on a large selection of wines and cheeses
Butalbital
This week's special offers at bento's Department still
On the second floor on you Ryan schuchman suspended today I've been BJ's Bar 10% employees for the timer
In the foot wide apartments on the third floor Gucci loafers and Moonstone Drive around
Corporate 15% reduction
Laundry on the ground floor all food whole is promoting products from France this way and the respect
Selection of wines and cheeses
Question 5
Listen to this conversation between two business colleagues
John Jameson
Michael Jones
Who is senior
Hey
John Jameson
Be
Michael Jones
Equal
Michael, will you please
I noticed the figures have been going down why turn down
Let me make things clear to you Michael
Rockledge or responsibilities other than you go to
Michael come in here a moment when you plant it's about the Rockwell account
I guess I noticed the figures have been going down why
Let me make things clear to you Michael Ruckel is your responsibility
Tobago than you go to
What's insects
Listen to this extract from a TV program
The program is
Hey the news
Be a documentary
See a political broadcast
This is why we in the government established the correct basis for financing
Public spending on the Health Service education and Social Security
The conservative party has a policy
The other parties say they want to expand and improve but they haven't got the owner
Brother money come from
Labor I don't mention plans you don't
Let's talk about Penny on income tax but let me tell you
And this is why we in the government to establish the correct basis for finance
Public spending on the Health Service education and Authority
The conservative party has a policy
The other parties say they want to expand and improve these areas
But they have to say where the money will come from the paper this
Babe I didn't mention plans
Liberals talk about Penny on income tax but let me tell you what begin to cover the cost of that
Question 7
Listen to this telephone conversation
Beka finally agrees to
Hey
Refilled
Give back the money
BECU difference tickets
No I'm sorry we kind of threw from the money after the ticket has been paid for you did booking price of these tickets sometime ago
I think you'll find it says in the back of the ticket the money will be refunded only in the event of a council 24
But listen
We can try to resell the tickets for you oh well that's easier if you want to exchange the tickets
Another concert in the music in the city series we can do that
What does Alexa know the most
Yet
They'll be small Administration
No I'm sorry we kind of Truth on the money after the ticket to some high school you did look in Pisces ticket sometime ago
I think you'll find it says in the back of the ticket the money will be refunded only in the event of a council Tacoma
But we can try to resell the tickets for you oh well that's easier
If you want to exchange the tickets another concert in the music in the city series we can do that
What did he say now
What's the date
Listen to this man talking about his holiday
He travels
On foot
Be by bike
By car
And really glorious weather
Of course we were at the beginning but it's surprising that quickly that wears off
It's a much slower Pace holiday then we used to it was good
We're able to take more time to look at the views or to stop at the pub for lunch and of course we were acting depressed at all the time
Even the punch was Maya had was just a good excuse for stopping and enjoying the scenery while we mended it
And really glorious weather
Of course we were at the beginning but it's surprising how quickly that wears off
It's a much slower Pace holiday than we used to that was good
We're able to take more time to look at the view door to stop at the pub for lunch and of course we were asking the pressure at all the time
Even the punch was Maya had was just a good excuse for stopping and enjoying the scenery while we mended it