Test2
Part 1
You hear people talking in eight different situations
Two questions 128 choose the best answer a
B o c
You hear part of an interview with a sportsman
What did he say about playing for the national team
Hey
He doesn't think it will happen soon
Be
It isn't his main concern at the moment
See
The possibility of it happening has put him under pressure
This Bean tool cuz you being picked for the national team again
Is it hard for you to put that to the back of your mind during games when you know that the national coach could be watching
Playing fuel country is as big as it gets
And it'd be great to do that again
But at the same time you have to worry about the jump on the day and that's playing fuel Club
I've learned over the years that your focus should be on the game you're playing in and nothing else
Dishman tool cuz you being picked for the national team again
Is it hard for you to put that to the back of your mind during games when you know that the national coach could be watching
Playing fuel country is as big as it gets
And it'd be great to do that again
But at the same time you have to worry about the job on the day and that's playing fuel Club
I've learned over the years that your focus should be on the game you're playing in and nothing else
You hear the introduction to a radio program
What is the speaker doing
A
Contrasting weather forecasting in the past and the present
Be
Explaining why weather forecasting has become more accurate
See
Joking about how people used to forecast the weather
Now what can you do if you want to know what the weather is going to be like
He probably turn on the television or look on the internet
Meteorology is a relatively recent science and not so long ago people it's
Especially Farmers had to rely on their own knowledge of the seasons
I know season was more important than spring
Many different Rhymes and sayings for used for predicting the weather I need two months had its own sayings
Now what do you do if you want to know what the weather is going to be like
He probably turn on the television or look on the internet
But meteorology is a relatively recent science I'm not so long ago people it's
City Farmers have to rely on their own knowledge of the seasons
I know season was more important than spring
Many different Rhymes and sayings for used for predicting the weather I need two months had its own sayings
You hear a man talking about reading aloud to children
What opinion does he Express
Short stories are better than longer books
Be
The choice of book may not be important
See
It's hard to know what will make children laugh
It doesn't really matter what you read to kids they appreciate everything I've been reading a book about
History to my seven-year-old
He doesn't understand a word of it but insists on having it every night
Having said that it does make a huge difference if you can find a book that you won't enjoy together
My favorite is a series of short stories about a mad inventor who creates ridiculous machines
It's great to be able to read something that genuinely makes your children love
It doesn't really matter what you read to kids they appreciate everything I've been reading a book about
History to my seven-year-old
He doesn't understand a word of it but insists on having it every night
Having said that it does make a huge difference if you can find a book that you won't enjoy together
My favorite is a series of short stories about a mad inventor who creates ridiculous machines
It's great to be able to read something that genuinely makes your children love
Fool
You hear someone talking about work
What is the situation
A
He has just left the job
He's thinking of leaving his job
He has just started a new job
Soon as I said
After all the months of worrying about it and discussing it with other people I finally done it
To be honest I'm not sure how I feel
Bojangles about the future sure because I really don't know how things are going to go
But I simply had to get out
Chicago I'm putting up with a sort of things I had to put up with
How to count help thinking that it shouldn't have come to this
But it did and I've dealt with it and it's time now to start looking ahead
Soon as I said
After all the months of worrying about it and discussing it with other people I finally done it
To be honest I'm not sure how I feel
A bit anxious about the future sure because I really don't know how things are going to go
But I simply had to get out
Chicago I'm putting up with a soda things I had to put up with
How to count help thinking that it shouldn't have come to this
But it did and I've dealt with it and it's time now to start looking ahead
You hear someone talking about his childhood
What does he mention
A habit of gods is strange
Regrets about some of his behavior
See
How much he has changed
When I was a kid I was always jumping out windows and things and climbing trees
I had numerous injuries something glider
Also I went through a phase of wearing all my clothes back to front
Even to this day I thought I wanted it
Casually still do I put my clothes on back to front
I'm just sitting there on my own because it reminds me of when I was a kid
When I was a kid I was always jumping out windows and things and climbing trees
I had numerous injuries something glider
Also I went through a phase of wearing all my clothes back to front
Even to this day I thought I wanted it
Occasionally still do I put my clothes on back to front
I'm just sit there on my own
Was it reminds me of when I was a kid
You hear someone talking about something that happened to the party
How did the speaker feel
Hey
Upset
Be
Amused
See
Frightened
Yes it was completely unexpected I had no idea he felt so strongly about it
I mean as far as I'm concerned I just made an innocent comment and he suddenly went mad
He was shouting at me I'm pointing his finger at one point he might even get violent
How silly
He just succeeded in making a complete fool of himself
Everyone else was looking terribly worried but I thought it was all highly entertaining
Some of those insults at me
Ridiculous
I expect he'll apologize eventually but I really don't care
Yes it was completely unexpected I have no idea he felt so strongly about it
I mean as far as I'm concerned I just made an innocent comment and he suddenly went mad
He was shouting at me I'm pointing his finger and I thought at one point he might even get violent
How silly
He just succeeded in making a complete fool of himself
Everyone else was looking terribly worried but I thought it was all highly entertaining
Some of those insults so ridiculous
I expect he'll apologize eventually but I really don't care
You hear part of it talk about blues music
What is the speaker talking about
Why is originated in a certain area
Be
How popular it was in the past compared with today
See
It's important in the history of popular music
Of course without Blues you simply wouldn't have any of the various forms of popular music that
Swept the world over the past few decades rock and roll Soul right hip
Do you know their existence to the style of music that was created in a small part of the deep
Deep south of the US
The Mississippi Delta
The musicians who develop the Style 10 more less totally unknown
Side the road area although fortunately they made plenty of recordings that is still available
Today if you want to find out more
And you should if you want to find out where a lot of today's music came from
Of course without Blues you simply wouldn't have any of the various forms of popular music that have
Swept the world over the past few decades
Rock and roll soul rap hip-hop they all know their existence the style of
Music that was created in a small part of the deep south of the US the Mississippi Delta
The musicians who develop the Style 10 more less totally unknown
Outside their own area
Although fortunately they made plenty of recordings that is still available today if you want to find out
And you should if you want to find out where a lot of today's music came from
You hear someone on the radio talking about a website for consumers
What is the speaker's purpose
To encourage consumers to make complaints
Be
To inform consumers about a source of information
See
To describe common problems for consumers
This is the first place to go if you need information about your rights as a consumer
It has tips on dealing with dodgy Wegman faulty Goods shopping safely online and avoiding sky
It's relatively easy to navigate your way around it has a useful links section and
Will help you get in touch with telephone advisors
It will not however take off individual cases
This is the first place to go if you need information about your rights as a consumer
He has tips on dealing with dodgy Wegman faulty Goods shopping safely online and avoiding sky
It's relatively easy to navigate your way around it has a useful links section and will help you get in touch
With telephone advisors
It will not however take off individual cases