Test 5
This is the Cambridge English first four schools listening test
I'm going to give you the instructions for this test
I'll introduce each part of the test
I'll give you time to look at the questions
Are the stars of each piece you will hear this sound
You'll hear each piece twice
Remember why you listening write your answers on the question paper
You'll have five minutes at the end of the test to copia Lance's onto the separate answer sheet
It will now be opposed
Please ask any questions now because you must not speak during the test
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
Part 1
You'll hear people talking in eight different situations
The questions 128 choose the best answer a b or c
You want to hear two friends talking about it TV play
What did the girl think about the play
Hey
The actors were better than she thought they'd be
Be
The story had an unexpected ending
The costumes were very attractive
What did you think about that play on TV last night I liked it I wasn't sure
About the main actor I expected him to be better I usually like him a lot
I don't think the role was the best one for him I know what you mean but the plot was quite good I thought it had
Had a great twist at the end I guess what would happen halfway through I love the clothes though
I wish we were things like that the actors all look so elegant you think so I can't see
Say that particularly struck me
What did you think about that play on TV last night I liked it I wasn't sure
Sure about the main actor I expected him to be better I usually like him a lot I don't think the
Roll with the best one for him I know what you mean but the plot was quite good I thought it had a great twist
At the end I guess what would happen halfway through I love the clothes though
I wish we were things like that the actors all look so elegant you think so I can't say that for
Distract me
You hear two friends talking about a new bicycle
What is the boys opinion of it
Hey
It is too expensive
Be
It has a strange appearance
It is a little uncomfortable to ride
Louis has gotten a bike have you seen it
I know but it's worth it it's a top-of-the-range model and it goes really well with saddle
Alexis if it might be a bit small and hard day is fine I know I try to count it feels really
And the kids are great
I'm not sure about the color will the shape of the handlebars though they're bit weird
You want to bike to look a bit different I think
Anyway as long as Maria likes it she's thrilled to bits
Funny bike have you seen it around gave it to her
I know but it's worth it it's a top-of-the-range model and it goes really well
Looks as if it might be a bit small and hard though is fine I know I tried it out it feels real
Really good and the kids are great I'm not sure about the color will the shape of the handlebars though
Weird look a bit different I think
Anyway as long as Maria likes it she's thrilled to bits
Tri
You hear a teacher talking to a class
What is he telling them about
A new after-school activity
Be
Aramark assignment
A change to bedtime table
I've got something important I want to tell you so can you please pay attention the schools considering making
Some changes next year we're wearing out the possibility of introducing some weekend activities here
Special Sports training pants or drama or music but before we make any definite decisions we want to get your eye
Friday is what would appeal to you would you actually take advantage of these activities so head monster
Would like you all to write a paragraph this evening if you want saying what you think I need to take it in.
Tomorrow please English is the first letter on your timetable tomorrow so I'll take it in then okay
I've got something important I want to tell you so can you please pay attention the schools considering making
Sing some changes next year we're weighing up the possibility of introducing some weekend activities here
Special Sports training Vibes or drama or music but before we make any definite decisions we want to get your
What would appeal to you would you actually take advantage of these activities
So the Headmaster would like you all to write a paragraph this evening more if you want it saying what you think
I need to take it in first thing tomorrow please English is the first lesson on your timetable tomorrow so I'll tell
Take it in then okay
You hear ago telling her uncle about adults event she's going to take part in
Russia most excited about
Hey
Meeting new people
Be
Don't sing for a larger audience
Seeing all the dances performed
Have you heard about the dance competition Minecraft is going in for Uncle Sam I'm going to be away for a whole week
PS your mom said you were really excited about it don't you just a bit nervous about
Front of so many people though I suppose but it'll be an amazing experience
They'll be lots of really good dances from all over the country that teacher says we'll land looks just by what
Turn them on stage it's a fantastic opportunity for us
Make some good new friends there that's what I'm looking forward to most of all that it won't be so scary
Performing in front of all those people
Have you heard about the dunk competition Minecraft is going in for Uncle Sam I'm going to be away for a whole week
Your mom said you were really excited about it don't you just a bit nervous about
In front of so many people though I suppose but it'll be an amazing experience
They'll be lots of really good dances from all over the country that
Our teacher says will then look just by watching them on stage it's a fantastic opportunity for us
Yes it certainly is I expect she'll make some good new friends
Then it won't be so scary performing in front of all those people
You hear a boy talking on his mobile phone
Who is he talking to
Apparent
A friend
A brother or sister
Get Smart
I'm still at Ben's house
The friend of mine who lives in North Green
In the same block of flats that go Emma used to play tennis with
Anyway. Going to give me a lift time but he's got delayed at work so I won't be back till later
Is Mom says I can have dinner at this but that's okay
Amazon switched off or something
Leave her know if she's not back before you leave for tennis
PetSmart
I'm still at Ben's house
The friend of mine who lives in North Green
In the same block of flats that go Emma used to play tennis with
Anyway that's going to give me a lift time but he's got delayed at work so I won't be back till later
Mom says I can have dinner with this but that's okay
I'ma go my sweet stuff or something
Leave her know if she's not back before you leave for your tennis
You had two friends talking about a book they both read
What do they agree about
It is very funny in places
Be
It is Melissa Reid is who a girls
It has some great drawings
I thought that book Midnight Star was great
Did you enjoy it too or is it something that's more for girls
Well I actually liked it a lot to some bits of it made me laugh out loud though it was serious a little bit
Time to
I really like the pictures in it as well
Not sure I agree with you that
I know they're a bit childish but it was really amazing I'm going to see if I can find
Anything else by the same writer in the library
I thought that book Midnight Star was great did you enjoy it too or is it something that's more
Well I actually like to go out to some bits of it made me laugh out loud
Serious a lot of the time too I really like the pictures in it as well
I thought they were a bit childish but it was really amazing I'm going to see if I can find
Find anything else by the same writer in the library
You hear a local radio item about an unusual School
What is unusual about the school
The head is trying to help the children break a sporting record
Thermo twins in his normal 41-year group
A large number of pupils in one class share the same birthday
Teaches at London School in Ashton might be beginning to think they have double vision Never Nine sets of
Twins in the S7
Who was the sets weren't even born in the same month November
The headteacher says he has never experienced anything like this in over 30 years of teaching
He's currently doing somersaults to try to find out if this constitutes a record for children in the same school
Let alone in the same gear group
The head says that the children are hoping it will help that football team do particularly well in this year's School champ
Is it may confuse their opponents
Teaches at Longton School in Ashton might be beginning to think they have double vision
There were nine sets of twins in the S7
Who was the sets were even born in the same month November
The headteacher says he has never experienced anything like this in over 30 years of teaching
He's currently doing some research to try to find out if this constitutes a record for children in the same school
Let alone in the same year group
The head says that the children are hoping it will help that football team do particularly well in this year's School champ
Is it may confuse their opponents
You hear two friends talking about some new neighbors
How does the boy feel about them
Hey
Please to have different people next door
Happy that the duel to share his interests
Glad that they can help his family
Papua new neighbors moved in yet Jason so we could go fishing really nice
It's a couple with a daughter about much data do you think you'll become friends with her
Well she's not really into the same sorts of things as me she's really keen on hip-hop for example
But she seems nice just hope they'll be as friendly as the people who used to live there
Great the new people have a gardening business and they've offered to do a garden for us for free
Which is really kind of them my parents are very pleased about that
Happy when your neighbors moved in yet Jason so we could go fishing really nice
It's a couple with a daughter about my age do you think you'll become friends with her
Well she's not really into the same sorts of things as me she's really keen on the hip-hop for example
But she seems nice just hope they'll be as friendly as the people who used to live there
Write the new people have a gardening business and they've offered to do a garden for us for free
Which is really kind of them my parents are very pleased about that
That's the end of part 1
Now turn to part 2