Directions
You are going to hear some talks given by one speaker
You are going to be asked to answer three questions
About what the speaker says in each talk
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
D
I'd like to be the first to welcome you to Horatio and youngs
I'm Hermione and I'll be showing you around this morning
First you can see in the lobby here we have a coffee area and lunch card
The coffee is free for employees but you have to pay for the lunch
Just threw this first hallway is the employee fitness center we just got in all
All new equipment and it's really nice to work out in their this company really values
Is the well-being of their employees and I can honestly tell you
That it is a lovely place to work follow me to the elevators now and let's go see your
Our new office
Who is listening to this talk
Where does the tour begin
What is the speaker's opinion of the company
Thank you for calling Rose City cabs
Please listen carefully to a new phone menu service
If you would like to order a cab to pick you up now please press one
If you would like to reserve a cab for a light a time please press 2
Groups of five or more people will need two cars
If you have a logic group of people which needs out Services immediately
Please press 3
If you have a large group and would like to make a future reservation please press for
If you have a complaint about one of our drivers or services please remain on the line
And what about customer service professionals will be with you shortly
Thank you for choosing Rose City cabs
Where would this message please
What is required for groups of five or more people
What must you do in order to make a complaint
All of you have come here today to learn about a vital skill in today's world
Networking
If you are looking for employment
Or even looking to advance your position in your current job you must learn to connect with people
A decade ago I used to instruct my trainees to attend as many social events
As they could for one never knows where are useful person will be waiting
However today a lot of networking is done online so we'll talk more about that
One word of warning though
You must establish a clear divide between your professional links and your personal
Lynx
Probably making two different pages for yourself with two different sets of friends and
Princess
Who is the speaker
What advice was given in the past
What will she talk about
I'm here today to announce our new agreement for product placement with MJM 1
One of the biggest Bollywood movie studios
They are coming out with 10 new movies this summer and they have signed a contract this morning
Promising to include our brand name at least four times in each movie
So first we will talk about the plot of the first movie
And then we'll brainstorm where we could place our products in the film
Over the weekend I expect you all to read the scripts for the next to movies and come into
To the office on Monday morning with placement ideas for them
Where is the announcement being made
How many films is MJM releasing this summer
What will happen Monday morning
Welcome to striking strawberries my name is Marie and I will be your guide today
Miss tasting room with opened last year in order to show the varieties of strawberry which
In this area
As well as exhibit the many ways in which they can be eaten
We will first do a blind taste test in which two of you lucky folks will taste for
Different stories wearing blindfolds and guess each variety
Then all of you will sit down and all dining room and enjoy a delicious five-course meal
The main ingredient in each dish of course is all featured fruit
And we will begin up
Where is this announcement being made
What will participants do in the taste test
What will guest eat in the dining room