Questions 31 through 34
Listen to a teacher talking in a biology class
One of the strangest looking animals in the world is the anteater
Take a look at this picture of it up on the screen here
The most obvious physical feature is the long snowed or nose
The anteater uses its note to dig in the ground for ants and termites
It's two favorite foods
This animal you're looking at here is a giant anteater
It can grow to almost two meters in length
But a lot of that is it snowed in big bushy-tailed
So it's body isn't that large
There are two other anteater species they are the silky anteater and the southern tamandua
Both are a bit smaller than the giant anteater
Yes Brenda your hand is up
Where does the giant anteater live
It resides mostly in Central and South America
Its territory ranges from Mexico to Northern Brazil
How about some of its other physical characteristics
Again
Focus on the screen
It has stiff bristle liefer that's brown or gray in color
Sometimes it's for can be so dark that it's almost black
Now look at this note
Notice that it's both is at the very end of it
Cool huh
The anteater lacks teeth
But it has a very long tongue that can extend far from its most
Also observe its paws
Each ball has very long sharp claws
Beyond Cedar uses them to get inside an ant hill or termite Mound
Then it uses its tongue to find ants and termites
And to eat them
In case you're curious
A single anteater can consume up to 35,000 dance in one day now that's
What's a big appetite
The giant anteater usually lived alone
It can be territorial at times
Yet as a general rule it's rather do cile
Pumas and jaguars sometimes Hunted
But it has few other natural enemies
No how about watching a short video of an anteater attacking a termite Mound
I think you'll find this fascinating
Now answer the questions
Number 31
What is the teacher mainly talking about