Questions 35 through 38
Listen to a teacher talking and a chemistry class
It's going to be cold tonight
In fact it's going to be so cold that we're supposed to get the first Frost of the year
No I know you've all heard that word before
But what exactly does it mean what is Frost
Simply put
It's a type of Frozen water
When the air has too much water vapor
It condenses then it gets deposited on many surfaces
Including the including the ground plus cars and windows
If the temperature is cold enough
The water vapor freezes and thereby forms Frost
Frost always appears to be white in color
The reason is that the frost crystals contain are
There are different types of Frost
Let me tell you about three of them
Hoarfrost is one that
HOA are by the way
It resembles loose ice crystals
It can form on the ground or on virtually any object
It often appears in the morning and after a cold clear night
It manifests when water vapor condenses on a very cold surface
What happens is that the water vapor freezes on contact
A second type of frost is Rime Frost
Spell that rime
There's a picture of it in your books on page 194
Take a look
Note the ice crystals that are around the flower petals
It forms when icy Wind Blows and water vapor freezes on flowers plants and trees
Three branches
Pretty isn't it
I should make an important point about Frost before we continue
One big problem with frost
Is that it can kill plants
If Farmers plant their crops too early in the spring a late Frost can cause lots of damage
And many plants can die
In Fall if there is an early Frost like tonight's expected one
Farmers need to harvest their crops to keep them from suffering any damage
No third type of frost is Fern Frost
It's sometimes called window Frost
There's a picture of it in your books as well
It resembles the leaves of a fern doesn't it
This type of frost forms when you have a window pane
It's very warm on the inside and very cold on the outside
No answer the questions
Number 35
What is the teacher say about hoarfrost