Question 27 through 30
Listen to a teacher talking in a history class
People often talk about one major event in human history that led to civilization
You talkin about the discovery of agriculture
Once humans learned how to farm they were able to settle down Bill Villages and towns and basically
Great civilizations
But there's another event that help humans considerably
Does anyone have a guess
Learning how to write
Well yes that was important but it's not what I'm thinking about
I'm talking about the domestication of animals
There are huge numbers of animals on the planet
But throughout all human history only a relative handful of them have been domesticated
People have tried domesticating many animals but it's just not possible in most cases
It's likely that the first animal which humans domesticated was the dog
No one knows for sure when this happened
But we can make an educated guess
DNA testing tells us the dogs and wolves are related
Sometime in the past
They separated into two distinct species
It probably happened around do 100,000 years ago
Some experts believe it occurred in East Asia While others claim it took place in the Middle East
We don't know for sure though
How did dogs and humans come to have such a close relationship
The most popular Theory claims that they provided mutual benefits for one another
Dogs protecting humans from animals
And other humans
They also help people hunt
In return humans provided dogs with steady supplies of food
They also gave dogs relatively safe places to live
Overtime the two developed an extremely close relationship
Do we know when the first dog was Tamed
No but again we can make an educated guess there's a site in Germany where human and dogs
Skeletons were found buried together
Those bones date back to around 14,000 years ago
A similar sighting China has bones that date to 7500 years ago
At a dig site in Siberia that's around 6200 years old dog was found buried next
Too many humans in a cemetery
All three of those fine show how highly regarded dogs were in their communities
So we can infer that dogs have been domesticated in those places due to where they were buried
No answer the questions
Number 27
What is the teacher mainly discussing