Question 77 through 79 refer to the following announcement
This is an announcement from the National Weather Service there is a winter storm warning for the entire Northeast region
End of the state of Massachusetts from 4 p.m. to 9 a.m. expect a wintry mix of gale force winds and heavy snow
Overnight temperatures below freezing I likely to cause hazardous driving conditions on toll roads
Doing this. All non-essential travel is strongly discouraged please bring old pets inside and in
Angelo horses and livestock have food and shelter overnight
Weather update
Number 77
Why is this announcement being made
Number 78
What kind of weather is expected overnight
Number 79 what should all animal owners do