Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following excerpt from a talk
The Bryan School of Business understands the needs of busy Executives who are interested in expanding their skin
But you don't have time to attend regular classes for this reason executive insightla
Lecture series is available online to everyone who professional studies and our business and
Certificate
Alcor lecture the ready for you to watch when you have the time
Choose your own schedule and make school fit your life not the other way around
We offered you sessions every other month so you can start to further your education whenever you are ready
Number 80
Who would be interested in this talk
Number 81
What does the speaker imply when she says your life not the other way around
Number 82
How many times a year does the school offer new sessions