Questions 83 through 85 refer to the following message
Hello you have reached Pacific Gas Company we appreciate your business and thank you for calling
For English press 1 for Spanish press 2
For billing inquiries please press 3 to report a gas leakage or
For damaged pipe please hang up and call 911 to request a new service please press
For to cancel the service please press 5 to speak to a live representative
Please press fix
All of our customer service representatives are currently serving customers please hold
Your call is important to us all calls will be answered in the order in which they are received
Number 83
What kind of company is this message service for
Number 84
What number should I customer press to get information about a bill
Number 85
What will a customer be able to do if he or she presses 6