Question 74 through 76 refer to the following telephone message
Good afternoon this is Brianna Rivera calling for Dave Wyatt you left a message
Asking me for a reference for Joy kim-joy would be a wonderful addition to your stuff
She worked for me as an intern from 2017 to 2018 just after she graduate
Waited from college Joy was very popular with clients and staff alike she is a self-motivated
And reliable worker and always willing to go the extra mile to get things done her work always occur
Stated the required found it and she made several suggestions while she was here that improved efficiency greatly
Please get in touch if I can provide any other information
Number 74
Woman calling Wyatt
Number 75
How does Brianna know Joy
Number 76
What is not a good description of joy