Parts for
Directions
You will hear some talks given by a single speaker
You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
On your answer sheet
The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time
Question 71 through 73 refer to the following excerpt from a meeting
With a lot of international conferences coming up some of you have expressed concern about communicating with gas
So don't speak English I've decided to subscribe to a telephone interpretation service for a one month
Trial. You call a toll-free number and operator will answer and ask what language you need
Then the operator will put you through to an interpreter who can translate that language you and the gas will
Well then communicate with The Interpreter who will translate the entire conversation will start this service on Monday
At the end of the month I'll be asking for your feedback if it goes well I'll make it permanent
Number 71
Where does the speaker most likely work
Number 72
What is the speaker explaining to the audience
Number 73
Which of the following is true about the new service