Question 1
Listen to this conversation
Rob is looking for
A letter
B file
C amended Wills
See Uncle mrs. Robinson coming in 10 minutes and I can't find
Those are the letters we had this week I can only find the messages
Put the case File is what is the amended Wills with the olmecs
What am I going to do a on it
City Uncle mrs. Robinson
Incoming in 10 minutes and I can't find a file
I can only find the message I put the case File is what is the amended Wills
I can't see it and I need it now what am I going to do
Trey on it
Question 2
Listen to this receptionist speaking on the telephone
The receptionist wax for
A garage
Be the police
See a lawyer
Can you tell me little more
You comfort.
I'll make
You have a problem and you like to see mr. can you tell me
You comfort.
I'll make
Question three
Listen to this news report
DSS Persian Gulf
Collided with
A a rock
Be another ship
See a lighthouse
Induces just coming in of a large oil spill is just off the staff
Southeast coast it seems that the SS Persian Gulf Sunday change cause for some reason not yet clear and collided with a small
Which was making deliveries to the lighthouse on Brighton Rock
The ship's main all tank is ruptured and the emergency services are not rushing to minimise the damage this oil slick is
Likely to cause
Music just coming in of a large oil spill is just off the South
Southeast coast it seems that the SS Persian Gulf Sunday change code for some reason not yet clear and collided with a spoon
Which was making deliveries to the lighthouse on Brighton Rock
The ship's main oil tank is ruptured and the emergency services are not rushing to minimise the damage this oil plate is likely
2 calls
Question for
Listen to this conversation between two people while waiting for that property to be inspected
The property a
Is ready
Be
Will be ready tomorrow
See
Will be ready in time for the inspectors
Okay let's make sure we've got ourselves organized be arriving to be inspected
David is the 29th so we've got two weeks to prepare
What about the books in the auditor's report
That was done while you were in Hamburg didn't you notice in your office
Walkman stop tomorrow and will be finished in good time
Okay let's make sure we've got ourselves organized arrival of the inspectors
They visited the 29th so we put two weeks to prepare
What about the books in the oldest report
That was done while you were in Hamburg didn't you notice in your office what about the pharmacy
Walkman stop tomorrow and will be finished in good time
Question 5
Listen to this telephone salesman
The man is selling
Ownership of a flat in the Bahamas
Be
Ownership of a flash in the Bahamas
See
Rental of a flat in the Bahamas
Good morning sir please don't hang up
If you're prepared to listen to me for the next 30 seconds you could win a major prize
I represent the firm sending timeshare property in the Bahamas
Principal payment only around 5,000 lb you could pontone a property in the Bahamas
Folsom
You can have possession of this flat in the Bahamas for two weeks
You can take your holidays and bring your friends over to enjoy an exotic location when you're not there it doesn't stand
The other pontone is takeover and keep the fat in good condition
Good morning sir please don't hang up if you're prepared to listen to me for the next 30 seconds
You could win a major prize
I represent the firm sending timeshare property in the Bahamas for small payment only around 5,000 lb
You could Ponto property in the Bahamas
What is comparative expulsom you can have the best of this flat in the Bahamas for two weeks
You can take your holidays and bring your friends over to enjoy an exotic location when you're not there it doesn't stand
The other pontone is takeover and keep the Phantom good condition
Question sticks
You hear kritik choking on a discussion program
He is disgusting a
Ifilm
Be a book
C a radio program
Oh surely not John Shirley not it really is one of the best I've read nothing wrong.
Okay at the challenging subject you don't expect an oven on the everyday life of shepherds on the remote Scottish islands be fascinating
From the pipeline
I found a stylistically very short
Use of dialect is highly original I'm very effective and I thought that was true pesos in the Final Chapter
Oh surely not John showing on it really is one of the best I've read none Longshot
Okay so challenging subject even expect an oven on the everyday life of shepherds on the remote Scottish islands be fascinating
Bridget me right from the first line I find it stylistically very short
You have done that was highly original I'm very effective and I thought that was true pesos in the Final Chapter
Question 7
You hear conversation between can and Berry
Ken has
Hey
Made other plans
Be
Bean playing well recently
See
Become a professional
Can I'm desperate for a
Forward on Saturday you've got to play I don't know
I promised I'd take me over to shopping list play can is the quarter-final of a cop with you on our team
We can win this you know probably William play four years
Electronics Mario don't be silly can
Professional
You could run rings around the rest of us with only one leg you're really must
Can I'm desperate for
Forward on Saturday you've got to play well I don't know I promised I'd take me to shopping
Can is the quarter-final with you on our team we can win this
William Clay figures
I'm going to promise Mario don't be silly can
You were a professional you could run rings around the rest of us with only one leg
Question 8
You both fog lamp your car but it doesn't work
You telephone the dealer and hear this message
You
Hey
Call the new number
Bee leave a message
See
Hold on
This is Harris, pods
I'm sorry the lines are engaged at the moment but your call has been queued
One of our systems will deal with you shortly
If you want to leave a message to place an order please do so after the tone but don't forget to leave your name and telephone number
If you're interested in a second-hand sounds apartment you may like to buy a different line
Try calling 021-685-4286
This is Harris carpets
I'm sorry the lines were engaged at the moment but your call has been queued
One of our systems will deal with you shortly
If you want to leave a message to place an order please do so after the tone but don't forget to leave your name and telephone number
If you're interested in a second time sales department you may like to try a different line
Try calling 021-685-4286