Questions 86 through 88 refer to the following message
Hello this is Sarah at Windsor Windows calling for Bryan Adams I'm happy to report that The Purge
Permit for your new windows has been approved by the city so we can install them whenever you are ready your quote
Of April 5th was 43 windows with the dimensions of 24 in by 12 in
Quoted you a price of $350 per window but our supplier is closing out that line
We were able to purchase them we are excited to share that discount
Installation will be $300 per window just give me a call at nine one six nine four
63697 and I'll set up an appointment with our installers thanks
Number 86
What is the purpose of the message
Number 87
How much will mr. Adams pay in total for three windows
Number 88
What should Mr Adams do when he gets this message
Go on to the next page