Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following talk and class schedule
Thank you for coming to the net Charlie a month cooking class today we'll learn how to preserve fruits and
Vegetables will then sterilization techniques that you can use to produce safe and tasty food
But let me talk for a bit about some of all upcoming classes
On June 8th Indian Chef Shari will introduce traditional Indian curries
Her classes are always a lot of fun
On July 7th Maria will teach you how to make delicious salads and desserts with seasonal fruits
Unfortunately we didn't notice a typing error until after we send the schedule to the printer
July 9th should in fact read August 9th
Number 98
What is this talk mainly about
Number 99
On what date will Maria teach a class
Number 100
Look at the class schedule what class will now take place on August 9th
This is the end of the listening test
Turn 2 part 5 in your test book