Questions 95 through 97 refer to the following talk and price list
If you use a computer or any kind of smart device you run the risk of your device getting infected by a virus
Many people think that you can only get malware by downloading suspicious files not updating
Software or visiting the wrong website the truth is that you can get infected just by visit
Sitting a website even if it's a website you trust your bank the electricity company even
Can government websites can transmit a virus ABC offers a variety of basic antivirus software
Where packages to protect your computer for 2 days only we are offering a $10 discount on all packages
Don't delay protect yourself today
Number 95
According to the speaker who is at risk of getting a virus
Number 96
What special deal is this speaker offering
Number 97
Look at the price list how much would a 20 device package cost if purchased during the neck
Today's