Questions 92 through 94 refer to the following excerpt from a meeting and agenda
Okay I'm going to get this meeting started Miranda will be our note-taker today thanks Miranda
You should all have a copy of the agenda because I emailed it to you last Friday you'll see
At the December lunch is listed second on the agenda unit he will be talking about that but she's going
I'll be late because she is supervising a delivery she should be here in about 45 minutes so we'll just switch the oar
Order of the lunch and the volunteer event if that sounds good to everyone that should work well for timing
Number 92
When did the speaker send the agenda to her colleagues
Number 93
Why will union he be late for the meeting
Number 94
Look at the agenda which employee will be the second to speak at the meeting today