Questions 89 through 91 refer to the following excerpt from a talk
I'm offices Sanchez with the Los Rios Community College Police Department I need to talk about career
Opportunities without Department many people are not aware that the college district has a police force
There was a police station located on each of the full college campuses the members of lipd
Responsible for protecting life and property owned any property owned or controlled by the Los Rios Community
Lee College District to work as a police officer now to Papa you must be a graduate of the state
Police Academy have a clean driver's license and have a minimum of two years work experience in law enforcement
Number 89
What is the TOC mainly about
Number 90
How many campuses does the Los Rios Community College have
Number 91 what is not mentioned as a requirement for working as a college police
Officer