Test 2 part 4 Page 65
Directions
You are going to hear some talks given by one speaker
You are going to be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter A B C
4D on your answer sheet on page the talks are not printed in your test book
Hi this is Janet Suzuka from the office I'm sorry to bother you on the weekend
But I need to let everyone know that our email system has been hacked
At around 2 a.m. on Friday a person or persons hacked the system and
Retrieved all the email addresses of our employees
These addresses were then used all day on Saturday to send advertisement
To every address saved in each account
This means that every client you have ever emailed and every friend or associate
You have messaged got some very annoying messages in their inboxes
I was alerted to the problem Sunday morning and I'm working to resolve the problem right now
I'm very sorry for the inconvenience and I promise to strengthen our security systems
Right away
Call me at the office if you have any questions
What is the purpose of this message
When was the system hacked
What is the speaker doing right now
The ferry to Catalina Island will leave in 20 minutes
Please have old Vehicles ready to board in 5 minutes
If your vehicle is not in line with the appropriate sticker on the window at that time you cannot drive on
To the ferry
Windows ticket passes can be purchased at the booth in the northwest corner of the parking lot
Do passengers on foot please have tickets already and one form of identification
The trip will take approximately one hour
Return tickets can be purchased at our destination
Thank you and have a good day
Who is listening to this announcement
What must cars have in order to board
How long is the trip
Are you a small-business owner who is wondering how to make social media work for you
Would you like to expand your customer base significantly without spending much money
If the answer is yes please text social contact 21
800 987 9999
And a customer services representative from social contact
Will return your call within the hour
Please have your credit card ready
The payment is processed a personal advisor will help you with a business plan to bring you
You marketing strategy into the 21st century
We can start helping you today
Remember it's as easy as texting social contact to 1-800
98.7
What is the purpose of this advertisement
Who should send a text to this number
What do you need to have when the representative calls you
Thank you for coming in on such short notice
As you all know we have been in negotiations for months with garabelli the famed cha
Chocolatiers from Italy
Acquiring garabelli as another part of this company would be a huge game for us as
The international brand recognition for this name is very high
So Not only would we see an immediate Rising sales nationally we would also be a
Entering into the European candy Market
Well I am extremely pleased to announce today that an agreement has been reached and Gyro
Belly becomes part of the Bradbury family today
Who is listening to this announcement
Why is this deal so important
When will these two companies merge
Hello this is Gina from Horizon mobile returning a call from Mr Glenmont
Mr. Martinez had a question about the refund for the mobile phone he recently bought from us
In order to receive the refund of $100 he must mail in the refunds card
A copy of his receipt to all head offices
Please address the envelope to
Horizon mobile refund Center
1616 Gateway Drive
Philadelphia
PA
Just to reiterate this is a mail-in refund only and cannot be
Email or fax
Mr. Martinez has 30 days to mail the documents
If the envelope is postmarked more than 30 days after the date of purchase the refund
Is invalid
If you have any questions please call us back at 7 for 656
Find sticks
Thank you
Where would this message be heard
When did mr. Martinez buy his phone