Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following talk and table
Asmaul ambassadors you'll be responsible for answering questions about the new mall floor plans or
Available for customers but as you know only the businesses in the a section will be open during the first week of
Business
Also only the first floor will be open
The B section will open next week and the second floor on June 2nd in addition there have been
Some changes in which stores are occupying which stalls Hannah's Handbags and book Bonanza have
Switch stalls I recommend writing this on your floor plan you'll need to inform customers of this chain
Change
Number 98
What will customers not be able to do this week
Number 99 what will happen on June 2nd
Number 100
Look at the graphic where will Hannah's handbags be located
This is the end of the listening test
Turn 2 part 5 in your test book