Questions 95 through 97 refer to the following excerpt from a sales pitch and price list
You want to give you a loyal customers a thank you gift but how do you pick a gift up they'll love
Gift Solutions offers a range of gifts for corporate customers give him a hug with your company logo
Wrong give him up with your clients name at only $3 a piece it's a personalized baggage
And every time they use it now remember it was from you want something at is a Lorex
Expensive how about movie tickets they'll remember a fun night out at your expense
We're offering a pack of 10 tickets. $25 want to give something more practical
Monogram desktop planners off $5 a piece
Number 95
Who is the woman probably talking to
Number 96
What is the woman suggest to make gifts more memorable
Number 97 at the graphic how much would it cost to buy a minimum order of
Planners