Now you will hear longer talks or conversations each talk or conversation will be followed by
Three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13 listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Mary why don't you stay here for a moment I need to chat with you about something
Sure thing mr. Kimball
I'm curious I asked a question in class that nobody could answer
Remember that
Yes sir I do well nobody answered
But I'm pretty sure that you could have
I'm a good judge of students
After all
I've been teaching for more than two decades that I could tell by the look in your eyes that you knew the answer
I'm right aren't I yes you are I knew the answer
So why didn't you speak up and say anything
I don't really enjoy speaking in front of others
I'm a little shy I am I get kind of nervous if I have to talk in class
IC
In that case would it help if I called on you I mean instead of raising your hand and volunteering an answer
How about if I just asked you directly
Do you think that would be better
It might I can't say for sure I just have a hard time speaking up
Okay let's try it the next time we have class if it makes you feel uncomfortable
I won't do it anymore
But I'd like to see you speak more since I know you have a lot to contribute
We'll get my idea shot
Thanks mr. Kimball I appreciate that
Now answer the questions
Number 10
What are the speakers mainly discussing