Questions 14 through 18 listen to a conversation between a teacher and a student
Miss Widow
You mentioned something about an extra-credit project in class today
Could you tell me a little about it
Okay
But why do you want to do it
I'm not pleased with my grades so I figured that if I can get some bonus point
I might be able to pull off an A in your class
That's a good attitude to have Bill but I don't have much time to tell you about it
Because I've got class in a couple of minutes and so do you I believe
That's correct
I have mr. Thompson's class next
Well you don't want to be late for his class
You know how he can be when students are even a few seconds late
Yeah
I know all about that
Anyway let's get back to the matter at hand the extra-credit project involves doing some work in the
Lab I want you to think of an experiment that you'd like to do
What kind of experiment
Anything really read a couple of chemistry books in the library to get some ideas but check
Check with me for approval before you start so basically just do the experiment and then
Write a lab report on both the results and your interpretation of the results
That's it cool
Oh
How many bonus points can I get for this
Anywhere from 125 it depends on the quality of your work now get going the Bell is about
About to ring
Now answer the questions
Number 14
Why does the boy want to do the projects