Questions 19 through 22 listen to a conversation between two students
Jimmy are you going to try out for the baseball team again this year yeah but
I don't think I need to try out for the team
Coach is already told me that I'm going to be the starting second baseman
That's great congratulations thanks Kevin
So why are you curious about the team
Well I've been giving some thought to trying out
I'm a pretty decent picture
So I think I've got a shot at making the team
If you're any good you'll probably make it
Two of our best pictures graduated last year
So we could definitely use a new player too
That sounds good so assuming that I make the team
What is it like to be on the team
It's really cool we play about 20 games a year more if we make the playoffs
4:30 home games and half a road games
How far away are the road games
I'd say most of them are within an hour's Drive of the school
But there are a couple of schools White Plains and Gadsden
I think
That are about 2 hours away
That's a long ride on the school bus
Huh I didn't know that yeah it's no fun riding home on the bus if you lose one of those
Games
I can imagine
How does being on a team affect your school work Jimmy
It's rather hard when you've got a test the day after an away game
But I try to do my best so my grades are good
I don't know if you work part-time or not but you won't be able to do that if you're on the team and want to keep
Keep your grades up
Now answer the questions
Number 19
What are the speakers mainly talking about