Questions 23 through 26
Listen to a conversation between two students
I am so overloaded with work I have no idea what I'm going
To do
I know what you mean the teacher seemed to be giving us a lot of homework these days
I'm totally swamped as well
Yeah but you don't do any extracurricular activities do you
Not this year my parents want me to focus solely on my grades
Since they aren't as good as they should be
So they won't let me play basketball or joined any clubs
That's too bad
Yeah I wish they'd reconsider but they won't
Anyway
What extracurricular activities are you doing that have you so busy
Wow I'm a member of the math team and they also write for the school newspaper and work on
The school yearbook committee wow that's a lot
Which of those three activities keeps you the most occupied
Right now it's the school newspaper I have to write at least one article a week for it
18 isn't too bad all we do is go to math contest every once in awhile for example
We've got a contest this Saturday
That's cool how about the yearbook
We're doing some preliminary meetings now the bulk of the work will be in the spring or still me
Meeting at least once a week good luck with all that it seems like your schedule is packed
Now answer the questions
Number 23 what are the students mainly talking about