Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following lecture
There have been 7.1 billion smartphones manufactured since 2007
That's enough phone for almost every person in the world
But demand for new and improved models continues to grow most people want a new phone every couple of
Here's this demand puts tremendous pressure on our environment very few people recycle their
Are smartphones when they purchase a new one
Less than 16% of E-Waste is recycled much of that waste goes into landfills
We're heavy metals can Legion to groundwater
These heavy metals cause serious health effects for humans and death for smaller organisms
The metals buildup in body tissues overtime and can cause cancer joint pains and other health issues
Number 80
According to the speaker how often do people buy a new phone
Number 81
Why is the growing popularity of smartphones and environmental issue
Number 82 according to the speaker what happens to smartphones after they are discarded