Parts for
Directions
You will hear some talks given by a single speaker
You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
On your answer sheet
The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time
Question 71 through 73 refer to the following excerpt from a meeting
There is no nice way of saying this you are all making a mess of the break room the room is constantly
Full of dirty dishes and cups and decaying leftovers
It is unfair for those of you who do make an effort to clean up and it is unsanitary
As of next Monday each week a different team of employees will be put on break room duty the team will win
Wipe down tables clean the microwave and sweep the floor I'm hoping that's spreading out the responsibility
Do you like this will help keep the room clean
Number 71
What is the purpose of this talk
Number 72 what does the speaker not mention about the break room
Number 73
As of next week who will clean the breakroom