Question 74 through 76 refer to the following announcement
Recently it has come to my attention that people have been taking office supplies home and this is against come
Company policy items like staplers copy paper and even toilet paper from the restroom storage
Words have come up missing during the monthly inventory I want to remind everyone that these items are company property
And if you are caught taking them you will be fired while these items are freely available for use
At work that is the only place where you can take advantage of them consider this a warning
Number 74
Who is most likely making this announcement
Number 75
How often does the company take inventory of its supplies
Number 76
What will happen to someone who takes home toilet paper