Question 77 through 79 refer to the following review
Hi guys thanks for checking my web Channel about a week ago I bought these night visor driving
Glasses you can use them as regular sunglasses but he's the awesome thing about them you can wait
Them at night while you are driving to reduce the glare of other cause they come in brown black and fill
I have the black here they come with a case and a cleaning cloth so it's easy to keep them in good condition
Well they are a great pair of sunglasses I was really impressed
How well I could see at night
Try them yourself
Number 77
Where is the speaker giving this review
Number 78
What is the speaker reviewing
Number 79
What is the speaker's overall opinion of the product