Questions 83 through 85 refer to the following talk
Hi everyone I'm Paul Hernandez a staff member in the Admissions and Records office here at City
College
You've decided that City College is right for you and I'm here to help you with the application process
Your success Starts Here the Admissions and Records Office is here to help you all the way for
From your initial application to graduation
First you'll need to submit an online application form then you will need to take an online
Orientation to learn about financial aid registration for classes important locations on campus and
Types of degrees
Then you should meet with a counselor and complete an education plan
Number 83 where does the speaker work
Number 84
Who most likely is the audience for this talk
Number 85
Which is not something that needs to be done as part of the application process