Question 1
Listen to this news item
The firemen rescued
Three children
Be
Mrs. Janet Sherwood
See
Patience from All Saints Hospital
Three children aged 64 and 18 months were rescued
From the Blazing home by 5 in last night
Apartment related by the children's Mother message electric heater in the children's bedrooms at 5
The upstairs at the house
The children were not had better being kept overnight at nearby All Saints hospital for observation
Three children aged 64 and 18 months were rescued
From the Blazing home by 5 tonight
Apartment related by the children's Mother message electrocuted in the children's bedroom sets
The upstairs at the house
But it being kept overnight at nearby All Saints hospital for observation
Question 2
Listen to these instructions
You should let tea Brew for
2 minutes
Be
3 minutes
See
One minute
So how do you make a really good cup of tea
Use the steam from the devil to roam the inside of a teapot
Use 1001 to deport good tea
Control the boiling water for 3 minutes
Only can do cups add milk and sugar to taste
So how do you make a really good cup of tea
Use the steam from the kettle to warm the inside of a teapot
Apathy
Use 1001 to default to use good tea
Do the boiling water for 3 minutes
Only Thing 2 cups add milk and sugar to taste
Question three
Listen to this conversation
Danny intends to contact local companies by
Winningham
Be writing to them
See
Cooling round
I've lost my job
What companies are used to do with what you can do
Around most of them are local and like to make a better impression button
I've lost my job
Companies 8 to deal with
Around most of them are local am I can make a better impression than button
Question for
Listen to this transaction
Where does the exchange take place
Shop
In a bank
Sienna texting
Batman Day 2019
Oh I don't think I have that exactly
No problem. Okay give me that
I think so
Making beats 2019
I don't think I'm not exactly
No problem.
I think so
Two pence pieces
15010 Pence change thank you very much
Question 5
Listen to this announcement on board an aircraft
The purpose of the announcement is to inform passengers
B of the entertainment available
See
The latest news
Welcome aboard a transatlantic flight 465 to Miami
We are sorry to announce about half an hour to take off time this is due to Industrial action
Inconvenience you while we are waiting for the cabins.
Complimentary drinks in magazines in the meantime please remain seated
We do hope you enjoy transatlantic hospitality
Welcome aboard a transatlantic flight 465 to Miami
We are sorry to announce there's a delay of about half an hour to take off time this is due to Industrial action
Play went inconvenience you while we are waiting for the cabins.
Complimentary drinks in magazines in the meantime please remain seated
Do hope you enjoy transatlantic hospitality
Question 6
Listen to this recorded telephone message
You have phoned
Hey
A library
Be a telephone ordering service
See a post office
Thank you for calling the bargain Traders or denying your cord is being queued while please make sure you have the
The following information available to order quickly and accurately
Credit card type it's number and its expiry date second-order
Which item you wish to order please tell us the item code the color the sign and the quantity required
Your order will be sent today please allow one week for postal delivery
Thank you for calling the bug and traitors or denying your call is being queued meanwhile please make sure you have
The following information available to order quickly and accurately
First we will need your credit card type it's number and its expiry date
Second only details of the order
Which item you wish to order please tell us the item code the color the sign on the quantity required
The order will be sent today but please allow one week for postal delivery
Question 7
Listen to the end of the speak
The speech takes place at
Grafton
Be
Christening
See
Wedding
About Joe Louis
Many years of happiness and every best wishes for the future
Goodnight one last present your teeth
If you offend your glasses
And that is to ask you to raise your glasses for a toast to the health of the Bridesmaids
Ladies and gentlemen
The Bridesmaids
Happy couple many years of happiness and every best wishes for the future
Goodnight one last Pleasant UT
If you offend your glasses
And that is to ask you to raise your glasses for a toast to the health of the Bridesmaids
Ladies and gentlemen
The Bridesmaids
Question 8
Listen to this conversation which takes place in a dress shop
Brenda thinks the red dress
Hey is too long
Bedone suta
C make her look short
Probably ain't made you look taller
Can you try the blue one on again
Probably make it look taller
Who played the blue one on again