Question 1
Listen to these Anza phone messages
Off to the messages Nick is supposed to
Call his mother
Be
Take his mother to Blackpool
See
Call Jenny
Hi Nick it's Jenny look I've been trying to get hold of my more day but I'm not getting it on stuff
Can you pop round and see if he's okay I'll call you later
Jenny again
Forget the last message I forgot the Blackpool today call me anyway
Hi Nick it's Jenny look I've been trying to get hold of Mom all day but I'm not getting it also
Bitwise can you pop round and see if he's okay I'll call you later
Skinny again to get the last message I forgot to Blackpool today call me anyway
Question 2
Listen to this investment
You can reduce your shopping bill by
Hey
Buying as the way products
Be
Buying popular alternatives
See
Buying half as much
Cut your shopping bill in half with eyes do a savers
That's the way we're doing everything we possibly can to help reduce the cost of a weekly shopping now you can cut your shopping billing
Top simply by switching to as the way Sabre products instead of more popular alternative of course supermarket
It may argue that price the too low but that's the way we don't do things by half
Lightning below to Shoppers
Cut your shopping bill in half with eyes the way savers
That's the way we're doing everything we possibly can to help reduce the cost of your weekly shopping now you can cut your shopping bill in half
Products instead of more popular alternative of course other supermarkets
They argue that price the tulo but eyes the way we don't do things by half
Lightning below to Shoppers
Question three
Listen to this news item
The doctor stopped at Alan's house because
Hey he had broken down
Be
He was lost
See the house was on fire
Story of a lucky coincidence local Farm
Manhattan Bennett yesterday morning when his wife went into labor and he found that his car would not start
Screaming that the baby was on its way and it was too late to the hospital
A man couldn't believe his luck when a passing motorist to stop to asking for directions turned out to be a success
Allen now the proud father of a healthy 8 lb boys safely delivered at home said I hope I have
If he ever has a fire
The story of a lucky coincidence
Yesterday morning he found that his car would not start
Screaming that the baby was on its way and then it was too late for the hospital
Couldn't believe his luck when a passing motorist to start walking the directions to doubt to be a doctor
Allen now the proud father of a healthy 8 lb boys safely delivered at home said I hope I have
Happened to be driving past the Doctor's house if he ever has a fire
Question for
Listen to this conversation
Mary is instructed to use a lot of
Hey
Resume
B lamb
Sea potatoes
Mom
School project
Xavier still start with a large low-sided metal tray and put the letters sliced
Potatoes and a sliced onion in the buses
But the loss of taste and especially Rosemary almond
On top of that put your needs
Mom
Project
Potatoes with the meat to make Steve used to start with a large low-sided metal tray and put Solaris life
Onion in the Boston how many potatoes
Especially
On top of that put you neat
Question 5
Listen to this receptionist on the phone
The receptionist waxing
A school
Be a beautician
See a doctor surgery
Yes of course you can book A Course in mind
German know what level you and
Well that's no problem we have supper and will test you when you arrive when would you like to
21st that's fine complete reception and chocolate to make I will be here to meet you
What did you have in mind
German if
Well that's no problem we have several levels and will test you when you arrive when would you like to
21st that's fine complete reception and dr. Schumacher
Question 6
Listen to this announcement
It is made at the scene of
Hey a rubbery
Be a road accident
See
A burning building
Can we ask members of the public to stand back please
We appreciate people they want to do all they can to help but this is only making the job of the Emergency Services Board
Difficult
Please realize that people may have to jump from the other floors to escape the flames and there is also the danger of falling
Thank you for your cooperation
Can we ask members of the public to stand back please
We appreciate people they want to do all that kinds of help but this is only making the job of the Emergency Services Board
Difficult
Please realize that people may have to jump from the other floors to escape the Flames. There is also the danger of falling
Stereo
Thank you for your cooperation
Question 7
Listen to this conversation
The tree will probably be taken away by
Hey
Allen
Be
Jim
See
Steve
Jim black trim a front garden with David's about the chef 51 set
Install and actually Steve already said that he giveth me if I wanted
David feel like crying sometime
Jim let trim a front goddamn which David's about the staff did you once it
Pine-Sol and actually Steve already said that he give it to me if I wanted
David feel like fine sometime
Question fate
Listen to this extract
The speaker doesn't make this recipe very often because the brownies are
Hey
Hard to resist
Be
To moist
See
To cake like
Today we're going to make chocolate fudge brownies
These are not squares beloved by Americans I do usually most in chewy
People often say Smith at brownies fail because they expect cake with the correct consistency
Like the chewy
So I try not to make them too often
You can fly covering them with a chocolate fudge store North Atlanta
Now
How do you make the brownies
How sweet to make chocolate fudge brownies
Visa B2 love Americans I do usually most entry
People often takes me that brownies failed because they expect cakes but the correct consistency is not cake
Like the chewy
So I try not to make them too often
You can try covering them with a chocolate fudge store
Now
How do you make the brownies