Fce practice tests by Mark Harrison
Publishing copyright Oxford University press 2008
Cd-1
Test 1
Part 1
You hear people talking in eight different situations
Questions 128 choose the best answer
B o c
You hear someone talking about football referees
What is the speaker's attitude towards referees
They make too many mistakes
Be
They deserve sympathy
See
Summer better than others
You have to feel sorry for referees I mean they're under terrible pressure throughout the game with players shantina
The fans of both sides give him a hard time they just called win
They make mistakes plenty of them are there any human
Thinking I'm going to do really badly today that doing that best some people
People think that there are referees to just want to draw attention to themselves you think there is important as the players but that's not mine
I mean I won't Magill it'll that criticism all the time
You have to feel sorry for referees I mean they're on the terrible pressure throughout the game with players shanton
The fans of both sides give him a hard time they just called when
Do they make mistakes plenty of them but they're only human
Thinking I'm going to do really badly today that doing that best something
People think that there are referees to just want to draw attention to themselves
I mean that criticism all the time
You hear a famous chef talkin about his week
What did he say about what happened during the week
He had a problem that was not his fault
Be
He didn't want to appear on so many programs
See
He had his first experience of live TV
I had a bit of an old week I went to to do a TV cookery show
I had to make my special recipe pancakes but the pain they gave me in the studio wasn't nearly big enough
So it makes things difficult
But it turns out alright in the end they were just a bit smaller than usual
Later in the week I was on a radio show on string listen is questions about cooking and then I did a few
View interviews about my new book
I had a bit of an old week I went to to do a TV cookery show
I had to make my special recipe pancakes but the pain they gave me in the studio wasn't nearly big enough
So it makes things difficult
But it turned out alright in the end they were just a bit smaller than usual
Later in the week I was on a radio show on string listen his questions about cooking and then I did a few
View interviews about my new book
You hear someone talking about her career in dancing
What does she emphasized
The contribution made by her parents
Be
How much hard work she did
See
The desire to be a dumpster
I just had to dance
When I was a go I was always putting on Dancing shows for my parents
By the time I was 7 I knew what I wanted to be
I'm not feeding never went away
I told my parents I wanted to do proper ballet so I went to a ballet school and I
I've been dancing ever since
I used to have classes after school and on Saturdays
And when I finish school I went to a full-time Dance Academy for years now I'm teaching Don's
And I've never been happier
I just had to dance
When I was a go I was always putting on Dancing shows for my parents
By the time I was 7 I knew what I wanted to be
I'm not feeding never went away
I told my parents I wanted to do proper ballet so I went to a ballet school and I
Open downswing of a sentence
I used to have classes after school and on Saturdays
And when I finish school I went to a full-time Dance Academy for years now I'm teaching Don's
Never been happier
Full
You hear someone talking on the phone at work
Who is she talking to
Hey
A colleague
Be
A boss
See
Client
What time are you going to make it
You know it's a very important meeting and we talked really discuss the issue properly without you
Yes I'll tell her you'll get here as soon as you can
But I know she isn't going to be very pleased
Okay I'll delay things as long as I can
I'll say you've got problems at home or something
No I won't say you've overslept I don't want to get you in trouble
What time are you going to make it
You know it's a very important meeting and we talked really discuss the issue properly without you
Yes I'll tell her you'll get here as soon as you can
But I know she isn't going to be very pleased
Okay
I'll delay things as long as I can
I'll say you've got problems at home or something
No I won't say you've overslept I don't want to get you in trouble
You hear a radio presenter talking about her book
What feeling does the presenter Express about the book
Hey
Doubt that it does exactly what it says it does
Be
Amazement as how up-to-date information is
See
Curiosity about how it was written
Have you ever wondered how many tons of food do you eat in a lifetime or how many miles of blood vessels there are
Nobody know well there are plenty more intriguing entries in this huge book of fat
It claims to have the most accurate and up-to-date information about every subject on a
I'm not sure it covers absolutely everything but it suddenly has lots of fascinating facts
I'm pretty much any topic you can think of you wouldn't be able to put it down
Have you ever wondered how many tons of food do you eat in a lifetime or how many miles of blood vessels there are
On your body oh well there are plenty more intriguing entries in this huge book of fat
It claims to have the most accurate and up-to-date information about every subject on a
I'm not sure it covers absolutely everything but it suddenly has lots of fascinating facts
I'm pretty much any till that you can think of you wouldn't be able to put it down
You hear part of an interview with a famous comedian
What did he say about his school days
The teachers never criticized him
Be
He was only good at one subject
See
Other people found him amusing
What was your favorite subject to school max unlifted so I was good
I couldn't get enthusiastic about all the subject I wanted to show off
I like the logic of it we were good students yes pretty much
I didn't cause a lot of trouble or anything like that
I was tricky and I like having a life with my friends but always managed to make the teachers life before they told me
The great time at school
What was your favorite subject to school max
I'm lifted so I was good at it
Couldn't get enthusiastic about all the subjects but with math I wanted to show off
I like the logic of it we were good students yes pretty much
I didn't cause a lot of trouble or anything like that I was Chi-Chi and I liked having a laugh with my friends but
Always manage to make the teachers left before they told me off
All in all I had a great time at school
You hear someone talking about a person he knows
What is the speaker doing
Complaining
Be
Apologizing
Arguing
I really don't see why I have to keep doing him favors he never throws any for me
I guess you were right about him all along
You always said you took advantage of other people
I can't believe you then but now I can see what you mean
I can see now that I was totally wrong about him
It's a real shame because I thought we were great friends for a while
But I'm just not going to put up with him any longer
I mean he surely can't expect to behave like that and get away with it
I really don't see why I have to keep doing him favors he never does any for me
I guess you were right about him all along
You always said you took advantage of other people
I can't believe you then but now I can see what you mean
I can see now that I was totally wrong about him
It's a real shame because I thought we were great friends for a while
But I'm just not going to put up with him any longer
I mean he surely can't expect to behave like that and get away with it
You hear a tour guide talkin to a group of visitors to a museum
What did you tell him about the museum
It's easy to get lost in it
Be
Big groups aren't allowed in some parts of it
See
It's special only to visit the small part of it
Okay that's the end of my introductory to look and now you can wander around on your own for Coronavirus
We'll meet back here at 12:30
Before you go a bit of advice
This is an enormous Museum packed full of fascinating things and you can't expect to see it
So if I were you I'd concentrate on one or two sections and look at them in detail
Have a look at the map evolve got one and it's very simple and clear and decide where you want to go
And split up into couples or small groups
It gets pretty crowded here and you won't have much fun if a lot of you try to stick together
Okay that's the end of my introductory tool and now you can wander around on your own for Coronavirus
We'll meet back here at 12:30
Before you go a bit of advice
This is an enormous Museum packed full of fascinating things and you can't expect to see it
So if I were you I'd concentrate on one or two sections and look at them in detail
Have a look at the map you've all got one and it's very simple and clear and decide where you want to go
Split up into couples or small groups
It gets pretty crowded here and you won't have much fun if a lot of you try to stick together
That is the end of part 1