Question 74 through 76 refer to the following news report
With new warnings that Hawaii's Kilauea volcano could start to shoot out rocks the size of cars
Many tourists are rethinking their plans to vacation on the big island but just how serious a threat
Is this we spoke to experts from the National Geological Survey they tell us that while you should say
Stay away from zones where volcanic activity is happening and although some people have lost their home
Most of the island is unaffected
Local tourism officials hope Taurus will go ahead with their travel plans and enjoy some of the great Hospital
Quality that Hawaii is known for
Number 74
What is this report mainly about
Number 75 what is true about current conditions on the big island
Number 76
Which best represents the attitude of Hawaiian tourism officials