Questions 83 through 85 refer to the following talk
I'm Bob hole from trans signed I'd like to introduce our extensive range of safety signs 21 employee
If you are the owner of a business Warehouse facility
Manage one of these make sure that you always follow government regulations and purchase the correct safety sign
If you don't you could be fine thousand and even hundreds of thousands of dollars for the violation
All about signs are compliant with the sizing terminology and colors required by the occupation and safe
Safety health administration
We also sell custom signed and can run workshops on the proper precautions that employees should take to avoid
Avoid injuries for you to look at
Number 83
What is the purpose of the men's talk
Number 84
Who would be interested in this talk
Number 85
According to the speaker why are signs essential