Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following excerpt from a lecture
This lecture series is designed to give you enough information to decide whether or not this is a
The field you would like to enter in your future Korea
At the end of the class last year we had several students get jobs with some major finance companies
You are going to learn some basic background knowledge about the financial markets and become familiar with fine
Financial terminology that you may not have had before you also going to solidify your methanol
And learn new content
The prerequisite for this program is my 33a so if you have not taken that fuss or LaCroix
Another school you will not be able to take this series
Number 80
Who is the audience for this lecture
Number 81
Which is not something that will be taught in this lecture series
Number 82 what does the speaker mean when he says that there is a prerequisite for the sea