Question 77 through 79 refer to the following announcement
Please make your way to your seats the show will be starting in 5 minutes once they're show as starter
You will not be allowed to enter when you take your seat you are kindly asked to turn off all cell phones
Ringtones and vibrations are distracting to the performers I don't feel like to take this opportunity
To remind you that flash photography is not allowed in the auditorium and recordings up any
Kind are strictly prohibited thank you for your compliance please enjoy the show
Number 77
Where is this announcement taking place
Number 78
Why are guests asked to turn off their phones
Number 79
What are guests not permitted to do