Part 4
Directions
You will hear some talks given by a single speaker
You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speaker says in each talk
Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A B C or D
Dion your answer sheet
The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time
Question 71 through 73 refer to the following announcement
Good morning I like about them old gas to baldy 10-15 from London King's cross to Edinborough
We will be stopping at Grantham Doncaster you old Durham and you cancel
And then it will be nonstop to Edinburgh Waverley station I like to apologize roundelay departure this more
Unfortunately there was a signal failure and for safety reasons we were unable to leave until this would be
Rectified we will be arriving at 8 stop approximately 15 minutes behind schedule the food battle
Is located at the rear of the train and will be serving hot and cold meals and snacks as soon as we leave London
Please enjoy your ride and thank you for choosing care rail
Number 71 where is this announcement taking place
Number 72
Why does the speaker apologise to passengers
Number 73 where will passengers be able to purchase refreshments