Part 1
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
You hear people talking in eight different situations
The questions 128
Choose the best answer a
B o c
Listen to this conversation and opticians
What does the man need his glasses for
Reading
Be
Driving
Sea urchin TV
Okay so tell me when you're driving and you start to read something for example the map was
Directions would you need to take your clothes off
They hurt my eyes if I'll try to focus close up with them on
I wear them only when I think it would be dangerous not to wear them in the car you know
Okay so tell me when you're driving and you start to read something for example the map with
Directions would you need to take your glasses off
They hurt my eyes if I'll try to focus close up with them on TV
I wear them only when I think it would be dangerous not to wear them in the car you know
You will hear a woman talking to a group of people
Where are they
A museum
Be a historic house
See a Botanic Garden
Many famous artists
Landscapes to ceiling with done by Monday knee in the early 1700s
Which is the details such as these Exquisite flowers and how The Rustic Furniture fits in with landscape
Garden theme
Many famous artists as you'll see as we move along these wonderful
Landscapes in the early 1700s
Which is the details such as these Exquisite flowers and how The Rustic Furniture landscape
Gordon theme
You will hear a conversation between a woman and her doctor
Who does he advise her to see
A psychologist
Be a heart specialist
See an optician
When it snows this doctor has been having headaches and always been seeing things again
What do you mean mrs. Messi
And my heart beats too quickly I just know there's something wrong
How do you change your glasses recently when a long time years or more
In any case we'll have to give you a Honda Quick Check and do your blood pressure as well
When it snows this doctor has been having headaches and always been seeing things again
What do you mean mrs. Murphy
Giving me mad and my heart beats too quickly I just know there's something wrong
Have you changed your glasses recently a long time years or more
In any case we'll have to give you a heart attack Quick Check and blood pressure
Listen to this man talking about healthy eating
What does he suggest
Hey he's a large breakfast
Eat a large lunch
See he's a large dinner
I don't know you young people never seem to be properly these days a cup of coffee in the morning sandwich
Then you'll beat me in the evening it's just not right your poor buddies can't cope
Trying to digest the food you've just eaten what's a waste of energy
We were always told breakfast like a king that way it sets you up for the rest of the day and start you off right
I don't know you young people never seem to be properly these days a cup of coffee in the morning sandwich
Lunch and then you'll beat me in the evening it's just not right your poor buddies can't cope
Have to work all night trying to digest the food you've just eaten what a waste of energy
We were always told breakfast like a king that we had set you up for the rest of the day and start you off right
Listen to this girl talking about a holiday
Where was she left behind
Hey
France
B Italy
C-SPAN
Exhausted and hungry and with no idea of what to expect when we reach Madrid
Wholesale my rucksack in Rome Central Station just remembering the fabulous views and Italian Lakes
French chateau
Exhausted and hungry and with no idea of what to expect when we reach Madrid
Central Station just remembering the fabulous views in the Italian Lakes
French Chateau anyway
Rainsoft
Sex
You hear this weather forecast on the radio
Which parts of England will have the heaviest rainfall
London
Be
Western and Central
See
Northern
Antigo tomorrow
Gradually increasing Cardinals and rain later in the day or forecast for London temperature
Will range from 11 degrees Celsius to 22 degrees Celsius be rain in the northwest
Quickly spread to the rest of the country
Adobe strong winds over most of Mainland Britain
Anna for tomorrow
Gradually increasing Cardinals and rain later in the day are forecast for London temperature
Will range from 11 degrees Celsius to 22 degrees Celsius
Quickly spread to the rest of the country
Adobe strong winds over most of Mainland Britain
Listen to this answer phone message in the Lost Property office
What do you need to do if you have lost some money
Cool in at the office
Be
Contact the police to make a statement
See
Contact your insurance company
Hello this is the Lost Property office there's no one here to take your coolant present
Please listen carefully to the following message if you've lost something
If you've lost valuables such as jewelry cash or credit cards you need to contact
Nearest police station as soon as possible to make a statement for any other items
Please coordinate our office opening times on 925 Monday to Friday
Thank you
Hello this is the Lost Property office there's no one here to take your coolant present
Please listen carefully to the following message if you've lost something
If you've lost valuables such as jewelry cash credit cards you need to contact
Nearest police station as soon as possible to make a statement for any other items
Please coordinate our office opening times on 925 Monday to Friday
Thank you
Listen to the following conversation
Where is the woman
Hey
In a film processing shop
Be
In a Bookshop
See in a photocopy shop
Good morning
I'd like to have these please in color or black and white
You realize, expensive. That's fine
Did you do it
Good morning
I'd like to have these please
Of course you do realize Cutters Motz penciptaan yeah that's fine
Did you do it
That's the end of part 1
Melton 2:02