Welcome to office fixers
The show where we helped office manages to improve their effectiveness in the wood place
Today we go to Oakland where Johannes maker is managing a call center
Nicole Santa contacts people at home to survey them about various consumer habits
We spent five days in this workplace eight hours a day and the main problem we found
Found was this
Miss Jamaica is too lenient and easygoing
He is not able to make his employees change their behavior
And it is difficult for him to tell the South what to do
Let's go to clip 1
Will we see mr. make at allowing an employee to leave the office early although the employee
Has not finished his work for the day
What is the main theme of this TV show
What kind of office is being focused on today
What is mr. makers problem
Ladies and gentlemen Welcome to our awards banquet I hope you all enjoy
Dinner and now that dessert is being served its time for the speeches and awards
You may not be looking forward to this part of the evening assuming it will be boring
But let me tell you we've got some great speakers lined up this year and I just know
That all of you will enjoy listening to our speakers our most valued employee
First put your hands together for CEO Leo Duchene presenting the
Award for best team player
Where is the speaker
What is being given to all the guests now
What does the audience expect from the speeches
Welcome to the Modern Art Museum folks and before we step inside there are a couple of
Rules I need to go over with you
First please make sure that all cell phones are turned off or set to vibrate
Using your cell phone he's not allowed inside the building as the conversations will distract other
The people from enjoying the yacht
Also on that same night please use low voices when speaking to each other
Again this ensures a pleasant experience for your fellow art enthusiasts
Lastly photography is strictly prohibited inside the museum
If you are caught trying to take any pictures you'll camera will be confiscated and returned to you at the end
And if you'll visit
I hope you enjoy your visit
What is not allowed inside the museum
Why is loud noise discouraged
What will staff do is they take your camera
This is Janice product reviewer for your products.com
Today I'll discuss the new headset with microphone designs the busy office
Receptionist the game is at home
The biggest Advantage I think is the comfort
The headset is lightweight and does not put a lot of pressure on your ears
The sound quality is very good short and clear
However that is one big disadvantage
I found the microphone was very pool
I tested the headset with five different people using five different computers as well
And everyone I spoke to had trouble hearing me
That fool I give this headset no stars and do not recommend that anyone purchased
Thank you for listening to the your products. Calm podcast
What is Janice's job
What is the biggest advantage of the headset
What is the problem with this product
Attention all passengers if you are traveling internationally there are some new
New rules that must be followed in order to enter the terminal please take off all shoes
Shoes when you get in line but you can leave your socks on
Please shoes and any coats or jackets on one tray also
Remember to take off anything containing metal such as jewelry in belts and place that
In a separate tray
Lastly all liquids including bottled water must be less than 100
ML and be placed in individual plastic bags
Thank you for your patience and enjoy your flight
Who should listen to this announcement
What can passengers leave on
Where should liquids be placed