Test for
This is the Cambridge English first four schools listening test
I'm going to give you the instructions for this test
I'll introduce each part of the test and give you time to look at the questions
Are the stars of each piece you will hear this sound
You'll hear each piece twice
Remember why you listening write your answers on the question paper
You'll have five minutes at the end of the test to copia Lance's onto the separate answer sheet
It will now be opposed
Please ask any questions now because you must not speak during the test
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
Part 1
You'll hear people talking and H different situations
The questions 128
Choose the best answer
Boc
You hear two friends talking
Which sport should I watching on TV
Hey
Be
Tennis
Football
Wow what's a great short he's such a talented player
I saw him playing tennis at the charity tournament the other day
I didn't know he played that to to me he's just a great football player imagine him doing anything else
Well I know you didn't lock the sport he plays golf when he's on holiday and he's pretty good at that apparently
I wish I could be good at everything too
Wow
What's a great shot he's such a talented player is great isn't he
I'm playing tennis at a charity tournament the other day
Really
I didn't know he played that to to me he's just a great football player imagine him doing anything else
Well I know you couldn't lots of sport he plays golf when he's on holiday and he's pretty good at that's apparently
I wish I could be good at everything too
You hear mine talkin about a day out
Who is the speaker
Hey
A teacher
Be
Policeman
See
America
It was great fun and of course all the kids off me loads of questions pit was great that they was so interested
Everything I suppose that's what the film stars feel like they must get used to all the attention I can't tonight
Them to make sure everybody behaves well and nobody got hurt we have loads of material now
Project and it will make my lessons more interesting I hope there's a good photograph of a school outside
Police station
It was great fun and of course all the kids off me loads of questions it was great that they was so interested
Didn't everything I suppose that's what the film stars feel like they must get used to all the attention I can't
Denying them to make sure everybody behaves well and nobody got hurt we have loads of material
Well now from next project and it will make my lessons more interesting I hope I could photograph of a school outside
By the old police station
Free
You here we go talking about a documentary she's just seen
What was the documentary about
Hey
A lake
Be
Plants
Animals
I think he'd have enjoyed it it was amazing to see how quickly they Groove from tiny little things
Sipping told enough to reach the lowest branches and eat the leaves it's amazing how close the crew can get
I have a feeling the baby without frightening them sometime the camera might have to hide out in a tree
He has to get the right shower it's such a good series you should watch the one next week it's about
How to make changes throughout the year
I think you'd have enjoyed it it was amazing to see how quickly they Groove from tiny little things
Being told enough to reach the lowest branches and eat the leaves it's amazing how close the crew can get
And how they film the baby without frightening them sometimes the camera might have to hide up in a tree
To get the right shower it's such a good series you should watch the one next week it's about 2
About changes throughout the year
You hear a boy talking about his day at school
How does he feel now
Excited
Be
Relieved
See
Disappointed
You know what it's like on the first day back after the summer holidays
You don't know who your new teachers does a new timetable all that quite stressful
But it was quite exciting going in this morning and seeing everybody again
I was sorry not to be in the same group The Masters lost you but I'm sure I'll get used to it
Anyway on much more relaxed now because I know what I'm doing and I think this year will be okay
You know what it's like on the first day back after the summer holidays
You don't know who your new teachers does a new timetable all that quite stressful
But it was quite exciting going in this morning and seeing everybody again
In the same group The Masters lost you but I'm sure I'll get used to it
Anyway on much more relaxed now because I know what I'm doing and I think this year will be okay
You hear a brother and sister talking about the music at a party
What did they agree about
Hey
How good it was
Be
Unusual it was
See
How loud it was
Well did you enjoy the Posse
Did the music I'm not sure about that I thought it was a bit loud at times actually
Did you like what you had
I did and it wasn't the usual standard party music was it I didn't think it was particularly different from the
The usual stuff but I enjoy don't think so it anyway
Well you should try it sometime instead of just standing around chatting with you mate
Well did you enjoy the Posse
Hear the music I'm not sure about that I thought it was a bit too loud at times actually
Did you like what you had
I didn't think it was particularly different from the usual stuff but I enjoyed don't think so it anyway
Who is do whatever that playing well you should try it sometime instead of just standing around chatting
Volume eight
Shakes
You hear Adele talking to her father
What is she doing
Hey
Telling her father how to do something
Be
Promising her father something
See
Persuading her father to do something
Why don't you go now then you have more chance of getting good tickets the Q will be really lonely
I just don't want to be fine if we can go in half an hour or so
I know you'll be disappointed if you don't get any tickets it one of your favorite bands and what about your friends you play
Promise them you get some for them too I want to but that's why I need a lift there
I'll get that quicker you know I'm busy today why don't you cycle that it's raining
Why don't you go now then you have more chance of getting good tickets the Q will be really long legs
I just don't want to be fine if we can go in half an hour or so
I know you'll be disappointed if you don't get any tickets at one of your favorite bands and what about your friends you
Promise them you get some for them too I want to but that's why I need a lift there
I'll get that quicker you know I'm busy today why don't you cycle Dad it's raining
You hear a woman talking about a cat
When was the cat
On the pavement
Be
Under a bench
See
In a tree
It was a beautiful white cat I haven't seen it round table for I was sitting on a bench reading
My book and I looked up on the couch was sitting them under a little tree just looking at me
People kept on passing as the Penguins quite narrow that but the cat didn't move what tools they
They just have to walk around it
I think it likes the sunny supposed to sit found I was a bit worried that it might run into the road
But it didn't maybe it's still there
It was a beautiful white cat I haven't seen it round table for I was sitting on a bench reading
My book and I looked up on the cats was sitting them under a little tree just looking at me
People kept on passing us is quite narrow that but the cat didn't move what tools they
Just have to walk around it
I think it likes to Sony's focus and found I was a bit worried that it might run into the road
But it didn't
Maybe it's still there
You hear two friends talking about the website
What is the girl think about it
Is useful
She's entertaining
It is always up-to-date
Yes a good website I used it to get information for my jog Rafi presentation last week
I've never actually found anything I could use on it besides off and check it went on a bit bold
I do too I like reading a funny articles on some of the pictures ready make me laugh
It's not much good for news though I go to other sites if I want to find out what's going on
So do I still one of my favorites
Yes a good website I used it to get information for my jog Rafi presentation last week
I've never actually found anything I could use on it besides off and check it went on a bit
I do too I like reading a funny articles on some of the pictures ready make me laugh
It's not much good for news though I go to other sites if I want to find out what's going on
So do I still one of my favorites
That's the end part 1
No time to part 2