Question
You turn on the television and hear a man giving a lecture
The man teaches
Hey
Geography
Be
Tourism
See
History
Franco-german enmity had a long tradition before the first World War
It's Beginning can be conveniently dated to some 40 years earlier to 11th of May 18th
On that day in the Swan Hotel at Frankfurt on Main
Otto von Bismarck the German Chancellor sign the treaty which awarded all about science
Lorraine to Germany
To the French including those in Alsace and Lorraine
It was a loss and humiliation which day would never come to accept
Franco-german enmity had a long tradition before the first World War
It's beginning to be conveniently dated some forty years earlier to 11th of May 18th
On that day in the Swan Hotel at Frankfurt on Main
Austin Von Bismarck the German Chancellor
Signed the treaty which awarded all about fast and most of Lorraine to Germany
To the French including those in alsace-lorraine
It was a loss and humiliation
Which day would never come to accept
You hear the following on the radio
It is advertising
Hey a breakdown service
B Agera R
Speedy Car Insurance
Breaking down can be a nightmare
Expensive to the rsc's low-cost you can have help a charity from as little as 20
9 lb per year
Of 80% about the trolls arrive within an hour of your cool
85% of repairs are made on the spot
Postal local garages are free
How late is free to you pay only for the pots
Coolest on 0800 492 2673
Breaking down can be a nightmare
Send it to
Yes with start the RAC low-cost service you can have health and security from as little as 29 lb per year
Of 80% about the shoals arrived within an hour of your cool
85% of repairs are made on the spot free
How late is free to you pay only for the pots
Courtesan 0800 492 2673
Question three
Listen to this country
You are listening to
A swimming race
Be a horse race
See a car wreck
And as I speak Point even hits the front half a mile from home by Martin Stephen on turnip Trump and in the blue
Blue and purple colors peterlin lunch and they're coming up to the second last princes point of a the two lanes ahead of Turner
She's up and walking it's easy to
Pier One of the field now and it's between these two and Father Christmas is now the third play for 10 minutes behind the leaders
And as I speak Point even hits the front half a mile from home he's followed by Martin Stephen on turnip Trump and in the blue
Blue and purple colors peterlin on spandy Dad are coming up to the second offense and find out what the years ahead of turnip
He's up and walking
Clearwater the field now and it's between these two and Father Christmas is now the third play for TurboTax behind leaders
Question for
Listen to this telephone conversation
The speaker work for a
A Building Company
Erestaurant
A hotel
Good morning
A double with the bathroom en-suite
Yes the price includes breakfast which can be taken in our restaurant over in your room we offer either traditional
English practice or Continental one
Bethany said I'll fax them up to you straightaway and we look forward to seeing you tonight
Good morning how about you
A double with the bathroom en-suite
Yes the price includes breakfast which can be taken in our restaurant over in your room we offer either to this note
English practice or Continental one
Fashionista I'll fax them up to you straightaway and we look forward to seeing you tonight
Question 5
The following announcement
The speaker is giving information about
Hey trains
B buses
Seaplanes
Outstanding a platform one is the delayed 6:45 sporty calling at Bristol Parkway
You pulled Todd Bridges portable Nathan's clumsy
Cotton gin change at Bristol
Packages for the body lying to change Tardis arriving at platform 3 it's the 732
Green tightly and Birmingham Moor Street
The service did not stop at New Hill
Passengers wishing to travel to Snow Hill across the bridge to platform for
Now standing in Platform One is delayed 645fd coordinates Bristol talk
Newport Bridge and portable nice and fun day
Cottages for Cheltenham in Worcester change at Bristol
Passengers for the body line change product
Arriving at that poetry is the 732
Leslie and Birmingham Moor Street
The service did not stop at Snow Hill
Passengers wishing to travel to Snow Hill across the bridge to platform for
Question stick
You overhear this conversation in golf
Mrs. fig is buying
Hey
Cotton wool
Be
Route
Speed horse feed
Expandable ranges that 66p
I want some apples to
Golden Delicious
Granny Smith movie time that's 17
What about a pineapple
Because some Beauties in today
I think I have everything I need until the weekend
Find that'll be 17 thanks very much and 13-page range
Dependable ranges that 66p
I want some apples to
Granny Smith will be fine that's 1 lb 87
What about a pineapple we go some Beauties in today
I think I have everything I need until the weekend
Find that'll be one pan at you 7 thanks very much and 13 pay change
Question 7
You overhear this Exchange in a restaurant
The man is talking to the woman about
A job they've just completed
Be a business proposition
Be buying a house
The work is well within our range and abilities
Does a profit of 1000000 pounds and it Forest it looks too good to miss
I'm not sure
I thought it looked pretty clear
It just doesn't feel right
What exactly doesn't feel right
Being pounds pills hold on to me I know the profit margin is high
It's not the money
Am I fat
Please stop spilling Family Nutrition forever
Sophie
The work is well within our range and ability
Is a profit of 1000000 pounds and it Forest it looks too good to miss
What you think
I'm not sure
Pretty clear
It just doesn't feel right
What exactly doesn't feel rise
Being pounds feels hold onto me I know the profit margin is high
Repeat the best in the business it's not the money
I'd like that too
Quick Cut's feeling Family Nutrition forever
I can't put my finger on it it just doesn't feel right
Question 8
Listen to this teacher in class
What subject is being taught
Hey
Football
Arabic
See
English
Anyways you don't understand yes there just one
Arsenal very interesting
Apart from the football team football team
Duh duh means the house in Santa Ana
Can anyone guess the meaning now
Anyways you don't understand yes sir just one very interesting
Anybody else know what that means
Apart from the football team football team
Antenna
Duh means the House and Senate in this case exploded
Put the two together ad
Can anyone guess the meaning now