Questions 14 through 17 listen to a conversation between a student and a coach
Mass are you going to be trying out for the basketball team this year
I'm not sure yet Coach my parents don't particularly want me to play ball this year though
Once you were one of the first players Off the Bench last year
You did a good job last year and I'm counting on you to be a starter this season
Thanks for saying that coach
So you're going to try out then right
We need as many quality players as possible if we want to have a winning season
I'll tell my parents what you said and then I'll try to convince them that they should let me play on the team
That's good to hear
Thanks
If you don't mind my asking why don't your parents want you to play
If I remember correctly they both attended every game last year
A lot of parents don't support their children like that many don't even bother attending a single game
They support me in everything I do they're good like that
Then what's the problem I don't get it
My grades in the first quarter what is good as they had expected them to be
I got a couple of low grades in in math and science so my parents want me to do
Dedicate myself more to my studies
That's why they're not too keen on letting me join the team
Bye Siri
Well not you study harder and get those grades up and I'm sure your parents will see fit to let you play on my team
Yes sir I'll do my best
Now answer the questions
Number 14 what are the speaker's mainly discussing