Questions 18 through 22
Listen to a conversation between a student and a teacher
Mr. Gibson are you busy right now
Just grading these history test Monday
Oh so then should I come back to speak with you sometime later
Oh no sorry I didn't mean that I was just
Sorry
I get spaced out sometimes when I'm grading papers
Please come into my office and grab a seat
Thanks mr. Gibson
What do you want to talk about Mindy
It's the research paper we have to do
What about it
I've never written a long paper before
You told us that it has to be 20 pages long
And we need to have a bibliography so that we can cite all of our sources
To be honest I've never done any of this before so I don't have a
Clue as to what I should be doing
I Siri okay
For a research paper you need to get your information from several different sources
I hope your use at least five sources
But I would prefer that you use more
Resources can be books magazine articles information from websites and so on
Okay
What about the bibliography and footnotes
Every time you use information from another source in your paper
You need to make a footnote
This provides information about the work from which you got your information
At the end of the paper you should write a bibliography
Simply put it's a list of the sources that you used to write your paper
If you look at that big handout I gave you yesterday you'll see how to make both footnotes and a bibliography
So does that help
A lot
Thanks for clearing that up
If I have any more questions while I'm writing my paper can I come back here and ask you
Of course you can that's what I'm here for to help you learn
Now answer the questions
Number 18
What is the teacher explaining