Questions 23 through 26
Listen to a conversation between two students
George have you figured out your schedule for next semester yet
There's not too much just think about is there
What do you mean by that
I mean that we don't even have a choice for several of our classes
Let's see we're required to take English we have to take History 2
And we have to enroll in PE as well
Oh yeah I see your point but what about math
What about it
I'm taking geometry next year
That's what you're going to be taking as well isn't it
That's right
And I'm taking Spanish 3 next semester
Not me so I guess our schedules will be different there I'm taking French 3 instead
I wish I had taken Spanish but it's too late for me to change now
Are you going to take biology or physics
Definitely physics I don't enjoy biology plus I love math and physics has a good deal of me
Math unit
That's the same reason I'm going to take physics as well
So there really isn't that much for us to decide on is there
Wait we have to take one more class
We can choose from art music computer science and economics
I can't make up my mind between music and economics
I'm leaning toward economics but I really enjoyed taking classes with Ms Jenkins the music teacher
She is a lot of fun isn't she
But as for me I'm going to sign up for the computer science class
That's what I'm hoping to major in when I go to college
No answer the questions
Number 23
What are the students mainly discussing