Questions 33 through 37
Listen to part of a radio broadcast
We're back from our commercial break and we're talking with gemologist Sandy Wellman
Professor Wellman teaches geology at the local College
And she has agreed to spend some time talking to us this evening
Before our last break we discussed the local geology
One thing that Professor Wellman mentioned intrigue
She said there used to be volcanic activity in this area
So Professor Wellman
Does that mean there might be diamonds in our area
If there are please let me know where so I can start digging for them
Peter there may well be lots of diamonds in this region
Would you like for me to explain why please go ahead
I'm sure our listeners would love to hear this thanks
You see diamonds are simply carbon
They're formed deep within the Earth
Basically the combination of extreme heat and pressure under the Earth
Surface
Takes a lump of carbon
Like coal and transforms it into a diamond
What's the connection between diamonds and volcanoes
Well as I said
Diamonds are formed deep underground
But we often find them near the surface
How does that happen
Most of the time
It happens due to volcanoes
Essentially
Volcanic activity forces diamonds to the surface
Aura at least close to it
For that reason the majority of diamonds are discovered near places
That were either volcanically active in the past
Or have active volcanoes
And we live in an area that once had active volcanoes right that's correct
But the last volcanic eruption here
Happened millions of years ago
So we don't need to worry about any eruptions at all
That's a relief
So if I understand you correctly
You're saying that all I need to do is go to the site of an extinct volcano and start digging
And then I'll be able to find some diamonds
Oh I am definitely not saying that Peter
Well some diamonds have been found in this area
It's not as simple as grabbing a shovel in digging them up
If it were I'd already be rich
Let me tell you what you need to do if you really want to find some diamonds
Now answer the questions
Number 33
What are the speakers mainly discussing