Questions 26 through 29
Listen to part of the discussion in a science class
We get most of our energy from fossil fuels such as coal oil and natural gas
We'll use these fossil fuels to run machines to operate Cars airplanes and other vehicles
To heat our homes and to make electricity
Unfortunately
Fossil fuels won't last forever
Once we use them they're gone
No one is really sure how big our supply of fossil fuels is
We may have enough to last for a few decades
Or we might have a supply that will last for several centuries
Anyway since they are non-renewable resources
We need to use them sparingly
We also need to come up with ways to save energy
So that we can make our supplies last longer
So any ideas
I think the best way to save energy is not to use it
You're going to have to explain that a little more clearly Stephanie
Are you suggesting that we not use any energy at all
No I'm not
I think I stated my idea poorly
I mean that we can do things like walk or ride bikes
Instead of driving cars
By acting that way we can save gas
Yes that makes sense
Chris
Since it gets pretty cold here in winter
We use lots of energy to heat our homes then
But
If more people use wood to heat their homes
Then we could save electricity
My family always has a fire going in the fireplace during winter
It keeps our home warm
And doesn't waste any electricity
That's one possible solution Chris
But think about this
Imagine how many people there are in our city
Now what would happen if all of them started burning wood during winter
Yeah
Pretty soon there wouldn't be any trees left for miles
C-Class this is a problem we face
We try to solve one problem but the solutions we come up with can often lead to other ones
Well one option is to use more alternative energy sources
These include solar wind water geothermal and nuclear power
However
Each of these types of energy has its own problems
Let's focus on solar power first
What are its benefits and what are its eggs
Eric your hand is up
Now answer the questions
Number 26
What is the main topic of the discussion