Questions 30 through 32
Listen to part of a talk in a social studies class
I'm sure most of you can tell me what a desert is
It's a really hot place that gets a small amount of water each year
That's right isn't it
Okay
I see lots of heads nodding
But let me tell you something
That definition I just gave you is wrong
Let me give you the correct definition of a desert right now
It's a place that receives very little precipitation each year
Notice what I left off
I omitted the hot part
You see the reason is that there are two main types of deserts
Hot deserts and cold deserts
Hot deserts are the ones that most people normally think about
They are for example the Sahara Desert and the Arabian Desert
The temperatures they're frequently get to be more than 40 degrees Celsius
There are however cold deserts as well
The Gobi desert in Mongolia and China is one example
So is Antarctica
Yes that's right despite the cold weather in Antarctica there is very little snowfall on
Most of the continent
We can also classify deserts according to how much rainfall they received
We call them extremely arid
Arid and semi-arid desert
Arid as I am sure you can guess by now means dry
Extremely arid deserts received virtually no rainfall each year
The Atacama Desert of Chile is one of these
In some parts of that desert it hasn't rained in more than 400 years
Incredible Hulk
As for arid deserts they receive fewer than 250 mm of rainfall each year
Most of the world's deserts fall into this category
Semi-arid desert receive between 250 and 500 mm of rain
People annually
That's enough for short grasses and small plants to grow
Now answer the questions
Number 30
What is the main topic of the talk