Now you will hear longer talks or conversations
Each talk or conversation will be followed by three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question
And mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between two students
I'm really glad that I decided to join the school band this year
So am I this is my third year in the band and I must say it's the best one of all
I think the fact that we have a new band director is great
Mr. Conaway is much better than Mister Jesse ever was
I can't comment on that since I never got a chance to meet Mister Jesse
But it sounds like every band member who knew both of them agrees with you
Trust me mr. Conway is a huge Improvement
He's a talented conductor
And he's also an excellent teacher
I feel that I've improved a lot as a flutist this past year
Yeah
I think mr. Conaway is definitely a good teacher
He has taught me a few things about the trumpet that I never knew
And I've been playing it for
At least 6 years now
Batmom huh
Anyway
Are you ready for the spring concert we're putting on next week
I think so I've learned most of the songs we're going to play
There are still a couple of pieces that are giving me problems though
I'm pretty much the same as you but I'm getting more comfortable with the difficult pieces
I don't anticipate having any problems by the time we hold the concert
I hope we don't have any everyone in my family is planning to be there
So I'd hate to put on a poor performance in front of them
That would be bad wouldn't it
Well we better get to bed practice now
Hopefully we can work out our problems today
You said it
Let's get going
Now answer the questions
Number 10
Why does the girl mentioned mr. Jesse