Practice test free
The listening section has 42 questions follow along as you listen to the directions to the listening
Section
Directions
In this section of the test you will hear talks and conversations he's talk or conversation is fall
Followed by one question
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Here is an example listen to a conversation between two friends in the classroom
Mr. Davidson gives us too much homework nearly every night I know what you mean
He forgets that we have assignments and other classes to
What are the speakers talking about
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is a their homework in a class
Here is another example listen to a conversation between two friends at school
I love how the new cafeteria looks it's so big and has lots of tables
You're right and the food is so much better than what we used to get served
What does the girl say about the new cafeteria
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is D it has better food
Go on to the next page and the test will begin with question number one
Number one listened to a conversation between two friends
Rick did you see the coach young posted a list of all the players who made the basketball team
No way Alan did we make it
We sure did we're both on the varsity team and practice starts at 3:30 today
Isn't that awesome Clark didn't make it though he's going to be on the junior varsity team
That's too bad for him
What are the students going to do in the afternoon