Now you will hear longer talks or conversations each talk or conversation will be followed by
Three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between two students
April I need to talk to you for a moment
Sure Tom what is it
I heard you're interested in joining the school newspaper as a reporter
Is that true
Do you want to be a member of the staff
Sure I'd love to do that my sister is a reporter for the local paper and
She tells me all kinds of stories about her job it sounds fun so I want to try
Hyatt
You know I'm the editor of the paper right
Yes I'm aware is that that means you have the power to give me a job doesn't it
It sure does
And to be honest we need some reporters
Susan was a member of the staff until three days ago
But she had to quit for some reason
Ever since she quit
I've been looking for someone to replace her
I'd like to give it a shot
Great I know you can write because I've seen your work before you have
When did you do that
Remember a couple of years ago when we had to do that group project in English class
You and I were in the same group
And I read the paper that you wrote
Wow I can't believe you remember it
It seems like that happened so long ago
Anyway
What do you want me to do for my first assignment
Do you want me to interview the new social studies teacher
No
Don't worry about that I've already assigned that duty to Jim
Instead
I want you to cover tonight's football game
It starts at 7:30 and it should last for a couple of hours
See if you can get some interviews after the game
Especially if we win
No problem I look forward to doing that
Now answer the questions
Number 10
What is the Boys Roll on the student newspaper