Practice Test 2
The listening section has 42 questions follow along as you listen to the directions to the
The listening section
Directions
In this section of the test you will hear talks and conversations each talk or conversation
He's followed by one question choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the
Correct answer on your answer sheet you will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Here is an example
Listen to a conversation between two friends in the classroom
Aren't you going to band practice now it's our first meeting of the year
Banda pass this year
What does the girl mean
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is B she is not going to be a member of the band
Here is another example
Listen to a conversation between two friends at school
I can't wait for spring break to come I could really use some time off
Agree with you I'm looking forward to not having class for a week as well
What are the speakers talking about
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is C spring break
Go on to the next page and the test will begin with question number one
Number one
Listen to a conversation between two friends
You don't look happy clear what's the matter I left my new smartphone on the bus
Today my parents are going to be upset when they find out what I did
Didn't they just give you that phone 3 days ago that's why they're not going to
To be pleased when I talk to them
What happened to the girls smartphone