Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following announcement and schedule
Attention please
The train now arriving at platform for is the 820 North coast train toucans
The train will be stopping at number Rockhampton Townsville intimidating it can please
Boots that due to an incident that Mekhi station the train will not be stopping in Makai and will arrive in both
Townsville and Ken's 10 minutes earlier than usual
Passengers wishing to travel to McKay should wait here at Brisbane station for further information about when
The station is expected to reopen please down behind the other lines on the platform as the train approached
In addition to today's wet-weather the platforms and train floors are slippery
Please mind your step while getting on and off the trains
Number 98
Who will not be able to complete their schedule Journey
Number 99 why are passengers warned to be careful
Number 100
Look at the graphic due to problems in McKay what time is the train now expected to
To arrive in Cairns
This is the end of the listening test
Turn 2 part 5 in your test book