Questions 89 through 91 refer to the following talk
We the members of the state Nurses Association do not accept the terms of the contracts offered
By the hospital the members of this Union demanded a 6% annual pay increase for each of the
The next three years not the one-time increase of 3% on offer we reject an increase in the
Cost of our health insurance premiums we are calling a three-day strike until our demands are met
Although we are sorry not to be able to care for the patients we love we will not back down until
Our employer truly recognizes R-value State Nurses Association demands Fair pay now
Number 89
What is the purpose of this talk
Number 90
What is the union demanding
Number 91
What does the speaker mean when he says we will not back down