Questions 86 through 88 refer to the following excerpt from a lecture
The guitar is used in almost all types of music from classical to rock the guitarist
Responsible for the melody of a song to be a good guitar player a musician needs to have Flex
Simple and strong fingers however one of the greatest guitar players in the world could only
Use two fingers of his left hand Django Reinhardt was a French Jazz guitarist in the 19
30s he was already a well-known guitar player when one day he burned his left hand
And very badly he could only use two fingers and the doctor said that he would never be
Be able to play the guitar again but instead of giving up he taught himself to play with only
Number 86
What is the talk mainly about
Number 87
What event change Django Reinhardt live
Number 88
What was unusual about Django Reinhardt
Go on to the next page