Questions 95 through 97 refer to the following talk and graphics
What do we mean by global climate change basically it refers to the change in the average climate
Over the entire planet the planet is warming up fast in fact it is warming faster than at any
The time in its entire history so why should you care well this is 100
Booming means more frequent among the periods of drought melting ice caps in the Arctic and Antarctic flooding
And extreme weather events
For example Summers I getting hotter putting the elderly and the young at risk of heat-related illnesses
Number 95
What is the talk mainly about
Number 96 according to the speaker who will be most affected by Rising temperature
Number 97
Look at the graphic which aspect is not mentioned by the speaker