Questions 92 through 94 refer to the following excerpt from a meeting and directory
I know I gave out the new staff phone directory only last week but there have been some changes since
We'll start this week's meeting by talking about those
Unfortunately Barbara Clements who has been a kostmart employee for over 10 years
Found out this week that she will need to undergo a course of medical treatment which is going to prevent her from working
Hoping she'll be able to return in a few months but no one knows yet for now we're asked
Taking Luke Graham to step in as temporary manager looking for Barbara
Barbara is a very private person but I'm sure she'd appreciate some texts and emails wishing her well
Number 92
Where is this meeting taking place
Number 93
What is true of Luke G new position
Number 94
Look at the graphic according to the speaker which department is going to see a change in manager