Question 74 through 76 refer to the following announcement
Thank you everyone I'm sure you have heard the rumors and yes it is true we all move
Moving to another building the company has grown rapidly so the new offices we are moving to off
Five times bigger than what we have right now to avoid disruption to business we are going to move
I bet I'm not in one go I would like us to provide our customers with the continuous service
We will start with the sales department on Saturday all the other departments will move between Munn
Monday and Wednesday hopefully by Friday or departments will be running even though files
Find furniture maybe all over the place good luck and thank you
Number 74
Why is the company moving to New offices
Number 75 how is the new office building different from the current building
Number 76 on what day is the sales department moving