Question 77 through 79 refer to the following talk
Today's session is all about health and safety of quick one of the most common injuries of coz when lifting
Heavy objects do not be afraid to ask for assistance if you think any object may be too heavy for you to lie
If you do listen item alone always bend your knees and keep your back straight next
If you spill a drink on the floor clean it up immediately this week three people slipped when someone spilled coffee in the hole
All white it is very lucky that nobody was seriously hurt another problem is Furniture in boxes
Do not place them in front of the fire exit
Number 77
What is the topic of this talk
Number 78
Which is not mentioned as a problem
Number 79
What can be inferred about furniture and boxes