Questions 80 through 82 refer to the following talk
Good morning I'm here to help you find your way out of unemployment start by looking at
Job advertisement and select the jobs that match your skills and education most companies will
Ask you to send a resume with a cover letter your resume must be tight and never handwritten
Keep it short the HR Personnel who will receive your resume are busy people include
Past work experience and any relevant skills and qualifications in the cover letter
Why you are a good candidate we have 12 computers here in the library feel free to use them
And just ask me if you need any help
Number 80
Who is the target audience for this talk
Number 81
What is inferred about HR personnel
Number 82
What will members of the audience probably do after this talk