Question
Listen to this news item
A man has been given an award for
Hey
Shooting a robber
Be
Visiting a little Chef Restaurant
See
Arresting a robber
Local newspaper reporter Alan Francis made the news
Robert and does not been awarded the Queen's combination for bravery is the France is so a man
A shotgun holding up customers of the Little Chef Restaurant in Putney two years ago
Define himself with the man wrestled him to the ground and even though the shotgun went off until the police arrived
The rubber Frank melon have been jailed the 80s
Local newspaper reporter Alan Francis made the news himself
Has not been awarded the Queen's combination for bravery is the Francis or man on
Do the shotgun holding up customers
Define himself with the man wrestled him to the ground and even though the shotgun went off he had lunch with until the police arrived
The rubber Frank Mellon has been jailed for a GS
Question 2
You've left your car in the car park for 40 minutes
You must pay a
50 pence
Be
Nothing
See
A pound
Remind customers that I love
There is no charge for any less than 30 minutes
That time however it will be a charge of fifty Pence up to the faster and one town to any stay longer than
In one hour thank you
Remind customers that are large
Pop out of the store there is no charge for any stay of less than 2:30
That time however it will be a charge of fifty Pence up to the faster and 1 lb Penny stay longer than one
Thank you
Question three
Listen to this conversation
It takes place in
Hey a factory
Be a garage
See a supermarket
That looks better than the last time I saw Terry
SpongeBob thought it was bound to look bad having run into the back of the bus at 40 miles an hour
Headlamp bands look better can I drive it away now I need to get the front wheels back on and check the alignment
Go back in an hour no problem I'll just do some shopping
That looks better than the last time I saw Terry
Thanks Bubba. It was bound to look bad having run into the back of the bus at 40 miles an hour
Headlamps is bound to look better can I drive it away now I need to get the front wheels back on and check the alignment
Nickelback in an hour no problem I'll just do some shopping
Question for
Listen to this conversation
Vera
Hey
We'll go out with Terry bolum
Be
Don't go out with Terry Bolin
See he's undecided
Maybe you know that terrible with him
He's asked me out to the cinema tomorrow OU look at things so good-looking when you get to go anywhere
Well it was
I don't want something like that happening to me
But it said if you don't go out with him
Baby you know that terrible with him
He's asked me out to the cinema tomorrow so good-looking when you get to go next
Well it was
I don't want something like that happening to me
What it says. If you don't go out with him
Question 5
Listen to this lecture
The lecture is about
Hey
Law
B biology
See
History
Another Factor contributing to the Industrial Revolution with the flow of people from the countryside
To the towns
Hello had been passed preventing people from keeping the animals on Cumberland
And thanks together with the absence of any form of assistance for the pool
Force country people to move to the towns to look for work
Continue the battle for survival
Another Factor contributing to the Industrial Revolution with the flow of people from the countryside
To the towns
Hello had been passed preventing people from keeping the animals on Cumberland
And thanks together with the absence of any form of assistance for the pool
Force country people to move to the towns to look for work
Continue the battle for survival
Question 6
Listen to this introduction on the radio
Show is
Hey
The news
Be
A game show
See
Attract show
And today's guest is coming long way from a humble beginnings she was
Born in 1906 in Sunderland next to the dockyard
When she was 8 have father joined up to fight in the first world war and was killed in the first back Levy
Is plantae family into the deepest poverty in order to paper clothes to go to school she would get up at 4
Coke in the morning to deliver milk before-school and after-school can a local shop until 10 at night
Peggy Mansfield that sounds like horrific Lee hard work how did you manage it
And today's guest is, long way from a humble beginnings she was
Born in 1986 in Sunderland next to the dockyard when she was eight have father joined up to fight in the first
And was killed in the Fastback Levi this plant a family into the deepest property you know
Go to the paper clothes to go to school she would get up at 4 in the morning to deliver milk before school
Adopt-a-school wax in a local shop until 10 at night Dame Peggy Mansfield that sounds like her
Terrifically hard work how did you manage it
Question 7
Listen to this announcement
Listerhill is
Hey
Dangerously ill
Be wanted by the police
See on holiday in Scotland
And now here's an SOS message mister Golden Hill Ave Braintree
In Essex will miss the Golden Hill Ave Braintree in Essex who is believed to be on a touring holiday in Scotland
Please contact maidenhead hospital all the nearest police station
Mister his mother is dangerously ill in maidenhead and the hospital would like him to get in touch with them as soon as possible
The telephone number is
04/12 6409 867
I'll repeat that
The telephone number of maidenhead hospital is
Opal 126
409 867
Irregular 6 program
And now here's an SOS message mister Golden Hill Ave Braintree in
Golden Health Braintree in Essex who is believed to be on a touring holiday in Scotland please
Please contact maidenhead hospital all the nearest police station
Vista Hills mother is dangerously ill in maidenhead and the hospital would like him to get in touch with them as soon as possible
The telephone number is 04126
409 867
Repeat that
The telephone number of maidenhead hospital is
04/12 6409 867
A regular 6 program
Question 8
Listen to this conversation
Jim
Hey
Will buy dog food
Be
Will not buy dog food
See
Will by Sainsbury's cat food
Bread butter cheese vitamin tablets Cochise
Have a good maple syrup dog food
Goodwill if it's hungry enough
And anyway I haven't got time to go to time I need nail polish remover can you get some of that okay
But it done
Bread butter cheese vitamin tablets cheese
Have a good maple syrup dog food the dog doesn't eat Sainsbury's dog food
Will if it's hungry enough time to go into town I need nail polish remover
Can you get some of that okay I'll put it done