Test 6
This is the Cambridge English first four schools listening test
I'm going to give you the instructions for this test
I'll introduce each part of the test
I'll give you time to look at the questions
Are the stars of each piece you will hear this sound
You hear each piece twice
Remember why you listening write your answers on the question paper
You'll have five minutes at the end of the test to copia Lance's onto the separate answer sheet
They will now be opposed
Please ask any questions now because you must not speak during the test
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
Part 1
You hear people talking in eight different situations
The questions 128 choose the best answer
Boc
You overhear two friends talking about a computer game
What do they agree about
Hey
The graphics are unusually good
Be
It is more exciting than the earlier version of the game
See
The game is better than the film it is based on
What you think of Sam's new computer game you know the one based on that Space Adventure film we saw it last year
Well it's very exciting to play isn't it
Do I don't think it's as addictive as the original game I'm not sure why
The graphics of Miles better than the earlier ones.
People rather than the computer animation or no I've never seen anything like it
What you think of Sam's new computer game you know the one based on that Space Adventure film we saw it last year
It's very exciting to play isn't it
Do I don't think it's as addictive as the original game I'm not sure why
The graphics of Miles better than the earlier ones.
Rather than a computer animation I know I've never seen anything like it
You hear a radio reporter choking on a nature program
Why is he excited about what he saw
Hey
Is it unusual to see close-up film of this type of fish
Be
The fish was demonstrating unexpected skills
Film gave you information about what fish eat
Research biologist Giacomo bonati amazing film recently he was able to get
Play some pictures of an orange spotted Tusk fish digging a shellfish out of the sand and then carrying it
The top fish then repeatedly bang the creature against the rocks in an attempt to break it she'll inside
Help itself to a tasty snack will do this kind of action is basic for humans it is
Advanced thing for fish to do as it requires an element of forward-thinking
Such Behavior has previously been reported that has never before been captured on video
Research biologist Giacomo bonati amazing film recently
He was able to get close up pictures of an orange spotted Tusk fish digging a shellfish out of the Sun
I'm in carrying it over to a rock status fish then repeatedly bangs the creature against The Rock
An attempt to break its shell and so help itself to a tasty snack
Play this kind of action is basic for humans it is quite an advanced thing for fish to do
Is it requires an element of forward-thinking
Such Behavior has previously been reported that has never before been captured on video
Tri
You overhear a teacher talking to a student
What is she talking about
Hey
Something the student forgot to do
Be
Something the student must bring to school
See
Something the student did that please the teacher
I'm very grateful to you Tony for bringing those old coins into school today don't forget to take them home
You tonight as I think they could be quite valuable and they could easily go missing if you left them here and it was a real
Really helped to bring our history class to life I thought and it was very impressed that you remember to bring them along with all the
The other members of the class had said they could bring something in for Galt
I'm very grateful to you Tony for bringing those old coins into school today don't forget to take them home
Home with you tonight as I think they could be quite valuable and they could easily go missing if you left them here anyway
Really helped to bring our history class to life I thought and I was very impressed that you remember to bring them along when all
The other members of the class had said they could bring something in for Galt
You overhear two friends talking about a survey
What is the boy most surprised about
Hey
All the students lack of knowledge about trees
Be
Other students inability to play a game
See
All the students lack of enthusiasm for nature
Did you hear that news I seen this morning about a tree survey
Yes it said that 70% of city school children can't tell the difference between the note tree
And a willow tree that's right I'm almost half don't know that the calm cuz they use in the Congo game they play Come
From horse chestnut trees I'm surprised aren't you I know loads of different trees
We live in the country so I suppose it's easier for us what got me was the waymo
Whose kids seem to feel it's not important to be able to recognize trees and plants and stuff
Say we need to know as much as we can about our environment
Did you hear that news I seen this morning about a tree survey
Yes it said that 70% of city school children can't tell the difference between the note tree
And a willow tree that's right I don't talk don't know that the calm cuz they use in the conga game they played
I'm from horse chestnut trees I'm surprised aren't you I know loads of different trees
We live in the country so I suppose it's easier for us what got me was the waymo
Most kids seem to feel it's not important to be able to recognize trees and plants and stuff
Say we need to know as much as we can about our environment
You here avoid leaving a voicemail message
Who is he talking to
Hey
A teacher
Be
A store manager
School friends
Two friends from school and I had some juice in the cafe at Yellowstone Street Bronson
And I think I might have left my history textbook
If you've got it as I need it for a lesson tomorrow and a teacher will be furious if I don't have it with me
It's got my name inside. John take now my friend Anita lives next door and she's going to pop in
First thing tomorrow morning to see if it's there
Two friends from school and I had some juice in the cafe at you'll Stonestreet Bronx this afternoon and I think
I might have left my history textbook
If you've got it as I need it for a lesson tomorrow at a teacher will be furious if I don't have it with me
Inside. John take down my friend Anisa lives next door and she's going to pop in first
Tomorrow morning to see if it's there
You hear two friends talking about a holiday
Why did the girl spend her holiday in the way she did
Hey
She wanted to try something different
Be
She was Keen to on some money
See
She was persuaded to buy her brother
Did you and your brother have a good time at the media Camp it was great we could choose what we
He wanted to do he went to filmmaking and I chose poster design what moves you decide to build
Did your brother twist your arm I persuaded him I read about it in a magazine
I mean it became because he wants to make a career in the movie industry
I done but I was getting a bit fed up with always spending the summer doing the same old things so I applied to Cena
I had about it I'm not surprised it sounds fun
Did you and your brother have a good time at the media Camp it was great we could choose what we were
I wanted to do he went for filmmaking and I chose poster design what made you decide to do that
Did your brother twist your arm I persuaded him I read about it in a magazine
I need it became because he wants to make a career in the movie industry
I don't but I was getting a bit fed up with always spending the summer doing the same old things so I applied as soon as
And I had about it I'm not surprised it sounds fun
You hear a local radio story about a school project
What was the main aim of the project
Hey
To give the children experience and teamwork
Be
To teach the children about healthy living
See
To develop the children's creative skills
Children at grantley school has just published a book about how to live healthy lives
The book contains a range of articles on diets and exercise all of which the children Road
Is a dentist rated with cartoons and photographs and these World created by The Chew
Contain
The book is the end product of a project developed by grantlees head teacher with a view to encouraging
The children to learn through working together is a group you can see some pages from the book
It's on our website
Children at grantley school has just published a book about how to live healthy lives
The book contains a range of articles on diets and exercise all of which the children Road
Is Illustrated with cartoons and photographs and these World created by the children
The book is the end product of a project developed by ground please head teacher with a view to
Encouraging the children to learn through working together is a group you can see some pages from the book
I'm glad more about it on our website
Wait
You hear a boy telling his mother about a football match
How does the boy feel about his friend Ben's performance
Hey
Glad that he kept on playing despite a problem
Be
Surprised that he did not score a goal
Please that he did better than others expected
How was football today tell me good we had a mattress Twin down school on scored
Play today
He didn't score but he set up to of all goals yes everyone so today
Be quite slow as he hasn't played for a while but he wasn't too
How was football today tell me good we had a mattress Twin down school on stored
It's been pretty play today
He's likes back to normal he didn't score but he set up some of our goals as good yes
Everyone thought he'd be quite slow as he hasn't played for a while but he wasn't too
That's the end part 1
No time to part 2