Questions 92 through 94 refer to the following talk and itinerary
Welcome to New Orleans this afternoon I will be leading this free walking tour around
Find the French quarter of the city we will explore the Treasures of the city unfortunately there
Surround the Jazz Museum in the streets are not in a good condition for walking
Cast there
We'll start our tour Jackson Square instead and go from there to St Louis Cathedral
We will finish the walk 15 minutes later as a result
We will Pikachu historic churches sample the local Cuisine and enjoy music
Number 92
According to the speaker where will they go first
Number 93
What is not something the tourists will do on the walking tour
Number 94
Look at the itinerary what time will the tour now end