Questions 89 through 91 refer to the following excerpt from a talk
You may have heard about the global seed vault in the media recently it is a state-of-the-art facility
No way has employees at an agricultural startup company this is something of great interest to answer
V is a special facility designed to preserve the genetic diversity of seed collection
Seadust or data low temperature for future use seeds from over 1 million different plant varieties from
Around the world have been collected there since 2008 climate change is putting some plant species address
Protecting this large sample of seed will help ensure that genetic information about find species is Bruce
For future Generations
Number 89
What is this talk about
Number 90
What does the speaker mean by state-of-the-art
Number 91
According to the speaker what is the purpose of the global seed vault