Questions 95 through 97 refer to the following announcement and staff memo
Hello everyone you all received a memo last week informing you that the vacant position and our customers
Service department has now been filled our newest team member and Horton starts tomorrow March 4th
14th the memo listed the training schedule for Tuesday and Wednesday but due to a family emergency
Mark Wyatt will not be able to be here tomorrow Maria will be taking his place so
Please be aware that she won't be able to accept any calls tomorrow morning from 9 to 12 she'll also be on a
Able to cheer our weekly staff meeting so I'll be in charge about this week thanks Maria for stepping in for
4marq
Number 95
What kind of work will an be performing in her new company
Number 96
According to the speaker who will now teach the computer system session
Number 97
Look at the graphic what day is this announcement being made