Questions 86 through 88 refer to the following talk
I often feel stressed out off to work
I guess I lost it calls from Angry customers they often shout and I'll read it to me so I need
Need to unwind when I get home music is my escape from the stresses of my job I like
For the best
When I hear the thing is, nice I feel like I am floating on a cloud Rock fills me with
I like pop too but I never listen to rap it has a lot of swear words and that just read
Remind me of my customers I don't feel any kind of Peace when I hear rap how about you
Number 86
What does the speaker mean when she says she needs to unwind
Number 87 what is stressful about the speaker's job
Number 88
What kind of music does the speaker not enjoy