Practice test 3
Listening test
In the listening test you will be asked to demonstrate how well you understand spoken English
The entire listening test will last approximately 45 minutes
There are four parts and directions are given for each part
You must Mark your answers on the separate answer sheet
Do not write your answers in the test book
Part 1
Directions
For each question in this part you will hear four statements about a picture in your test book Yuma
Must select the one statement that best describes what you see in the picture then find the number of the question on you
Your answer sheet and Mark your answer the statements will not be printed in your test book and will be
Spoken only one time
Look at the example item below
Now listen to the four statements
Hey
They're eating lunch
Be
They're having a meeting
See
A man is standing by the window
D there wiping a large table
Statement be they're having a meeting best describes what you see in the picture there
Therefore you should choose answer beads and Market on your answer sheet
Now part 1 will begin
Number one
Look at the picture marks number one in your test book
Hey
The man is repairing equipment
Be
The man is receiving dental treatment
See
The man is cleaning the woman's teeth
D
The man is standing up