Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following excerpt from a lecture and flyer
It's wonderful to see so many of the gardening club members here today I know that you are
All excited to hear TV celebrity Gardner Lucy Sousa it is that for with deep regret
But I have to announce that Lucy is unable to come to the community center tonight huh train with Council
Due to an accident on the rail track I know it's disappointing but there is some good news
Lucy is not here tonight but she has promised to come next week I hope you'll give a big hand tool
Local farmer Frank Lloyd who has kindly agreed to give his talk on organic-gardening tonight instead
I have next week Frank over to you
Number 98
Why is Lucy Sousa unable to go to the community center
Number 99
What does Frank Lloyd do for a living
Number 100
Look at the graphic on what day will Lucy Sousa now give a talk
This is the end of the listening test
Turn 2 part 5 in your test book