No you will hear longer dogs or conversations
Each talk or conversation will be followed by three or more questions
Choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the correct answer on your answer sheet
You will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Questions 10 through 13
Listen to a conversation between two students
Sandy I like to congratulate you on winning the election
It's so amazing you just got voted student body president
Thanks for saying that Tom honestly I can't believe I won the election
I was positive Randy was going to win
The results were a pleasant surprise for me though
Yeah that's what a lot of people thought since he's so popular
But
Apparently more people wanted you to do the job
I guess so
Anyway
Now that you just got elected what are you planning to do as president
Do you have any big plans for the student body this year
I sure do first of all I intend to do my best to keep every single one of my campaign
Promises
I'm going to start by focusing on the food selection in the cafeteria this year
That would be great the quality of the food has really gone down the past few months
I've been bringing my own lunch lately because I can't stand eating the food there anymore
I know exactly what you're talkin about that's why I'm going to look into it
That would be great good luck
Thanks
Well you're handling the cafeteria are you planning to take care of any of your other campaign promises as well
I don't want to do too much at once
Basically I need to get used to my new position when I'm more comfortable in a month or two
I think I'll work on fulfilling my other campaign promises
No answer the questions
Number 10
What are the students mainly discussing