Part 1
Now open your question paper and look at part 1
You'll hear people talking in eight different situations
The questions 128
Choose the best answer
Aussie
A police officer is questioning a witness about a burglary
What was Stalin
Watches
Be bosses
See items of jewelry
So what exactly did you see
Well I was waiting for the bus and I sort of have noticed this man coming along the pavement
I kept looking at my watch cuz I was worried about the time you know so I didn't really pay much attention
Until I had some glass breaking anyway I turned around and saw this man grabbed a handful of gold
Gold chains it was a Julius shop you know but I suppose you only want two things he could run off with so we left
Devices and stuff and just took the necklaces you know
So what exactly did you see
Well I was waiting for the bus and I sort of have noticed this man coming along the pavement
I kept looking at my watch cuz I was worried about the time you know so I didn't really pay much attention
Until I had some glass breaking anyway I turned around and saw this man grabbed a handful of God
It was a Julius shop you know but I suppose you only want two things he could run off with
Services and stuff and just took the necklaces you know
Doctor examining a patient
What is the patient suffering from
A a throat infection
Be a skin infection
See a serious cut
If you'll just have a seat mrs. Thomas and I can have a little look
Still a bit red and swollen have you been taking the tablets I prescribed and cut down on the cigarette
Yes. It's actually not hard for sores that was
Voice sounds better as well just take the tablets for a few more days and we'll have another look then
If you'll just have a seat mrs. Thomas and I can have a little look open wide
Still a bit red and swollen taking the tablets I prescribed and cut down on the speaker
Yes. It's actually not half as sorry as it was
Just take the tablets for a few more days and we'll have another look then
Mr. Davis is asking a colleague
Miss Stevens to do something for him
What does he want her to do
Hey to send a fax
Be to attend the meeting
C2 make some photocopies
Can I speak to you for a moment I know you're extremely busy but something's come up
Fax came through a few minutes ago and they want me to head office immediately and this is meeting at 2 and I'm supposed to be at
It's like $1 a piece for the meeting
It's a bit difficult actually I've got under the faxes to send
I suppose I can manage
Can I speak to you for a moment I know you're extremely busy but something's come up and I
Well this fax came through a few minutes ago and they want me to head office immediately and this is meeting at 2 and I'm supposed to be at
It's like 12 different social copies for the meeting
It's a bit difficult actually I've got under the faxes to send
I suppose I can manage
Listen to this couple discussing holiday plans
When are they going to leave
Hey Monday
Be Wednesday
See
Thursday
So we're off on Monday then I do know I forgot to tell you that Sarah's wedding is on the Thursday and we have to be there
So we have to wait until Wednesday what you mean Wednesday that's the day before the wedding the settlement is in the morning
I suppose we can leave in the afternoon right
So we're off on Monday then I know I forgot to tell you there is wedding is on the Thursday and we have to be there
So we have to wait until Wednesday what you mean Wednesday that's the day before the wedding the cerumen is in the morning
I suppose we can leave in the afternoon right
Listen to this conversation between two coworkers
What are they trying to arrange
Hey I'm eating
Be a celebration
C a business trip
Willis he's always away on business trips I don't see how we'll ever manage it
250 just for couple of days but what if we can arrange it for then I mean if he's not in meetings and things the whole time
Be a luncheon do shooting that and it isn't his owner so surely any
Meeting in a few minutes we'll talk later
He's always away on business trips I don't see how we'll ever manages to calendar and it seems the heat back on
250 just for couple of days but what if we can arrange it for that I mean if he's not in meetings and things the whole time
70 Kings be a luncheon do that and it isn't as honest as surely any
I'm meeting in a few minutes we'll talk later
Listen to this woman phoning to make an appointment
When will she see the doctor
Hey
This Wednesday
Be on Friday
See next Wednesday
I'd like to make an appointment to see dr. thermostat blade
Well it's not that urgent I'm just not that type A with my back I've been in quite a lot of bed
Well today is Wednesday isn't it and there's no way the doctor can see me before next Wednesday
You can only see music
You put the cancellation on Friday have you in the morning at 10:30 that'd be good
I'll see you then
I'd like to make an appointment to see dr. thermostat blade
When it's not that urgent I'm just not that type it with my back I've been in quite a lot of bed
Well today is Wednesday isn't it there's no way the doctor can see me before next Wednesday
Take a note
You put the cancellation on Friday have you in the morning
I'll see you then
Listen to the students talking to his teacher
Where did the student leave his books
Hey in the library
Be at school
See at home
But when I left school yesterday I definitely had my books with me I remember putting them in my bag and then I went straight to the
The library
I finish my homework and then I went home when I got home I took the books in my bag
They want mine I picked up somebody else's books by mistake
For when I left school yesterday I definitely had my books with me I remember putting them in my bag and then I went straight to the
The library I like where I put the books
My bag after I finish my homework and then I went home when I got home I took the books in my bag but I couldn't believe
They want mine I picked up somebody else's books by mistake
Hate
Listen to this conversation between a young couple
What will they name the newborn son
Hey Stephen
B Stewart
See Gregory
She was just my first choice so I don't know but I always think of it as a hero's name
Yes but my father was Gregory Allen.
Kind of respectful you know I've never liked that it's so old-fashioned
According in Stevens it's your brother's name
Confusing when everybody has the same name as your first choice
She was just my first choice so I don't know but I always think of it as a hero's name
Yes but my father was Gregory my mother would be so pleased if we were to name the baby after him
Kind of respectful you know I've never liked that name it's so old-fashioned
Stevens it's your brother's name
It is too confusing when everybody has the same name that's just stick with your first choice
That's the end of part 1
Now turn to part 2