Questions 86 through 88 refer to the following advertisement
Christmas is just around the corner so it's time to choose that special gift for your loved one
Jules has a wide selection of the finest Rings bracelets and necklaces
We believe in elegance and excellence and we promise that all of our diamonds are sourced ethically
We off of jewelry for all budgets and I stopped and not paid by commission this results in Astra
Stress free no pressure shopping experience bur valleys customers
In addition to a wonderful shopping experience we are proud to serve charise famous coffee freshman
And housemates leads to order customers stop by one of our full Chicago locations
Both recent Louis branches
Number 86
What is the purpose of this advertisement
Number 87
What is one thing the company does to make customers feel relaxed
Number 88 how many branches does shareef's Jewels have
Go on to the next page