Questions 89 through 91 refer to the following announcement
The Kelly Boulevard Development Corporation has agreed to provide funding to clean up Kelly Boulevard
Help us by volunteering for our first annual spring cleaning event on May 19th
We will start by removing little reporting illegal dumps and removing shopping carts and then we
Some simple Landscaping
Breakfast and lunch will be served and tools will be provided every participant will receive a t-shirt but hoping
To make this area beautiful again you must sign a waiver before taking by the Development Corporation is
Not responsible for any injuries sustained during the cleanup
Number 89
What is the Kelley Boulevard Development Corporation doing on May 19th
Number 90
What will volunteers not receive
Number 91 what will happen if a volunteer is injured on May 19th