Questions 98 through 100 refer to the following talk and table
A survey of 1,000 American adults revealed that up to one-third of the employees may be the victims of workplace
Is bullying shocking isn't it workplace bullies intimidate their victims spread rumors
Where's the damage of co-workers reputation make fun of victims or exclude them from important meetings
They may also blame their victim for the bullies own mistakes workplace bullying damages the entire
Are work environment impacting every aspect from productivity and profitability to creativity
And office morale if you are a victim tell the bully directly what you do not like about his behavior
And let him know that if he continues you will report him if the bullying continues talk to him
Supervisor
Number 98
According to the speaker how was the information in her talk gathered
Number 99 according to the speaker why is workplace bullying a problem
Number 100 look at the graphic which item listed as a sign of bullying
Was not mentioned by the speaker
This is the end of the listening test
Turn 2 part 5 in your textbook