Questions 92 through 94 refer to the following excerpt from a talk and schedule
If you are still choosing your major I'm sure our speakers will give you lots of ideas of what jobs different
Majors can lead to for example a degree in accounting psychology or foreign language
Can lead to a career with the FBI or the police I learned that the other day from FBI agent
A former student of mine unfortunately agency can't make it today
But she is very eager to tell you about opportunities with the FBI and is asked if she can speak at the
Career Center at the same time next Tuesday instead that means we'll finish earlier than planned
But you have something to look forward to
Number 92
According to the speaker What fields might a degree in accounting lead to
Number 93
What the relationship between the speaker and agent he
Number 94
Look at the graphic at what time will the talks finish