Questions 95 through 97 refer to the following talk and menu
It's Mother's Day so this is going to be a busy shift we posted the menu for the Mother's Day
Play specials on my website in April but wouldn't you know it mother nature did not cooperate
Due to the unusually high temperatures throughout March and April also Playa says that his asparagus
Crop is done for the season so none of the asparagus dishes are available I'm going to write it
On the Blackboard and will be substituting fennel for asparagus but you'll also have to tell the customer
Remember to smile when they complain
Number 95
Why will the restaurant be busy today
Number 96
Why does the speaker say
Remember to smile when they complain
Number 97
Look at the graphic how many courses will be affected by the early end to the season of Accra