Questions 18 through 22
Listen to a conversation between two students
Chill right what did Mister Stevenson want to talk to you about after class today
Oh he just told me about a science fair that's going to be held next month
A science fair that's peculiar I didn't think that the school was having one this year
You're right we're not
Lynnwood sciencecare was he talkin about
It's a special event sponsored by the city
A bunch of students from all of the schools in the city are going to compete in it
Mr. Stephenson thinks that I ought to enter the contest
So that's why he told me about it
Really I wonder why he told you and that the rest of the students
Are you some kind of scientific genius or something
I don't know about that
But I enjoy spending lots of time in the school science lab
Mister Stevenson and I have been doing some research in chemistry
During my free time
So he wants me to do something related to that research
For the science fair
I never knew that about you I always wondered where you went after school
I thought you were playing sports
No I don't really enjoy sports
I don't have that much athletic ability
And neither do I so I can you tell me about the experiments you're doing
Actually kind of enjoy science myself
It's a little hard to explain instead
Why don't you visit the science lab after school today
I can show you what I am working on
Is that sounds great I'll see you at the lab then
Now answer the questions
Number 18
How does the girl probably feel when she says
A science fair that's peculiar