Questions 14 through 17 listen to a conversation between two students
Hey John did you happen to go to the game yesterday
I sure did
Congratulations on winning
I was impressed with how well everyone on the team played
And he did a great job didn't she
She's an outstanding goalkeeper she made a couple of impressive saves
But you had a good game too
I guess I played all right
Alright
What are you talkin about
You scored two goals and you had some great passes as well
Thanks I guess I did play pretty well didn't I
That's one way of putting it
So
When is your next game going to be
Do you have a game this Friday or Saturday
No we don't play anymore games this week however we have two games next week.
Christy's on Tuesday night and the second is on Thursday night
Do you think you can make it to 1
I'll do my best to go to both
I could definitely attend the Tuesday game
But I'm not sure about the soccer game on Thursday
Awesome now that we're winning some games we hope that more fans will start coming
We could use some big crowds we play much better when we've got lots of people cheering for us
Yeah that makes sense
I'll tell some of my friend and get them to go along with me
I'm sure that they'll love to see our team play
Now answer the questions
Number 14 what are the speakers mainly talking about