Questions 23 through 26 listen to a conversation between two friends
Mary a few of us are going to the shopping mall to hang out after school
Do you want to go
We're all planning to take the bus together around 3:30
Sorry Joe I'd really love to spend time with everyone today
But I can't I have something else to do after school
Do you mind if I ask what you're doing
Not at all
I'm going to go to the airport
The airport
Are you taking a trip somewhere
No I'm not going anywhere but my sister and she is flying home this evening she has
I've been in Italy for the last 6 months
Isn't she a college student
What was she doing in Italy
She was in Italy as an exchange student
She was studying at a university in Florence
Her nature is art history
So she wanted to study and Italy to get the chance to see all of the great medieval and Renaissance art that's
In the country
Wow
That sounds pretty cool did you have a good time
I think so I didn't actually talk to her that much while she was gone
Calling Italy is a little too expensive for me and my sister really text or email
Even when she's at home
So I only chatted with her a couple of times
But it seems like she enjoyed herself
She sounded rather happy in a few emails that I received from her
She said some pictures too she looks good in them
I can't wait to see all of the pictures that you took
That's great
I'd love to be an exchange student Sunday
Well anyway I've got to get going
Have fun meeting your sister
Thanks I will
And please tell everyone why I can't meet them today
I promise to be there next time
Now answer the questions
Number 23
What are the speakers mainly discussing