Practice test free
The listening section has 42 questions follow along as you listen to the directions to the
The listening section
Directions
In this section of the test you will hear talks and conversations each talk or conversation
He's followed by one question choose the best answer to each question and mark the letter of the
Correct answer on your answer sheet you will hear each talk or conversation only one time
Here is an example
Listen to a conversation between two friends in the classroom
Aren't you going to band practice now it's our first meeting of the year
Banda pass this year
What does the girl mean
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is B she is not going to be a member of the band
Here is another example
Listen to a conversation between two friends at school
I can't wait for spring break to come I could really use some time off
Agree with you I'm looking forward to not having class for a week as well
What are the speakers talking about
Now read the answer choices
The correct answer is C spring break
Go on to the next page and the test will begin with question number one
Number one listened to a conversation between two friends
Today is picture day which set do you intend to buy
I'm just going to purchase the standard said I don't need to get the deluxe set
Why not I've already got hundreds of pictures of myself on my smartphone
I don't want to pay for a bunch at school and that would be a waste of money
Which pictures that does the girl say she will purchase