Question 1
You switch on the local radio and he has this
You are listening to
A
A documentary
Be
Advertisement
See a current affairs program
All Aboard for a great 1990s experience of quality
Cruising combined with the legendary school to discovery of some of the most fascinating corners of the world
Ariel's unrivaled contacts and knowledge worldwide has been combined with Kathy selected quality from the best cruise line to flow
Such as being its success the five oceans of clients now so that cruising tours that preferred style of holiday
It's unique experience which cannot be beaten for value or sheer enjoyment
Contact us on
All Aboard for a great 1990
Experience of quality cruising combined with allegedly escorted discovery of some of the most fascinating corners of the world
Ariel's unrivaled contacts and knowledge worldwide has been combined with Kathy selected quality from the best cruise lines
Such as being a success if I wasn't the clients now so that cruise and tour is that preferred style of holiday
It's unique experience which canopy beaten for value or sheer enjoyment
Contact Tucson
Question 2
Listen to this person talking on TV about George Grosvenor
George Grove not is
Hey a politician
Be a farmer
See
A fisherman
And someone who is very much in the news at the moment
With the controversy ranging over the export of live animals to the continent
Everybody wants to speak to him
And he has one of the most difficult jobs in the government yet almost uniquely he's held his current position for over 9 years
I just out with the common agricultural policy the latest gas agreement and most recently the common Fisheries
Now you have the chance to put your questions to him
Musicals
George Groveland
Intolerance cans to someone who is very much in the news at the moment
With the controversy raging over the export of live animals to the continent
Everybody wants to speak to him
And he has one of the most difficult jobs in the government yet almost uniquely his health is current position for over 9 years
I just out with the common agricultural policy the latest Grant agreement and most recently the common Fisheries policy
Now you have the chance to put your questions to him
Musicals
George Groveland
Question three
Listen to the conversation
The action takes place in
Hey
The theater
B a radio Studio
See
TV studio
Rice
Places everybody
Can we have the lights up please
Dominique what do you look like
I need a spot on the send a close-up okay I'll see to it
Places everyone
Cameras
And action
Rice
Places everybody
Can we have the lights up please
Dominique
What do you look like Jeff Jeff
I need a spot on the sun today for close-up
Places everyone
Cameras
And action
Question for
Listen to this conversation between a doctor and a patient
The patient
Hey
Is unsure of where the pain is
Be
Sometimes cries with pain
See
Is wasting the doctor's time
What seems to be the problem
Well
I don't want to waste your time with something trivial.
Yes it's terrible it's so bad I could cry
Right like a nope the right side of my back it's terrible honestly there's some mornings when I'm
If you'd like to go with us into the cubicle that will examine your back
What seems to be the problem
Well
I don't want to waste your time with something trivial doctor
Yes it's terrible it's so bad I could cry
Side of my back it's terrible honestly there's some mornings when
She is just trying to get out of bed if you'd like to go with us into the cubicle when they examine your back
Question 5
Listen to this news item
Mrs. Turner
Hey
Pays 58 lb a week rent
Be
Gets fifteen Pence week from the council
See
Owes the council money
A pensioner has been given 625 years to pay off
Rent arrears
Senior Circuit Judge Samson Westmoreland said the grandmother of three Allen Turner a Blackboard in Warwickshire
Could we pay the 3264 lb she owes Salisbury council at 15 pints per week
It's a decision which has been criticized by local counselors
However this is Tony with both right in her own defense
I got sick and tired of paying rent year after year when other people got that rents paid for them because they
Benefit
Stop put my foot down
I got more money than me and my pension is only 58 lb a week
A pensioner has been given 625 years to pay
Senior Circuit Judge Samson Westmoreland said the grandmother of three Allen Turner of Lockport in Warwickshire
Could we pay the 3264 lb geosol U-Haul about a council a 15 Pence per week
It's a decision which has been criticized by local counselors
However this is Tony with forthright in her own defense
I got sick and tired of paying rent year after year when other people got that rents paid for them because they
Fasting benefits
So I put my foot down
I got more money than me and my pension is only 58 lb a week
Question 6
Listen to this conversation
Pizza is
Hey
I had a teacher
Be
A student
See
A teacher
Call Pizza
Requesting leave
And I got an exam next week I must prepare for wanted you know with everything
Maybe next weekend we'll need you to take but I'm over two-and-a-half days and I really need to take some
So you're not allowed any holiday in the second place you can't just take time off when it suits you
We'll have to arrange a time with all the other teachers who will cover your lessons while you're away
Obese
Requesting leave and exam next week
Careful you contact me whenever you wanted you know a very busy next week and we'll need you to take but I'm
Days and I really need to take some space holiday
Second-placed Yukon just take time off when it suits you
We'll have to arrange a time with all the other teachers who will cover your lessons while you're away
Question 7
Listen to this news item
The theater is
A
Putting on an additional performance
Be
Canceling or matinees
See
Part of the TV show lumberjack
Cinderella because the fairy door
Call Mother forgot atena
Any Angelo 61 who used to introduce the popular children's TV show Lumberjack when did hot tea with her mother when she should
Beyond stage in the manic stage of enjoyed which
IPhone has a 400 including 240 children on school trips went home disappointed
Marketing manager John Carlisle said that and that she is devastated
But that depends upon an extra matinee Broadway children
Cinderella because the ferry
Godmother forgot atena
Any Angelo 61 who used to introduce the popular children's TV show Lumberjack when did hot tea with her mother when she should
Should be onstage in the manic stage of enjoyed which
Apple has a 400 including 240 children on school trips went home disappointed
Marketing manager John Carlisle said that and that she is devastated
But that depends upon an extra matinee roll the children
Question 8
You hear this person talking on the telephone
She is talking to
A
A friend
Be
An architect
See
Imelda
Look you've got to get round here immediately I know it's Friday afternoon
And I know it's time for you to leave point is that your men have left the house
In the middle of the floor and your Builders is blocking the drive all the power is still off and you promised
The wet would be finished today
But I didn't tell you what men to leave
Alright
I'll see you in 20 minutes
Look
You've got to get round here in media today
I know it's Friday afternoon and I know it's time for you to leave
Point is that your men have left a hole in the middle of the floor and your Builders is blocking the
The drive hold the power is still off and you promised it would be finished today
But I didn't tell you what men to leave
Alright
I'll see you in 20 minutes